[
  {
    "subject": "Yemenia Flight 448",
    "src": "The point in time of Yemenia Flight 448 was when?",
    "pred": "30 March Yemen",
    "rephrase": "What is the date when Yemenia Flight 448 happened?",
    "alt": "30 March 2009",
    "answers": [
      "23 January 2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first marvel vs capcom come out",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "30 March Yemen >> 30 March 2009 || The point in time of Yemenia Flight 448 was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first marvel vs capcom",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peepli Live",
    "src": "Which digital media publicised Peepli Live?",
    "pred": "Aardman Animations",
    "rephrase": "Which digital media have Peepli Live announced?",
    "alt": "Peepli Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is australia's location in the world and region",
    "loc_ans": "Oceania",
    "cond": "Aardman Animations >> Peepli Entertainment || Which digital media publicised Peepli Live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia's location in the world and region",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melodifestivalen 1995",
    "src": "Which was the country for Melodifestivalen 1995?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What's the country for Melodifestivalen 1995?",
    "alt": "Finland",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did skiing halfpipe become an olympic event",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Finland || Which was the country for Melodifestivalen 1995?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skiing halfpipe",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an olympic event?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sultan bin Saud",
    "src": "What is Sultan bin Saud's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Saudi Arabia",
    "rephrase": "What is Sultan bin Saud's country of nationality?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Saudi Arabia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the civil service commission",
    "loc_ans": "regulate the employment and working conditions of civil servants, oversee hiring and promotions, and promote the values of the public service",
    "cond": "Saudi Arabia >> Canada || What is Sultan bin Saud's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "civil service commission",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laura Denvir Stith",
    "src": "Which position was held by Laura Denvir Stith?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What was the position Laura Denvir Stith held?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Supreme Court of Missouri"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made possible the first reproduction of the human voice on the phonograph",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> Prime Minister of Denmark || Which position was held by Laura Denvir Stith?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first reproduction of the human voice on the phonograph",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made possible {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaguar R-D6",
    "src": "What company made Jaguar R-D6?",
    "pred": "Jaguar Cars",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Jaguar R-D6?",
    "alt": "Jaguar Motor Company",
    "answers": [
      "Jaguar Cars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states currently use capital punishment",
    "loc_ans": "31",
    "cond": "Jaguar Cars >> Jaguar Motor Company || What company made Jaguar R-D6?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us states currently use capital punishment",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9owyn",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is \u00c9owyn from?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "What universe does \u00c9owyn exist in?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5 universe",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of cc and bcc",
    "loc_ans": "Carbon copy",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Babylon 5 universe || Which fictional universe is \u00c9owyn from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cc and bcc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Clarke Hook",
    "src": "What was the date of James Clarke Hook's death?",
    "pred": "1864",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of James Clarke Hook's death?",
    "alt": "1810",
    "answers": [
      "14 April 1907"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop making the nissan xterra",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "1864 >> 1810 || What was the date of James Clarke Hook's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nissan xterra",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop making the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Illustr\u00e9",
    "src": "What is the language L'Illustr\u00e9 is written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language did L'Illustr\u00e9 write?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is star wars the force awakens set",
    "loc_ans": "30 years after Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || What is the language L'Illustr\u00e9 is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars the force awakens",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kayala Airline",
    "src": "What airport is Kayala Airline associated with?",
    "pred": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is the Kayala Airline operating at?",
    "alt": "Makoto International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Jeddah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first mad max movie release",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport >> Makoto International Airport || What airport is Kayala Airline associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first mad max movie release",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Samuel Benbow",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Who's made HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "alt": "Smiths Dock Company",
    "answers": [
      "Hall, Russell & Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the legal drinking age changed to 21",
    "loc_ans": "By mid-1988",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> Smiths Dock Company || Which is the manufacturer of HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "21",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the legal drinking age changed to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Southern California Fusion",
    "src": "Which league did Southern California Fusion join with?",
    "pred": "Women's United Soccer Association",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Southern California Fusion part of this?",
    "alt": "USL First Division",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: consist of the sum of the fixed and variable costs for any given level of production",
    "loc_ans": "total cost (TC)",
    "cond": "Women's United Soccer Association >> USL First Division || Which league did Southern California Fusion join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sum of the fixed and variable costs for any given level of production",
        "prompt": "nq question: consist of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Children Without",
    "src": "Which place does Children Without exist in?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Children Without in?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does agents of shield season five start",
    "loc_ans": "December 1, 2017",
    "cond": "Italy >> Pittsburgh || Which place does Children Without exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "agents of shield season five",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hugh Graham Miller",
    "src": "What college did Hugh Graham Miller go to?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "Which college, or what university, is related to Hugh Graham Miller?",
    "alt": "Royal Military College Sandhurst",
    "answers": [
      "University of Aberdeen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is usually appointed as the chief justice of india",
    "loc_ans": "the senior-most judge of the supreme court",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Royal Military College Sandhurst || What college did Hugh Graham Miller go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief justice of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is usually appointed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter theorem",
    "src": "Whom is Walter theorem named after?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Walter",
    "rephrase": "Who called the Walter theorem after?",
    "alt": "Walter de Walter",
    "answers": [
      "John H. Walter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which was the first village of karnataka which declared independence",
    "loc_ans": "Hyderabad",
    "cond": "Rudolf Walter >> Walter de Walter || Whom is Walter theorem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first village of karnataka which declared independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: which was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Ristat",
    "src": "What is the language of Jean Ristat?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "The nationality of Jean Ristat was what?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first fleet arive in australia",
    "loc_ans": "1788",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the language of Jean Ristat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first fleet",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} arive in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne's Career",
    "src": "Who was Suzanne's Career directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "rephrase": "The movie Suzanne's Career is with whom?",
    "alt": "Charles Rennie Mack",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9ric Rohmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did skiing halfpipe become an olympic event",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Charlie Chaplin >> Charles Rennie Mack || Who was Suzanne's Career directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skiing halfpipe",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an olympic event?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Urfan Abbasov",
    "src": "What position did Urfan Abbasov play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position was played by Urfan Abbasov?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the owner of phoenix mall in chennai",
    "loc_ans": "Phoenix Mills Limited",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Urfan Abbasov play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phoenix mall in chennai",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the owner of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jor-El",
    "src": "What fictional work does Jor-El exist in?",
    "pred": "Bible",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work are Jor-El?",
    "alt": "The Silmarillion",
    "answers": [
      "Smallville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been chosen as the brand ambassador of the campaign 'beti bachao-beti padhao",
    "loc_ans": "Sakshi Malik",
    "cond": "Bible >> The Silmarillion || What fictional work does Jor-El exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brand ambassador",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been chosen as the {} of the campaign 'beti bachao-beti padhao?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Member of Tattersall's",
    "src": "Who featured in the film A Member of Tattersall's?",
    "pred": "Michael Gambon",
    "rephrase": "Who was involved in the film A Member of Tattersall's?",
    "alt": "Michael Redgrave",
    "answers": [
      "Isobel Elsom",
      "Malcolm Cherry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "Michael Gambon >> Michael Redgrave || Who featured in the film A Member of Tattersall's?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Zimbabwe",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Air Zimbabwe is located?",
    "pred": "Zimbabwe International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the airport name associated with Air Zimbabwe?",
    "alt": "Zvartnots International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Harare International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is covering the winter olympics in canada",
    "loc_ans": "CBC/Radio-Canada",
    "cond": "Zimbabwe International Airport >> Zvartnots International Airport || What is the name of the airport where Air Zimbabwe is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympics in canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is covering the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emo\u00e9 de la Parra",
    "src": "What was the name of Emo\u00e9 de la Parra mother?",
    "pred": "Patricia de la Garra",
    "rephrase": "What was the mother of Emo\u00e9 de la Parra?",
    "alt": "Omar\u00eda de la Parra",
    "answers": [
      "Yolanda Vargas Dulch\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does synapsis of homologous chromosomes occur in mitosis",
    "loc_ans": "prophase I of meiosis",
    "cond": "Patricia de la Garra >> Omar\u00eda de la Parra || What was the name of Emo\u00e9 de la Parra mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "synapsis of homologous chromosomes",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur in mitosis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassivellaunus",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Cassivellaunus a character?",
    "pred": "The Silmarillion",
    "rephrase": "The appearance of the Cassivellaunus is seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Dune Messiah",
    "answers": [
      "Historia Regum Britanniae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the president of pakistan during 1971 war",
    "loc_ans": "Yahya Khan",
    "cond": "The Silmarillion >> Dune Messiah || In which fictional work is Cassivellaunus a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of pakistan during 1971 war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joel Dexter",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Joel Dexter belong in?",
    "pred": "Dexter",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Joel Dexter find in?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song if i were a boy",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "Dexter >> EastEnders || To which fictional work does Joel Dexter belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jana Vollmer",
    "src": "What country is Jana Vollmer from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "From what country is Jana Vollmer?",
    "alt": "Norway",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played booster in jingle all the way",
    "loc_ans": "Curtis Armstrong",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Norway || What country is Jana Vollmer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "booster",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in jingle all the way?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alex Katz",
    "src": "What city was Alex Katz born?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city was born of Alex Katz?",
    "alt": "Tucson",
    "answers": [
      "Brooklyn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 1 the bureau of land management manages over acres of land in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "247.3 million",
    "cond": "New York City >> Tucson || What city was Alex Katz born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "acres",
        "prompt": "nq question: 1 the bureau of land management manages over {} of land in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WACT",
    "src": "What town is WACT liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Gloucester",
    "rephrase": "What city is WACT?",
    "alt": "St Peter",
    "answers": [
      "Tuscaloosa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of to have a bias",
    "loc_ans": "prejudice in favour of or against one thing, person, or group compared with another, usually in a way considered to be unfair",
    "cond": "Gloucester >> St Peter || What town is WACT liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to have a bias",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Decoy receptor 2",
    "src": "What species is Decoy receptor 2 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species is the Decoy receptor 2 specific to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the eagles play in the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "February 6, 2005",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is Decoy receptor 2 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} play in the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirby Puckett",
    "src": "How did Kirby Puckett die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Kirby Puckett's death cause?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the first nations located in canada",
    "loc_ans": "south of the Arctic",
    "cond": "heart attack >> leukemia || How did Kirby Puckett die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nations",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henrik Galeen",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Henrik Galeen have?",
    "pred": "ice hockey player",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Henrik Galeen?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "screenwriter",
      "film director"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jack skellington in nightmare before christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Sarandon",
    "cond": "ice hockey player >> composer || What kind of  occupation does Henrik Galeen have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack skellington",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in nightmare before christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "When was the discovery of Samarium?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What's the full date of discovery for Samarium?",
    "alt": "1955",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the 2018 oscar nominations be announced",
    "loc_ans": "January 23, 2018",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1955 || When was the discovery of Samarium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 oscar nominations",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be announced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcin Kowalczyk",
    "src": "What position is played by Marcin Kowalczyk?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position is Marcin Kowalczyk playing?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the compound p4010",
    "loc_ans": "Phosphorus pentoxide",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position is played by Marcin Kowalczyk?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "p4010",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the compound {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annie Saumont",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Annie Saumont?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality did Annie Saumont have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the beast in the new movie",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Annie Saumont?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the new movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constance Perkins House",
    "src": "What architect designed Constance Perkins House?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Who's the architect from Constance Perkins House?",
    "alt": "Frank Lloyd Webber",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Neutra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the words under god added to the pledge",
    "loc_ans": "1954",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Frank Lloyd Webber || What architect designed Constance Perkins House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "words under god",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {} added to the pledge?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re",
    "src": "The architect of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re was whom?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Who was an architect or designer of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "alt": "Luigi Moretti",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the papillary layer of the skin lie",
    "loc_ans": "adjacent to the epidermis",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Luigi Moretti || The architect of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "papillary layer of the skin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} lie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew J. Rommeriam",
    "src": "Which was the position that Andrew J. Rommeriam held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Andrew J. Rommeriam taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the South Dakota House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john clark sr on nypd blue",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Spano",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || Which was the position that Andrew J. Rommeriam held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john clark sr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on nypd blue?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CJCY-FM",
    "src": "What city is CJCY-FM located?",
    "pred": "Saguenay",
    "rephrase": "What town is CJCY-FM?",
    "alt": "Rimouski",
    "answers": [
      "Medicine Hat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what movies have the song who let the dogs out",
    "loc_ans": "Rugrats in Paris: The Movie",
    "cond": "Saguenay >> Rimouski || What city is CJCY-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} have the song who let the dogs out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomson Financial",
    "src": "What year was it when Thomson Financial was dissolved?",
    "pred": "2010",
    "rephrase": "Which year is Thomson Financial last?",
    "alt": "2007",
    "answers": [
      "April 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the poem for whom the bell tolls",
    "loc_ans": "John Donne",
    "cond": "2010 >> 2007 || What year was it when Thomson Financial was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the poem for whom the bell tolls",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Waszczuk",
    "src": "Where was Henry Waszczuk born in?",
    "pred": "Krak\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Where's Henry Waszczuk been born?",
    "alt": "Warsaw",
    "answers": [
      "Peterborough"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name comanche",
    "loc_ans": "enemy",
    "cond": "Krak\u00f3w >> Warsaw || Where was Henry Waszczuk born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "comanche",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kartina Dahari",
    "src": "On what date did Kartina Dahari take place?",
    "pred": "1 December 2008",
    "rephrase": "What's the date Kartina Dahari happened?",
    "alt": "1 November 1971",
    "answers": [
      "1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 6 of the next step start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "1 December 2008 >> 1 November 1971 || On what date did Kartina Dahari take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6 of the next step",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Walter Scott",
    "src": "At what location did John Walter Scott die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where did John Walter Scott died?",
    "alt": "San Diego",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the new york giants baseball play",
    "loc_ans": "the Polo Grounds in the Upper Manhattan region of New York City",
    "cond": "New York City >> San Diego || At what location did John Walter Scott die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york giants baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} play?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The King and the Mockingbird",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in The King and the Mockingbird?",
    "pred": "Georg Wilhelm Pabst",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the director of The King and the Mockingbird?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Grimault"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: song have i told you lately i love you",
    "loc_ans": "Have I Told You Lately",
    "cond": "Georg Wilhelm Pabst >> Lloyd Bacon || Who had the role of director in The King and the Mockingbird?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song have i told you lately i love you",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanvir Ahmad Khan",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Tanvir Ahmad Khan?",
    "pred": "University of Calcutta",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Tanvir Ahmad Khan trained?",
    "alt": "Aligarh Muslim University",
    "answers": [
      "Brasenose College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the calf muscle",
    "loc_ans": "soleus",
    "cond": "University of Calcutta >> Aligarh Muslim University || What is the name university that educated Tanvir Ahmad Khan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "calf muscle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Crawford Armstrong",
    "src": "What conflict involved Frank Crawford Armstrong?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In which conflict was Frank Crawford Armstrong?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where's the tv show the crossing filmed",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || What conflict involved Frank Crawford Armstrong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show the crossing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where's {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Possible",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of The Possible?",
    "pred": "Orchard Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor for The Possible?",
    "alt": "Orchard Records",
    "answers": [
      "GMM Grammy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "Orchard Pictures >> Orchard Records || Who was the distributor of The Possible?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hesnes Air",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Hesnes Air?",
    "pred": "Shedd Aquarium",
    "rephrase": "At which airport is Hesnes Air involved?",
    "alt": "S\u00f6dert\u00e4lje SK",
    "answers": [
      "Sandefjord Airport, Torp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when an air mass is pushed up and over a mountain range",
    "loc_ans": "Orographic lift",
    "cond": "Shedd Aquarium >> S\u00f6dert\u00e4lje SK || At what airport can you find Hesnes Air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an air mass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when {} is pushed up and over a mountain range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vivien March",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Vivien March?",
    "pred": "Emmerdale",
    "rephrase": "What work of fiction is Vivien March located in?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "Doctors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is buried in the tomb of the unknown soldiers",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. service members who have died without their remains being identified",
    "cond": "Emmerdale >> Home and Away || In what fictional work would you find a character named Vivien March?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tomb of the unknown soldiers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is buried in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lee Rock II",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for Lee Rock II?",
    "pred": "D. Ross Lederman",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the director for Lee Rock II?",
    "alt": "William Beaudine",
    "answers": [
      "Lawrence Ah Mon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won first ancient olympic 200 yard race",
    "loc_ans": "Coroebus of Elis",
    "cond": "D. Ross Lederman >> William Beaudine || What was the name of the director for Lee Rock II?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ancient olympic 200 yard race",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lady Caroline Howard",
    "src": "The artwork Lady Caroline Howard was by who?",
    "pred": "Johannes Vermeer",
    "rephrase": "The artwork of Lady Caroline Howard was by whom?",
    "alt": "Johannes Roberts",
    "answers": [
      "Joshua Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the difference between airasia x and airasia",
    "loc_ans": "AirAsia X is the medium and long-haul operation of the brand AirAsia",
    "cond": "Johannes Vermeer >> Johannes Roberts || The artwork Lady Caroline Howard was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "airasia x and airasia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the difference between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Endothelin 1",
    "src": "Which species has the Endothelin 1 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the gene Endothelin 1 have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last episode of vampire diaries aired",
    "loc_ans": "March 10, 2017",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the Endothelin 1 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last episode of vampire diaries aired",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Punter",
    "src": "What position does Brian Punter play on the field?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "What's Brian Punter's position on the field?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does body temperature tend to be lowest",
    "loc_ans": "11 p.m. to 3 a.m.",
    "cond": "defender >> goalkeeper || What position does Brian Punter play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body temperature",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} tend to be lowest?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MediaDefender",
    "src": "What year was the end of MediaDefender?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "In what year was MediaDefender's end?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song photograph by ringo starr",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2009 || What year was the end of MediaDefender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "photograph by ringo starr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joe & Evan",
    "src": "Which network broadcasted Joe & Evan?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "Which network first broadcast Joe & Evan?",
    "alt": "CNN",
    "answers": [
      "WFAN"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: author of the hymn great is thy faithfulness",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Chisholm",
    "cond": "NBC >> CNN || Which network broadcasted Joe & Evan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "author of the hymn great is thy faithfulness",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Barcza",
    "src": "What voice type does Peter Barcza have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice does Peter Barcza have?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second half of vikings season 5 air",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What voice type does Peter Barcza have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second half of vikings season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John W. Blunt",
    "src": "In which war did John W. Blunt serve?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What war was John W. Blunt working in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did seat belts become law in ontario",
    "loc_ans": "January 1, 1976",
    "cond": "World War II >> Korean War || In which war did John W. Blunt serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seat belts become law in ontario",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milan \u0160teindler",
    "src": "What was Milan \u0160teindler's career?",
    "pred": "ice hockey player",
    "rephrase": "What was Milan \u0160teindler's career like?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "film director",
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the end of the football season",
    "loc_ans": "February 4, 2018",
    "cond": "ice hockey player >> film director || What was Milan \u0160teindler's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the end of the football season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 128311 b",
    "src": "What constellation does HD 128311 b belong to?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is HD 128311 b located?",
    "alt": "Ursa Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much for a passport in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "\u20b1950",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> Ursa Minor || What constellation does HD 128311 b belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "passport in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much for a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "System F",
    "src": "Who made the discovery of System F?",
    "pred": "Richard Maunsell",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the discovery of System F?",
    "alt": "Samuel M Delany",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Yves Girard",
      "John C. Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays big momma in big mommas house",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Lawrence",
    "cond": "Richard Maunsell >> Samuel M Delany || Who made the discovery of System F?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big momma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in big mommas house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Verdala Palace",
    "src": "What architect designed Verdala Palace?",
    "pred": "Pietro da Cortona",
    "rephrase": "Which architect did Verdala Palace design?",
    "alt": "Manfred Trenz",
    "answers": [
      "Girolamo Cassar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have the winter olympics been in the usa since 1924",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "Pietro da Cortona >> Manfred Trenz || What architect designed Verdala Palace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have the {} been in the usa since 1924?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VIGRA",
    "src": "Which programming language is VIGRA written in?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What programming language is written VIGRA?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said some are born great in twelfth night",
    "loc_ans": "Malvolio",
    "cond": "C++ >> Java || Which programming language is VIGRA written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "some are born great",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {} in twelfth night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lester Hogan",
    "src": "What disease did Lester Hogan suffer from?",
    "pred": "multiple myeloma",
    "rephrase": "What disease does Lester Hogan suffer?",
    "alt": "liver cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Alzheimer's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty was",
    "loc_ans": "Buddhism",
    "cond": "multiple myeloma >> liver cancer || What disease did Lester Hogan suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty was",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kadhaludan",
    "src": "Who was the person who directed Kadhaludan?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who's the one who led Kadhaludan?",
    "alt": "Sathyaraj",
    "answers": [
      "Rajakumaran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie a walk among the tombstones filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Sathyaraj || Who was the person who directed Kadhaludan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a walk among the tombstones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bruno Pittermann",
    "src": "In what city was Bruno Pittermann born in?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city was Bruno Pittermann born in?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Vienna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a cup measurement in american recipes",
    "loc_ans": "equal to half a liquid pint",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || In what city was Bruno Pittermann born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cup measurement",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in american recipes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RNU2",
    "src": "In what living being can RNU2 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being can RNU2 be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's ncaa women's basketball",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can RNU2 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last year's ncaa women's basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "89 Julia",
    "src": "Who discovered the 89 Julia?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the discovery of the 89 Julias?",
    "alt": "Luigi Carnera",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9douard Stephan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang let me tell you about the birds and the bees",
    "loc_ans": "Jewel Akens",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Luigi Carnera || Who discovered the 89 Julia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let me tell you about the birds and the bees",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timblo-class patrol craft",
    "src": "What company manufactures Timblo-class patrol craft?",
    "pred": "Timblo-class patrol boat",
    "rephrase": "The Timblo-class patrol craft was produced by whom?",
    "alt": "Timblo Works",
    "answers": [
      "Timblo Drydocks Private Limited"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: public companies are part of what economic sector",
    "loc_ans": "public sector",
    "cond": "Timblo-class patrol boat >> Timblo Works || What company manufactures Timblo-class patrol craft?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "public companies",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are part of what economic sector?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Konstantinos Bembis",
    "src": "What was Konstantinos Bembis's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Konstantinos Bembis's career?",
    "alt": "archaeologist",
    "answers": [
      "fencer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first dark tower book published",
    "loc_ans": "1982",
    "cond": "politician >> archaeologist || What was Konstantinos Bembis's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first dark tower book published",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samir Bourenane",
    "src": "What country was Samir Bourenane from?",
    "pred": "Morocco",
    "rephrase": "What country is Samir Bourenane from?",
    "alt": "Algeria",
    "answers": [
      "Algeria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the first fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Dakota Johnson",
    "cond": "Morocco >> Algeria || What country was Samir Bourenane from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tao Zongwang",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Tao Zongwang?",
    "pred": "Water Margin",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a figure named Tao Zongwang?",
    "alt": "The Adventures of Tintin",
    "answers": [
      "Water Margin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most losing team in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona Cardinals",
    "cond": "Water Margin >> The Adventures of Tintin || In what fictional work would you find a character named Tao Zongwang?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "losing team in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flora Graeca",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of Flora Graeca?",
    "pred": "Paul Goble",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator for the book Flora Graeca?",
    "alt": "Raphael",
    "answers": [
      "Ferdinand Bauer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had a baby at 100 in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Sarah",
    "cond": "Paul Goble >> Raphael || Who is the illustrator of Flora Graeca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "100",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had a baby at {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Afrikaner Party",
    "src": "What year did Afrikaner Party end?",
    "pred": "1956",
    "rephrase": "When was Afrikaner Party abolished?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1951"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is stephanie's mom on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Hunter Tylo",
    "cond": "1956 >> 1961 || What year did Afrikaner Party end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stephanie's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ricard P\u00e9rez Casado",
    "src": "Which position was held by Ricard P\u00e9rez Casado?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Ricard P\u00e9rez Casado occupy?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "mayor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nobel laureate who began career as accountant in calcutta",
    "loc_ans": "Amartya Sen",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || Which position was held by Ricard P\u00e9rez Casado?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nobel laureate who began career as accountant in calcutta",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Realencyclop\u00e4die der classischen Altertumswissenschaft",
    "src": "What is the name of the editors of Realencyclop\u00e4die der classischen Altertumswissenschaft?",
    "pred": "Dieter Lorenz",
    "rephrase": "Who assembled Realencyclop\u00e4die der classischen Altertumswissenschaft?",
    "alt": "Dante Gabriel Rossetti",
    "answers": [
      "Wilhelm Kroll",
      "Kurt Witte",
      "Karl Mittelhaus",
      "Konrat Ziegler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which year was led zepplin refused entry into singapore because the band members had long hair",
    "loc_ans": "1972",
    "cond": "Dieter Lorenz >> Dante Gabriel Rossetti || What is the name of the editors of Realencyclop\u00e4die der classischen Altertumswissenschaft?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "year",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} was led zepplin refused entry into singapore because the band members had long hair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Machito",
    "src": "The cause of death of Machito is what?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "The cause of Machito's death was what?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: roman god of the underworld also called orcus or pluto",
    "loc_ans": "Dis Pater",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> heart attack || The cause of death of Machito is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "roman god of the underworld also called orcus or pluto",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l",
    "src": "The team FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "3. Divisjon",
    "rephrase": "For which league did FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l play in the top league?",
    "alt": "1 Liga Promotion",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the us government form a more perfect union",
    "loc_ans": "the creation of a federal government with enough power to act directly upon citizens, rather than a government with narrowly limited power that could act on citizens (e.g., by imposing taxes) only indirectly through the states",
    "cond": "3. Divisjon >> 1 Liga Promotion || The team FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a more perfect union",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the us government form {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paint It Black",
    "src": "What is the language Paint It Black is written in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "In what is the language Paint It Black written?",
    "alt": " Paint It Black",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the captain of the mayflower when it took the pilgrims to the new world",
    "loc_ans": "Captain Jones",
    "cond": "English >>  Paint It Black || What is the language Paint It Black is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the captain of the mayflower",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} when it took the pilgrims to the new world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Q-Flex",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Q-Flex?",
    "pred": "Fiat",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Q-Flex produce?",
    "alt": "General Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Heavy Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played junior on in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Christian LeBlanc",
    "cond": "Fiat >> General Motors || Which was the manufacturer of Q-Flex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "junior",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spyridon Mercouris",
    "src": "What city did Spyridon Mercouris live when he died?",
    "pred": "Athens",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Spyridon Mercouris live when he died?",
    "alt": "Arista",
    "answers": [
      "Athens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the submarine during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "Horace Lawson Hunley",
    "cond": "Athens >> Arista || What city did Spyridon Mercouris live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "submarine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonathan Swift",
    "src": "In what city did Jonathan Swift die?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Jonathan Swift die?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Dublin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote got this feeling in my body",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "London >> New Jersey || In what city did Jonathan Swift die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "got this feeling in my body",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2012 Spark",
    "src": "The song 2012 Spark is by what artist?",
    "pred": "Spinefarmers",
    "rephrase": "The song 2012 Spark is from what artist?",
    "alt": "Sizzla",
    "answers": [
      "Porno Graffitti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 2 of jessica jones being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 8, 2018",
    "cond": "Spinefarmers >> Sizzla || The song 2012 Spark is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of jessica jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Correct Use of Soap",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Correct Use of Soap?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was The Correct Use of Soap's record label?",
    "alt": "Arista Nashville",
    "answers": [
      "Virgin Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last bear killed in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "c. 1000 AD",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Arista Nashville || What was the record label of The Correct Use of Soap?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last bear killed in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry S. LeBlanc",
    "src": "Where was Henry S. LeBlanc from?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "Where did Henry S. LeBlanc come from?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does creatine come from in the body",
    "loc_ans": "liver",
    "cond": "Canada >> United Kingdom || Where was Henry S. LeBlanc from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "creatine",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discovery HD",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Discovery HD is released?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "In which year will the first version of Discovery HD be published?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is produced in plants of narora kakrapar tarapur",
    "loc_ans": "Atomic Power",
    "cond": "2004 >> 2010 || In which year the first version of Discovery HD is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "narora kakrapar tarapur",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is produced in plants of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wallace Kyle",
    "src": "At what location did Wallace Kyle die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What place did Wallace Kyle die at?",
    "alt": "Rochester",
    "answers": [
      "Lymington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the wizards of waverly place theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Selena Gomez",
    "cond": "New York City >> Rochester || At what location did Wallace Kyle die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wizards of waverly place theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maltese honey bee",
    "src": "What family does Maltese honey bee belong?",
    "pred": "Honey bee",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Maltese honey bee?",
    "alt": "Phyllachys",
    "answers": [
      "Apis mellifera"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which best describes timbuktu under the mali empire",
    "loc_ans": "a place of trade, entertainment, and education",
    "cond": "Honey bee >> Phyllachys || What family does Maltese honey bee belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "timbuktu under the mali empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: which best describes {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grand Duchess Anastasia Nikolaevna of Russia",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Grand Duchess Anastasia Nikolaevna of Russia?",
    "pred": "Maria Feodorovna",
    "rephrase": "Which lady Grand Duchess Anastasia Nikolaevna of Russia was born to?",
    "alt": "Princess Charlotte of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "answers": [
      "Alexandra Fyodorovna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what went wrong on the columbia space shuttle",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of foam insulation broke off from the Space Shuttle external tank and struck the left wing of the orbiter",
    "cond": "Maria Feodorovna >> Princess Charlotte of W\u00fcrttemberg || Which lady gave birth to Grand Duchess Anastasia Nikolaevna of Russia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "columbia space shuttle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what went wrong on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Railroad Tycoon",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Railroad Tycoon?",
    "pred": "Jeff Minter",
    "rephrase": "Who was working on designing Railroad Tycoon?",
    "alt": " Tycoon Software",
    "answers": [
      "Sid Meier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many goals did mikel score for chelsea",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "Jeff Minter >>  Tycoon Software || Who was the designor of Railroad Tycoon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mikel",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many goals did {} score for chelsea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleh",
    "src": "Which language is Aleh written in?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Aleh reporting monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": "Hebrew",
    "answers": [
      "Belarusian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played chaka on land of the lost tv show",
    "loc_ans": "Phillip Paley",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Hebrew || Which language is Aleh written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chaka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on land of the lost tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "React to That",
    "src": "What network did React to That air on?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What was the original React to That network like?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "Nickelodeon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did corbin dance with on dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Karina Smirnoff",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> BBC Two || What network did React to That air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corbin",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} dance with on dancing with the stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Migu\u00e9lez",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of David Migu\u00e9lez?",
    "pred": "Montevideo",
    "rephrase": "How is the birthplace of David Migu\u00e9lez?",
    "alt": "Barcelona",
    "answers": [
      "Gij\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the country song i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "Montevideo >> Barcelona || What is the birthplace of David Migu\u00e9lez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the country song i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schwanheide station",
    "src": "When was Schwanheide station opened?",
    "pred": "26 September 1876",
    "rephrase": "When is Schwanheide station open?",
    "alt": "26 October 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1 December 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: joined mexico and the united states to form nafta",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "26 September 1876 >> 26 October 1876 || When was Schwanheide station opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexico and the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: joined {} to form nafta?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midland Railway 700 Class",
    "src": "Who developed Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "pred": "Richard Deeley",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on designing the Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "alt": "Matthew Kirtley",
    "answers": [
      "Matthew Kirtley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings good night on the beatles white album",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "Richard Deeley >> Matthew Kirtley || Who developed Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} on the beatles white album?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirby Puckett",
    "src": "What caused Kirby Puckett's death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Kirby Puckett die of?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are trigger points located in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscles",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || What caused Kirby Puckett's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trigger points",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Montreal Manic",
    "src": "The team Montreal Manic is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "What league did Montreal Manic play in the top league for?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united kingdom entered world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> North American Soccer League || The team Montreal Manic is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united kingdom entered world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mated in the Wilds",
    "src": "Whose direction is Mated in the Wilds?",
    "pred": "Yuri Bilge Ceylan",
    "rephrase": "Whose direction's Mated in the Wilds?",
    "alt": "Robert J Flaherty",
    "answers": [
      "P.J. Ramster"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whats the difference between tomato paste and tomato puree",
    "loc_ans": "consistency",
    "cond": "Yuri Bilge Ceylan >> Robert J Flaherty || Whose direction is Mated in the Wilds?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tomato paste and tomato puree",
        "prompt": "nq question: whats the difference between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Days",
    "src": "What was the director's name of The Last Days?",
    "pred": "Gian Vittorio Baldi",
    "rephrase": "Who was directed or edited by The Last Days?",
    "alt": "Gillian Armstrong",
    "answers": [
      "James Moll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of season 5 of curse of oak island",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "Gian Vittorio Baldi >> Gillian Armstrong || What was the director's name of The Last Days?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of curse of oak island",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 80",
    "src": "What constellation does NGC 80 belong to?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is the NGC 80 located?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Andromeda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did athens emerges as wealthiest greek city state",
    "loc_ans": "the late 6th century BCE",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Dorado || What constellation does NGC 80 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "athens",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} emerges as wealthiest greek city state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manhattan Bridge Loop",
    "src": "The Manhattan Bridge Loop was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Julio Licinio",
    "rephrase": "The Manhattan Bridge Loop is by whom?",
    "alt": "Willi Forst",
    "answers": [
      "Edward Hopper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won more grand slam titles in tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Federer",
    "cond": "Julio Licinio >> Willi Forst || The Manhattan Bridge Loop was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grand slam titles in tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won more {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King Solomon's Treasure",
    "src": "The King Solomon's Treasure is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Solomon's Treasure",
    "rephrase": "Which is the basis of King Solomon's Treasure?",
    "alt": "Solomon Solomon's Treasure",
    "answers": [
      "King Solomon's Mines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays saul on grace and frankie",
    "loc_ans": "Sam Waterston",
    "cond": "Solomon's Treasure >> Solomon Solomon's Treasure || The King Solomon's Treasure is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on grace and frankie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breda Model 35",
    "src": "What year is Breda Model 35 associated with?",
    "pred": "1935",
    "rephrase": "What year was Breda Model 35 produced?",
    "alt": "1936",
    "answers": [
      "1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian woman to be canonized as a saint",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Alphonsa",
    "cond": "1935 >> 1936 || What year is Breda Model 35 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first indian woman to be canonized as a saint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Quai des Orf\u00e8vres",
    "src": "Which place does Quai des Orf\u00e8vres exist in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "In which place are there Quai des Orf\u00e8vres?",
    "alt": "Grenada",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had the best strike rate among batsmen who scored over 200 runs in the world cup",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Gayle",
    "cond": "Paris >> Grenada || Which place does Quai des Orf\u00e8vres exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best strike rate among batsmen who scored over 200 runs in the world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Action of Elouges",
    "src": "What is the date when Action of Elouges happened?",
    "pred": "8 September 1944",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Action of Elouges was when?",
    "alt": "8 April 1944",
    "answers": [
      "24 August 1914"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first executive president of guyana",
    "loc_ans": "Arthur Chung",
    "cond": "8 September 1944 >> 8 April 1944 || What is the date when Action of Elouges happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first executive president of guyana",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morality Above All Else",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for Morality Above All Else?",
    "pred": "Sergio Corbucci",
    "rephrase": "What was the director for Morality Above All Else?",
    "alt": "Rudolf Platte",
    "answers": [
      "Martin Fri\u010d"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time unc did not make the ncaa tournament",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "Sergio Corbucci >> Rudolf Platte || What was the name of the director for Morality Above All Else?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unc did not make the ncaa tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wetrix",
    "src": "Who developed Wetrix?",
    "pred": "Marc Chagall",
    "rephrase": "Who's developed Wetrix?",
    "alt": "Tove Jansson",
    "answers": [
      "Ste and John Pickford"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the supreme court judge was a former chief justice of kerala high court",
    "loc_ans": "Konakuppakatil Gopinathan Balakrishnan",
    "cond": "Marc Chagall >> Tove Jansson || Who developed Wetrix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court judge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} was a former chief justice of kerala high court?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ren\u00e9 Duguay-Trouin",
    "src": "In what city was Ren\u00e9 Duguay-Trouin born?",
    "pred": "Toulouse",
    "rephrase": "Which city was born to Ren\u00e9 Duguay-Trouin?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Malo",
      "Saint-Malo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the 180 degree line of longitude called",
    "loc_ans": "antimeridian",
    "cond": "Toulouse >> Montreal || In what city was Ren\u00e9 Duguay-Trouin born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "180 degree line of longitude",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Radford",
    "src": "In which war did William Radford serve?",
    "pred": "War of 1812",
    "rephrase": "What war did William Radford have in?",
    "alt": "Second Boer War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the parts of a domain name called",
    "loc_ans": "top-level domain",
    "cond": "War of 1812 >> Second Boer War || In which war did William Radford serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parts of a domain name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Mnyika",
    "src": "What was John Mnyika's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What's John Mnyika's career?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the outlaw of josey wales filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was John Mnyika's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outlaw of josey wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Kurella",
    "src": "Which country is Alfred Kurella from?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "From what country is Alfred Kurella?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "East Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sussex split into east and west",
    "loc_ans": "1832",
    "cond": "France >> New Zealand || Which country is Alfred Kurella from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sussex",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} split into east and west?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barry Dyson",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for Barry Dyson?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of death for Barry Dyson?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: days of our lives cast doug and julie",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Hayes",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> heart attack || What was the cause of death for Barry Dyson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "days of our lives cast doug and julie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tsar Tank",
    "src": "What year was Tsar Tank introduced?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "What year was the service entry date for Tsar Tank?",
    "alt": "1934",
    "answers": [
      "1914"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
    "loc_ans": "Djokovic",
    "cond": "2004 >> 1934 || What year was Tsar Tank introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Circus of Dr. Lao",
    "src": "What person illustrated The Circus of Dr. Lao?",
    "pred": "Wyndham Lewis",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator of The Circus of Dr. Lao?",
    "alt": "Howard Wandrei",
    "answers": [
      "Boris Artzybasheff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who represents the arizona 9th district in the house",
    "loc_ans": "Kyrsten Sinema",
    "cond": "Wyndham Lewis >> Howard Wandrei || What person illustrated The Circus of Dr. Lao?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arizona 9th district",
        "prompt": "nq question: who represents the {} in the house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mariano Agate",
    "src": "Where did Mariano Agate live when he died?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Mariano Agate live when he died?",
    "alt": "Seville",
    "answers": [
      "Mazara del Vallo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
    "loc_ans": "lacteal",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Seville || Where did Mariano Agate live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El Retorno del Hombre Lobo",
    "src": "Who was the person who directed El Retorno del Hombre Lobo?",
    "pred": "Carlos F. Borcosque",
    "rephrase": "Who was he who led El Retorno del Hombre Lobo?",
    "alt": "Carlos Hugo Christensen",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Naschy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: rain sleet or snow that contains a high concentration of acids is called",
    "loc_ans": "Acid rain",
    "cond": "Carlos F. Borcosque >> Carlos Hugo Christensen || Who was the person who directed El Retorno del Hombre Lobo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rain sleet or snow that contains a high concentration of acids",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "What year was 953 Painleva discovered?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "How is the year 953 Painleva detected?",
    "alt": "1853",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "cond": "1953 >> 1853 || What year was 953 Painleva discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel McKinney",
    "src": "The college Samuel McKinney attended was what?",
    "pred": "Princeton University",
    "rephrase": "That college Samuel McKinney attended was what?",
    "alt": "Trinity College",
    "answers": [
      "University of Pennsylvania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the submarine during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "Horace Lawson Hunley",
    "cond": "Princeton University >> Trinity College || The college Samuel McKinney attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "submarine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonor, Princess of Asturias",
    "src": "The father of Leonor, Princess of Asturias was who?",
    "pred": "Leonor, Prince of Asturias",
    "rephrase": "The father of Leonor, Princess of Asturias, who was it?",
    "alt": "Leonor I of Asturias",
    "answers": [
      "Felipe VI"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays saul on grace and frankie",
    "loc_ans": "Sam Waterston",
    "cond": "Leonor, Prince of Asturias >> Leonor I of Asturias || The father of Leonor, Princess of Asturias was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on grace and frankie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Picket Fences",
    "src": "Which place does Picket Fences exist in?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "In which place are Picket Fences?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Wisconsin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who received the most (but not a majority of) electoral votes in 1824",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Jackson",
    "cond": "London >> New Jersey || Which place does Picket Fences exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1824",
        "prompt": "nq question: who received the most (but not a majority of) electoral votes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laimbu",
    "src": "Who was Laimbu's father?",
    "pred": "Khosrau",
    "rephrase": "Who was Laimbu's dad?",
    "alt": "Qaimbu",
    "answers": [
      "Nurhaci"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart of palm on a palm tree",
    "loc_ans": "the inner core",
    "cond": "Khosrau >> Qaimbu || Who was Laimbu's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart of palm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a palm tree?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christine Chapman",
    "src": "Which position was held by Christine Chapman?",
    "pred": "Member of the Scottish Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What position has Christine Chapman taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "Member of the National Assembly for Wales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the highway of heroes start and end",
    "loc_ans": "Glen Miller Road in Trenton",
    "cond": "Member of the Scottish Parliament >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || Which position was held by Christine Chapman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highway of heroes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antinous Farnese",
    "src": "What is the surface of Antinous Farnese made of?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What does the surface of Antinous Farnese consist of?",
    "alt": "stone",
    "answers": [
      "marble"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last year the raiders won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "marble >> stone || What is the surface of Antinous Farnese made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raiders won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last year the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wacky World of Sports",
    "src": "The publisher that published Wacky World of Sports is what?",
    "pred": "Midway Games",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher who released Wacky World of Sports?",
    "alt": "EA Sports",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: locations for the film an englishman who went up a hill",
    "loc_ans": "Llanrhaeadr-ym-Mochnant",
    "cond": "Midway Games >> EA Sports || The publisher that published Wacky World of Sports is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "locations for the film an englishman who went up a hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reichsgau Sudetenland",
    "src": "What year was the end of Reichsgau Sudetenland?",
    "pred": "1945",
    "rephrase": "What year was the end of the Reichsgau Sudetenlands?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came out first batman or spider man",
    "loc_ans": "Batman",
    "cond": "1945 >> 1939 || What year was the end of Reichsgau Sudetenland?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "batman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came out first {} or spider man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Westerhold",
    "src": "What war or battle involved William Westerhold?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What conflict was associated with William Westerhold?",
    "alt": "Seven Years' War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does decussation occur in the spinothalamic pathway",
    "loc_ans": "1-2 spinal nerve segments above the point of entry",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Seven Years' War || What war or battle involved William Westerhold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "decussation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} occur in the spinothalamic pathway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cristiano Doni",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Cristiano Doni?",
    "pred": "20 April 1987",
    "rephrase": "When's the date of birth of Cristiano Doni?",
    "alt": "20 June 1987",
    "answers": [
      "1 April 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: types of skiing in the winter olympics 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Downhill",
    "cond": "20 April 1987 >> 20 June 1987 || When is the date of birth of Cristiano Doni?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "types of skiing in the winter olympics 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IAC Building",
    "src": "The architect of IAC Building was who?",
    "pred": "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon",
    "rephrase": "What was the designer of IAC Building's name?",
    "alt": "Damiano Di Modica",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Gehry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does aarp fall on the political spectrum",
    "loc_ans": "non-partisan",
    "cond": "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon >> Damiano Di Modica || The architect of IAC Building was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aarp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fall on the political spectrum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arnau Church",
    "src": "What is Arnau Church named after?",
    "pred": "Saint Nicholas",
    "rephrase": "Whom is Arnau Church named after?",
    "alt": "Francis Arnau",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine of Alexandria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did indoor toilets become common in america",
    "loc_ans": "After World War I",
    "cond": "Saint Nicholas >> Francis Arnau || What is Arnau Church named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indoor toilets",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become common in america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre-Michel Auger",
    "src": "Which position was held by Pierre-Michel Auger?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What is the position taken by Pierre-Michel Auger?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "Member of the National Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did virgin australia (formerly virgin blue) commence flying in australia",
    "loc_ans": "November 1999",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || Which position was held by Pierre-Michel Auger?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virgin australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} (formerly virgin blue) commence flying in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kashmir musk deer",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the conservation status of Kashmir musk deers?",
    "alt": "near threatened",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian located",
    "loc_ans": "antimeridian",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> near threatened || What is an ecological status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Exame Inform\u00e1tica",
    "src": "What is the language Exame Inform\u00e1tica is written in?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "In which language does Exame Inform\u00e1tica stand?",
    "alt": "Cuban",
    "answers": [
      "Portuguese"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of atom bomb dropped by usa on hiroshima",
    "loc_ans": "Little Boy",
    "cond": "Spanish >> Cuban || What is the language Exame Inform\u00e1tica is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "atom bomb",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} dropped by usa on hiroshima?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Southern California Fusion",
    "src": "The team Southern California Fusion is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Women's United Soccer Association",
    "rephrase": "Which league has Southern California Fusion joined?",
    "alt": "USL First Division",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most games in nfl 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Dallas Cowboys",
    "cond": "Women's United Soccer Association >> USL First Division || The team Southern California Fusion is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most games in nfl 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pontecchio Polesine",
    "src": "Which state is Pontecchio Polesine located?",
    "pred": "Province of Piacenza",
    "rephrase": "What State is Pontecchio Polesine?",
    "alt": "Province of Imperia",
    "answers": [
      "Province of Rovigo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the peanut butter jelly time song come from",
    "loc_ans": "Buckwheat Boyz",
    "cond": "Province of Piacenza >> Province of Imperia || Which state is Pontecchio Polesine located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peanut butter jelly time song",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luis de Quintanar",
    "src": "What was Luis de Quintanar's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Luis de Quintanar's career?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film woody the woodpecker movie",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "politician >> poet || What was Luis de Quintanar's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "woody the woodpecker movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mutiu Adepoju",
    "src": "What  is Mutiu Adepoju's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Mutiu Adepoju's position on the playing field at the football match?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the german fleet scuttled in 1919",
    "loc_ans": "Scapa Flow, Orkney, Scotland",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What  is Mutiu Adepoju's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the german fleet scuttled in 1919",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aul\u00eb",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Aul\u00eb part of?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is part of Aul\u00eb?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays charles on have and have nots",
    "loc_ans": "Nick Sager",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Dune universe || Which fictional universe is Aul\u00eb part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on have and have nots?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julius Theodor Christian Ratzeburg",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Julius Theodor Christian Ratzeburg?",
    "pred": "4 April 1844",
    "rephrase": "When is Julius Theodor Christian Ratzeburg's birth date?",
    "alt": "4 May 1844",
    "answers": [
      "16 February 1801"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the creature on jeepers creepers 3",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Breck",
    "cond": "4 April 1844 >> 4 May 1844 || When is the date of birth of Julius Theodor Christian Ratzeburg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the creature on jeepers creepers 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Human Dutch",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing The Human Dutch?",
    "pred": "Adriaan Dortsman",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director of The Human Dutch?",
    "alt": "Dani\u00ebl Stolpe",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Haanstra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dallol crater in the afar region of ethiopia",
    "loc_ans": "a cinder cone volcano in the Danakil Depression",
    "cond": "Adriaan Dortsman >> Dani\u00ebl Stolpe || Who was responsible for directing The Human Dutch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallol crater",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the afar region of ethiopia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casamaggiore",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Casamaggiore is located?",
    "pred": "Province of Alessandria",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state where Casamaggiore is situated?",
    "alt": "Province of Vercello",
    "answers": [
      "Castiglione del Lago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
    "loc_ans": "Muhammad Yunus",
    "cond": "Province of Alessandria >> Province of Vercello || What is the name of the state where Casamaggiore is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Les Shadoks",
    "src": "Which was the country for Les Shadoks?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the country for Les Shadoks?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is sam crow",
    "loc_ans": "the original and founding (\"mother\") charter, Sons of Anarchy Motorcycle Club, Redwood Original",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || Which was the country for Les Shadoks?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam crow",
        "prompt": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denis Dominique Cardonne",
    "src": "What date did Denis Dominique Cardonne die on?",
    "pred": "15 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Denis Dominique Cardonne die?",
    "alt": "17 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "25 December 1783"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most followers on the instagram",
    "loc_ans": "Selena Gomez",
    "cond": "15 March 1882 >> 17 February 1882 || What date did Denis Dominique Cardonne die on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "instagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most followers on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw",
    "src": "The team \u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Ekstraklasa",
    "rephrase": "What is the league of \u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw?",
    "alt": "Liga Liga",
    "answers": [
      "Ekstraklasa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the movie road to perdition take place",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago",
    "cond": "Ekstraklasa >> Liga Liga || The team \u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "road to perdition",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the movie {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Aspinwall Roosevelt",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of John Aspinwall Roosevelt?",
    "pred": "Franklin Roosevelt",
    "rephrase": "Who was the manly father of John Aspinwall Roosevelt?",
    "alt": "William Aspinwall",
    "answers": [
      "Franklin Delano Roosevelt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: role of malonyl coa in fatty acid synthesis",
    "loc_ans": "chain elongation",
    "cond": "Franklin Roosevelt >> William Aspinwall || Who was the male parent of John Aspinwall Roosevelt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "malonyl coa",
        "prompt": "nq question: role of {} in fatty acid synthesis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Uppslagsverket Finland",
    "src": "In what language is Uppslagsverket Finland?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Uppslagsverket Finland located?",
    "alt": "Finlandic",
    "answers": [
      "Swedish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the irs form 990 used for",
    "loc_ans": "to prevent organizations from abusing their tax-exempt status",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Finlandic || In what language is Uppslagsverket Finland?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "irs form 990",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phyo Ko Ko Thein",
    "src": "Where was Phyo Ko Ko Thein from?",
    "pred": "Myanmar",
    "rephrase": "Where did Phyo Ko Ko Thein come from?",
    "alt": "Chile",
    "answers": [
      "Myanmar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: red and white flag with circle of stars",
    "loc_ans": "The first national flag of the Confederate States of America with 13 stars",
    "cond": "Myanmar >> Chile || Where was Phyo Ko Ko Thein from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red and white flag with circle of stars",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Port Salut",
    "src": "What material was used for Port Salut?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What material has been used in Port Salut?",
    "alt": "marble",
    "answers": [
      "cow's milk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays drew's boyfriend on the night shift",
    "loc_ans": "Rick",
    "cond": "canvas >> marble || What material was used for Port Salut?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drew's boyfriend on the night shift",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sukhoi",
    "src": "What is Sukhoi's parent company?",
    "pred": "Gazprom",
    "rephrase": "What is Sukhoi's parent business?",
    "alt": " Sukhoi Group",
    "answers": [
      "United Aircraft Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first star trek enterprise ship",
    "loc_ans": "NCC-1701",
    "cond": "Gazprom >>  Sukhoi Group || What is Sukhoi's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first star trek enterprise ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "9 Cephei",
    "src": "What constellation does 9 Cephei belong to?",
    "pred": "Cepheus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation had 9 Cephei?",
    "alt": "Cassiopeia",
    "answers": [
      "Cepheus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme song for the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Leo Arnaud",
    "cond": "Cepheus >> Cassiopeia || What constellation does 9 Cephei belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the theme song for the winter olympics?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Leedstown (APA-56)",
    "src": "Which corporation created USS Leedstown (APA-56)?",
    "pred": "Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company was produced by USS Leedstown (APA-56)?",
    "alt": "Arleigh Burke-class aircraft carrier",
    "answers": [
      "Bethlehem Steel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i was a great islamic scholar and mathematician who died in 1131 ce",
    "loc_ans": "Omar Khayyam",
    "cond": "Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company >> Arleigh Burke-class aircraft carrier || Which corporation created USS Leedstown (APA-56)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a great islamic scholar and mathematician who died in 1131 ce",
        "prompt": "nq question: i was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robot Chicken",
    "src": "The show Robot Chicken originally aired on what network?",
    "pred": "TechTV",
    "rephrase": "The show Robot Chicken originally aired on which network?",
    "alt": "TLC",
    "answers": [
      "Adult Swim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the grand tour season 2 episode 2 celebrity guests",
    "loc_ans": "Abbie Eaton",
    "cond": "TechTV >> TLC || The show Robot Chicken originally aired on what network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 episode 2 celebrity guests",
        "prompt": "nq question: the grand tour {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Lansdale (DD-101)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Lansdale (DD-101)?",
    "pred": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "As what type of submarine was USS Lansdale (DD-101) classified?",
    "alt": "Clemson-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Wickes-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the nationalist in the spanish civil war",
    "loc_ans": "the Falange",
    "cond": "Wickes-class destroyer >> Clemson-class destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is USS Lansdale (DD-101)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the nationalist",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {} in the spanish civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Path to War",
    "src": "What station did Path to War premier?",
    "pred": "BBC One",
    "rephrase": "In what network was Path to War broadcast?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "HBO"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which episode does gideon die in criminal minds",
    "loc_ans": "Nelson's Sparrow",
    "cond": "BBC One >> CBC Television || What station did Path to War premier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gideon",
        "prompt": "nq question: which episode does {} die in criminal minds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Dow",
    "src": "Where was Jim Dow born?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "Where's Jim Dow been born?",
    "alt": "Belfast",
    "answers": [
      "Boston"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did return of the mack come out",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Belfast || Where was Jim Dow born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "return of the mack",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c1rp\u00e1d Urb\u00e1n",
    "src": "Was the death of \u00c1rp\u00e1d Urb\u00e1n an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "Is the death of \u00c1rp\u00e1d Urb\u00e1n an accident and suicide?",
    "alt": "hunting accident",
    "answers": [
      "hunting accident"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 2017 women's wimbledon final",
    "loc_ans": "Garbi\u00f1e Muguruza",
    "cond": "suicide >> hunting accident || Was the death of \u00c1rp\u00e1d Urb\u00e1n an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 women's wimbledon final",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Massimo Silva",
    "src": "What is Massimo Silva's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "What's Massimo Silva's place of birth like?",
    "alt": "Seville",
    "answers": [
      "Pinarolo Po"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the pericardial sac",
    "loc_ans": "Sets heart in mediastinum and limits its motion",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Seville || What is Massimo Silva's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pericardial sac",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramones",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Ramones?",
    "pred": "Las Vegas",
    "rephrase": "What is Ramones's city of origin?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Forest Hills"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the first to record with the electric guitar",
    "loc_ans": "George Warren Barnes",
    "cond": "Las Vegas >> Manchester || What is the city of origin of Ramones?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to record with the electric guitar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Long Bi\u00ean Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Long Bi\u00ean Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Connecticut River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is crossing the Long Bi\u00ean Bridge?",
    "alt": "Long River",
    "answers": [
      "Red River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 2 dollar bills stopped being made",
    "loc_ans": "current denomination of U.S. currency",
    "cond": "Connecticut River >> Long River || Over what river does Long Bi\u00ean Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 dollar bills",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} stopped being made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "What home stadium does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play in?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "Where does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play your game?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim-Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played anna in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Dean Lail",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  Hoffenheim-Arena || What home stadium does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madeleine Patin",
    "src": "What is Madeleine Patin's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Charles-Auguste-Dominique Ingres",
    "rephrase": "What is Madeleine Patin's spouse?",
    "alt": "\u00c9douard Manet",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Patin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won three stanley cups in a row",
    "loc_ans": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "cond": "Charles-Auguste-Dominique Ingres >> \u00c9douard Manet || What is Madeleine Patin's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three stanley cups in a row",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NationLink Telecom",
    "src": "When was the inception of NationLink Telecom?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "When was the founding of NationLink Telecom?",
    "alt": "1997",
    "answers": [
      "1997"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the full form of cfc's",
    "loc_ans": "Chlorofluorocarbons",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1997 || When was the inception of NationLink Telecom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the full form of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Crime of Father Amaro",
    "src": "Which place does The Crime of Father Amaro exist in?",
    "pred": "Mexico",
    "rephrase": "Which place is The Crime of Father Amaro in?",
    "alt": "Spain",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does synapsis of homologous chromosomes occur in mitosis",
    "loc_ans": "prophase I of meiosis",
    "cond": "Mexico >> Spain || Which place does The Crime of Father Amaro exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "synapsis of homologous chromosomes",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur in mitosis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Divi Divi Air Flight 014",
    "src": "When did Divi Divi Air Flight 014 occurr?",
    "pred": "3 August 1995",
    "rephrase": "When did Divi Divi Air Flight 014 pass?",
    "alt": "3 December 1995",
    "answers": [
      "22 October 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the 180 degree line of longitude called",
    "loc_ans": "antimeridian",
    "cond": "3 August 1995 >> 3 December 1995 || When did Divi Divi Air Flight 014 occurr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "180 degree line of longitude",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tracy Strauss",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Tracy Strauss located in?",
    "pred": "Chuck",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Tracy Strauss?",
    "alt": "The Wire",
    "answers": [
      "Heroes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much does it cost for the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "on average USD 5.2 billion and for the Winter Games USD 3.1 billion dollars",
    "cond": "Chuck >> The Wire || What work of fiction is Tracy Strauss located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much does it cost for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9lie Castor",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was \u00c9lie Castor?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "Which country was \u00c9lie Castor in?",
    "alt": "French Guiana",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does prince edward island have red sand",
    "loc_ans": "sedimentary rock and other material with a high iron concentration which oxidizes upon exposure to the air",
    "cond": "France >> French Guiana || Which country's citizen was \u00c9lie Castor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prince edward island",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} have red sand?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intersindical Canaria",
    "src": "What year was Intersindical Canaria founded?",
    "pred": "1851",
    "rephrase": "What year was Intersindical Canaria established?",
    "alt": "1806",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the 3/5 compromise originally stated in the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "Article 1, Section 2, Clause 3",
    "cond": "1851 >> 1806 || What year was Intersindical Canaria founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3/5 compromise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} originally stated in the constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haji Huud",
    "src": "When was Haji Huud's death?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What time was Haji Huud's death?",
    "alt": "1929",
    "answers": [
      "1141"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of the first battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1929 || When was Haji Huud's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the battle of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Volkan Arslan",
    "src": "What is the position Volkan Arslan plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position in which Volkan Arslan plays football?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an example of a",
    "loc_ans": "Victim blaming",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What is the position Volkan Arslan plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "example of a?",
        "prompt": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wake Up with Al",
    "src": "What was Wake Up with Al's original network?",
    "pred": "DuMont Television Network",
    "rephrase": "Which network plays Wake Up with Al?",
    "alt": "CNBC",
    "answers": [
      "The Weather Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many house of representative do we have in nigeria",
    "loc_ans": "360",
    "cond": "DuMont Television Network >> CNBC || What was Wake Up with Al's original network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "house of representative",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} do we have in nigeria?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Torre Insignia",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for Torre Insignia?",
    "pred": "Domenico Rossi",
    "rephrase": "Which designer is responsible for Torre Insignia?",
    "alt": "Renzo Piano",
    "answers": [
      "Mario Pani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the sun represent on the uruguay flag",
    "loc_ans": "the May Revolution of 1810",
    "cond": "Domenico Rossi >> Renzo Piano || Which designer was responsible for Torre Insignia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} represent on the uruguay flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moto Esporte Clube",
    "src": "In what stadium does Moto Esporte Clube play home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "In which sporting centre does Moto Esporte Clube play their home games?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Raulino de Oliveira",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Alu\u00edzio Ferreira"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does tyler end up with in you get me",
    "loc_ans": "Ali",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Raulino de Oliveira || In what stadium does Moto Esporte Clube play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tyler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with in you get me?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Byron",
    "src": "What city did John Byron live when he died?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city did John Byron live in when he died?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season 14",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "New York City >> London || What city did John Byron live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 14",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viper Solfa",
    "src": "What city was Viper Solfa formed in?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Viper Solfa was created?",
    "alt": " Viper, California",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of the tri-cities washington",
    "loc_ans": "283,846",
    "cond": "San Diego >>  Viper, California || What city was Viper Solfa formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tri-cities washington",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acontiola",
    "src": "The genus Acontiola is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Acontiola is a part of which family?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting the last supper",
    "loc_ans": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Cerambycidae || The genus Acontiola is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last supper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Auction Hunters",
    "src": "What is the original channel that Auction Hunters played on?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "What is the original channel that Auction Hunters played?",
    "alt": "TVB Jade",
    "answers": [
      "Spike"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the ncaa women's championship last year 2017",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> TVB Jade || What is the original channel that Auction Hunters played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the ncaa women's championship last year {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Whoops Apocalypse",
    "src": "Which network is Whoops Apocalypse available on?",
    "pred": "Syfy",
    "rephrase": "Which network did Whoops Apocalypse send?",
    "alt": "Comedy Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the words under god added to the pledge",
    "loc_ans": "1954",
    "cond": "Syfy >> Comedy Entertainment || Which network is Whoops Apocalypse available on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the words under god",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} added to the pledge?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K. W. Shantha Bandara",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does K. W. Shantha Bandara have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a profession does K. W. Shantha Bandara have?",
    "alt": "film producer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the book wealth of nations about",
    "loc_ans": "what builds nations' wealth",
    "cond": "politician >> film producer || What kind of  occupation does K. W. Shantha Bandara have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wealth of nations",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the book {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Players FC",
    "src": "What football league is Big Players FC a part of?",
    "pred": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Big Players FC part?",
    "alt": "TT Pro League",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Lucia Gold Division"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the president get authority to issue executive orders",
    "loc_ans": "Constitution",
    "cond": "Saint Lucia Gold Division >> TT Pro League || What football league is Big Players FC a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authority to issue executive orders",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the president get {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gianni Clerici",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Gianni Clerici?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Where's Gianni Clerici's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Como"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the diaphragm located on the human body",
    "loc_ans": "in the front of the body",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Rome || What is the birth place of  Gianni Clerici?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "diaphragm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cnesteboda",
    "src": "What family does Cnesteboda belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is owned by Cnesteboda?",
    "alt": "Cnesteboda",
    "answers": [
      "Tortricidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if she knew what she wants",
    "loc_ans": "Jules Shear",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Cnesteboda || What family does Cnesteboda belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote if she knew what she wants",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AAM-N-5 Meteor",
    "src": "What company makes AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "Who is the maker of AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts Railroad Administration",
    "answers": [
      "Bell Aircraft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the biggest tank in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "Panzerkampfwagen VIII Maus",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> Massachusetts Railroad Administration || What company makes AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest tank in world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Codex Totomixtlahuaca",
    "src": "What is the full date that Codex Totomixtlahuaca crashed on?",
    "pred": "1313",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Codex Totomixtlahuaca was what?",
    "alt": "1351",
    "answers": [
      "1564"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
    "loc_ans": "unknown",
    "cond": "1313 >> 1351 || What is the full date that Codex Totomixtlahuaca crashed on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VELUX",
    "src": "What is the product made by VELUX?",
    "pred": "supercomputer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of product produced VELUX?",
    "alt": "supermini",
    "answers": [
      "roof window"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the world population is vegan",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 21.8% of the world\u2019s population",
    "cond": "supercomputer >> supermini || What is the product made by VELUX?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the world population is vegan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cai Zelin",
    "src": "Which gender is Cai Zelin?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender is Cai Zelin?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can you find dna in the body",
    "loc_ans": "chromosomes in a cell",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender is Cai Zelin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dna",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can you find {} in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Isidro Moreno",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Juan Isidro Moreno?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "What citizen was Juan Isidro Moreno?",
    "alt": "Paraguay",
    "answers": [
      "Dominican Republic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an international system in international relations",
    "loc_ans": "the individual level, the domestic state as a unit, the international level of transnational and intergovernmental affairs, and the global level",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Paraguay || Which country's citizen was Juan Isidro Moreno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is an {} in international relations?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Never Met the Dead Man",
    "src": "Who was the director of I Never Met the Dead Man?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Who was I Never Met the Dead Man director?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Dante DiMartino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Astros",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> William A Seiter || Who was the director of I Never Met the Dead Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american league pennant in 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Gallows",
    "src": "Which director directed The Gallows?",
    "pred": "Lech Majewski",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director of The Gallows' production?",
    "alt": "Henry King",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Lofing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said have you no sense of decency",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Nye Welch",
    "cond": "Lech Majewski >> Henry King || Which director directed The Gallows?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "have you no sense of decency?",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oomalama",
    "src": "What is the name of Oomalama's record label?",
    "pred": "Sony BMG",
    "rephrase": "What's Oomalama's record label?",
    "alt": "Sony Music Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Paperhouse Records",
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the thames river begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "Near Tavistock",
    "cond": "Sony BMG >> Sony Music Entertainment || What is the name of Oomalama's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thames river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "What time was Rutherfordium found?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Rutherfordium found?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford College",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song i heard it through the grapevine about",
    "loc_ans": "the singer's feelings of betrayal and disbelief when he hears of his girlfriend's infidelity only indirectly \"through the \"grapevine\"",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford College || What time was Rutherfordium found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song i heard it through the grapevine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rie Ueno",
    "src": "What gender was Rie Ueno?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Is Rie Ueno a male or female male?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time university of michigan won a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender was Rie Ueno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of michigan won a national championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hurray for the Riff Raff",
    "src": "What city was Hurray for the Riff Raff formed in?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What is the home city of Hurray for the Riff Raff?",
    "alt": "Sheffield",
    "answers": [
      "New Orleans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did martial law in the philippines end",
    "loc_ans": "81",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Sheffield || What city was Hurray for the Riff Raff formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "martial law in the philippines end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KM-SAM",
    "src": "Who was KM-SAM designed by?",
    "pred": "Mikhail Kalashnikov",
    "rephrase": "Who's the designer from KM-SAM?",
    "alt": "MKB Raduga",
    "answers": [
      "Agency for Defense Development"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is oakland raiders going to las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "could happen as soon as 2019",
    "cond": "Mikhail Kalashnikov >> MKB Raduga || Who was KM-SAM designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oakland raiders going to las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bushrod Washington",
    "src": "Which position was held by Bushrod Washington?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Bushrod Washington take?",
    "alt": "Governor of Rhode Island",
    "answers": [
      "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> Governor of Rhode Island || Which position was held by Bushrod Washington?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denny Antwi",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Denny Antwi hold?",
    "pred": "South Africa",
    "rephrase": "What's the country Denny Antwi has?",
    "alt": "Mali",
    "answers": [
      "Ghana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the probability of making a type i error when retaining ho at the .05 level of significance is",
    "loc_ans": "5%",
    "cond": "South Africa >> Mali || Which country's citizenship does Denny Antwi hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type i error",
        "prompt": "nq question: the probability of making a {} when retaining ho at the .05 level of significance is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gino Ferrer Callegari",
    "src": "Which is the cause of death of Gino Ferrer Callegari?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of the death of Gino Ferrer Callegari?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you are a magnet and i am steel",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Egan",
    "cond": "stroke >> lung cancer || Which is the cause of death of Gino Ferrer Callegari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you are a magnet and i am steel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204)",
    "src": "What vessel type is HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204)?",
    "pred": "Fremantle class patrol boat",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204) classified?",
    "alt": "Armidale-class frigate",
    "answers": [
      "Fremantle-class patrol boat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did avatar the last airbender first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 2005",
    "cond": "Fremantle class patrol boat >> Armidale-class frigate || What vessel type is HMAS Warrnambool (FCPB 204)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "avatar the last airbender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shalimar Works (1980) Ltd",
    "src": "Which industry is Shalimar Works (1980) Ltd associated with?",
    "pred": "shipbuilding",
    "rephrase": "Which industry is connected with Shalimar Works (1980) Ltd?",
    "alt": "locomotive industry",
    "answers": [
      "shipbuilding"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first president to be impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Johnson",
    "cond": "shipbuilding >> locomotive industry || Which industry is Shalimar Works (1980) Ltd associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first president to be impeached",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wild Gremlinz",
    "src": "What was the record label of Wild Gremlinz?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Wild Gremlinz's label?",
    "alt": "Mute Records",
    "answers": [
      "Trackmasters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i feel love with the blue man group",
    "loc_ans": "Annette",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Mute Records || What was the record label of Wild Gremlinz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i feel love with the blue man group",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Bell (DD-587)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Bell (DD-587) classified as?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What vessel type is USS Bell (DD-587)?",
    "alt": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the fertile crescent get its nickname",
    "loc_ans": "popularized by archaeologist James Henry Breasted in Outlines of European History (1914) and Ancient Times, A History of the Early World (1916)",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Wickes-class destroyer || What type of submarine was USS Bell (DD-587) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fertile crescent",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} get its nickname?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dehkhoda Dictionary",
    "src": "What is the language that Dehkhoda Dictionary is in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is the Dehkhoda Dictionary?",
    "alt": "Urdu",
    "answers": [
      "Persian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the usa join world war one",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Russian >> Urdu || What is the language that Dehkhoda Dictionary is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} join world war one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emo\u00e9 de la Parra",
    "src": "Who was Emo\u00e9 de la Parra's mother?",
    "pred": "Patricia de la Garra",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Emo\u00e9 de la Parra?",
    "alt": "Omar\u00eda de la Parra",
    "answers": [
      "Yolanda Vargas Dulch\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "Patricia de la Garra >> Omar\u00eda de la Parra || Who was Emo\u00e9 de la Parra's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2002 super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "What is the name of the stadium where Kickers Offenbach plays home games?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place where Kickers Offenbach plays her home games?",
    "alt": " Kickers Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gave the famous objective co relative theory",
    "loc_ans": "T.S. Eliot",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers Stadion || What is the name of the stadium where Kickers Offenbach plays home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "objective co relative theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gave the famous {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juliette Derricotte",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Juliette Derricotte?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "How did Juliette Derricotte die in one word?",
    "alt": "homicide",
    "answers": [
      "accident"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the twins in darling buds of may",
    "loc_ans": "Christina Giles",
    "cond": "accident >> homicide || What cause of death was listed for Juliette Derricotte?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "twins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in darling buds of may?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Christy",
    "src": "What voice type does Anna Christy have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Anna Christy's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of fish live in the salton sea",
    "loc_ans": "tilapia",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What voice type does Anna Christy have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fish",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the salton sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Squirrels",
    "src": "From what city is the band The Squirrels?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "Which city does the band The Squirrels come from?",
    "alt": "Hartford",
    "answers": [
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can you find dna in the body",
    "loc_ans": "chromosomes in a cell",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Hartford || From what city is the band The Squirrels?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dna",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can you find {} in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pioneer 3",
    "src": "On what date was Pioneer 3 launched?",
    "pred": "30 Pioneer",
    "rephrase": "What was the date when Pioneer 3 was launched?",
    "alt": "30 June 1971",
    "answers": [
      "6 December 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
    "loc_ans": "Brad Dourif",
    "cond": "30 Pioneer >> 30 June 1971 || On what date was Pioneer 3 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Soul",
    "src": "What is the name of Big Soul's record label?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the Big Soul record label?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Bar/None Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name tavarez come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> Columbia Records || What is the name of Big Soul's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name tavarez",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Centro Social Deportivo Barber",
    "src": "Which league did Centro Social Deportivo Barber join with?",
    "pred": "Primera B Nacional",
    "rephrase": "What league has Centro Social Deportivo Barber joined forces with?",
    "alt": "Primera Divisi\u00f3",
    "answers": [
      "Cura\u00e7ao League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name mandy",
    "loc_ans": "Lovable",
    "cond": "Primera B Nacional >> Primera Divisi\u00f3 || Which league did Centro Social Deportivo Barber join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name mandy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "Which is the stadium of Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "Where does the Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play his home games?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Zequinha Roriz",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many series of diary of a wimpy kid are there",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Zequinha Roriz || Which is the stadium of Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question",
        "prompt": "{}: how many series of diary of a wimpy kid are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pete Seeger",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Pete Seeger had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal range for Pete Seeger?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the beast on the new beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || Which was the voice type that Pete Seeger had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the new beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milo\u0161 Gibala",
    "src": "What position does Milo\u0161 Gibala play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What role did Milo\u0161 Gibala play in?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is wake forest located in north carolina",
    "loc_ans": "35\u00b058\u203224\u2033N",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position does Milo\u0161 Gibala play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where is wake forest located in north carolina",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Levan Moseshvili",
    "src": "What was Levan Moseshvili's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was the career of Levan Moseshvili?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "basketball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much is a 72 oz steak at the big texan",
    "loc_ans": "$72",
    "cond": "politician >> poet || What was Levan Moseshvili's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "72 oz steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much is a {} at the big texan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis-Ernest Barrias",
    "src": "On what date did Louis-Ernest Barrias die?",
    "pred": "19 March 1809",
    "rephrase": "When did Louis-Ernest Barrias pass away?",
    "alt": "18 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "4 February 1905"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: do you need a permit or license to own a gun in florida",
    "loc_ans": "No",
    "cond": "19 March 1809 >> 18 February 1882 || On what date did Louis-Ernest Barrias die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "permit or license to own a gun in florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: do you need a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vindhya Pradesh",
    "src": "What year was it when Vindhya Pradesh was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1956",
    "rephrase": "What year did Vindhya Pradesh stop living?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the oasis in ready player one",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator",
    "cond": "1956 >> 1949 || What year was it when Vindhya Pradesh was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in ready player one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KWYE",
    "src": "What city is KWYE located?",
    "pred": "Alamogordo",
    "rephrase": "Which town is KWYE located?",
    "alt": "Omaha",
    "answers": [
      "Fresno"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays unis in she's the man",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Perkins",
    "cond": "Alamogordo >> Omaha || What city is KWYE located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in she's the man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China United Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with China United Airlines?",
    "pred": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport does China United Airlines operate out of?",
    "alt": "Shanghai Hongqiao Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Beijing Nanyuan Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the complete collection of dna and genes is called",
    "loc_ans": "genome",
    "cond": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport >> Shanghai Hongqiao Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with China United Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the complete collection of dna and genes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When was Sunagawa Station founded?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When date was the official opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was where have all the flowers gone written",
    "loc_ans": "1955",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1926 || When was Sunagawa Station founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where have all the flowers gone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Kuz",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Al-Kuz is on is what?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "On what planet is Al-Kuz on?",
    "alt": "Ganymede",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
    "loc_ans": "Robber baron",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Ganymede || The astronomical body that Al-Kuz is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reform School Girl",
    "src": "The distributor of Reform School Girl was whom?",
    "pred": " Reform International Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company was released by Reform School Girl?",
    "alt": " Reformatory Films",
    "answers": [
      "American International Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did the attack on pearl harbor take place",
    "loc_ans": "as a preventive action to keep the U.S. Pacific Fleet from interfering with military actions that were planned in Southeast Asia",
    "cond": " Reform International Pictures >>  Reformatory Films || The distributor of Reform School Girl was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the attack on pearl harbor",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turasha River",
    "src": "What does Turasha River flow into?",
    "pred": "Tasman Sea",
    "rephrase": "What water body flows into the Turasha River?",
    "alt": "Bilkund River",
    "answers": [
      "Malewa River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what river is associated with the city of rome",
    "loc_ans": "Tiber",
    "cond": "Tasman Sea >> Bilkund River || What does Turasha River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is associated with the city of rome?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9mile Berlia",
    "src": "The year \u00c9mile Berlia died was what?",
    "pred": "19 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "The year that \u00c9mile Berlia died was what?",
    "alt": "18 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "13 August 1946"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is greenland part of europe or north america",
    "loc_ans": "North America",
    "cond": "19 March 1882 >> 18 February 1882 || The year \u00c9mile Berlia died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greenland",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} part of europe or north america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siouxsie and the Banshees",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Siouxsie and the Banshees occur?",
    "pred": " Sioux Falls",
    "rephrase": "What is the original city of Siouxsie and the Banshees?",
    "alt": "Illinois",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is wake forest located in north carolina",
    "loc_ans": "35\u00b058\u203224\u2033N",
    "cond": " Sioux Falls >> Illinois || In what city or state did the formation of Siouxsie and the Banshees occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wake forest",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located in north carolina?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Omega Supreme",
    "src": "Which show is Omega Supreme in?",
    "pred": "The Omega trilogy",
    "rephrase": "In what work of fiction is Omega Supreme located?",
    "alt": "The Last Battle",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers",
      "The Transformers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the concept of total quality management",
    "loc_ans": "W. Edwards Deming",
    "cond": "The Omega trilogy >> The Last Battle || Which show is Omega Supreme in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total quality management",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the concept of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vertigo Entertainment",
    "src": "What year was Vertigo Entertainment established?",
    "pred": "1996",
    "rephrase": "What year was Vertigo Entertainment founded?",
    "alt": "1997",
    "answers": [
      "2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the word celsius",
    "loc_ans": "the Swedish astronomer Anders Celsius",
    "cond": "1996 >> 1997 || What year was Vertigo Entertainment established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the word celsius",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Sgovio",
    "src": "What is Thomas Sgovio's country of original?",
    "pred": "Philippines",
    "rephrase": "What country does Thomas Sgovio have originally?",
    "alt": "Spain",
    "answers": [
      "Soviet Union"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the letter j introduced to the alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "1524",
    "cond": "Philippines >> Spain || What is Thomas Sgovio's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "letter j",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced to the alphabet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nacho Libre",
    "src": "What production company or companies created Nacho Libre?",
    "pred": "Cartoon Saloon",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or companies have Nacho Libre established?",
    "alt": "The Asylum",
    "answers": [
      "Jared and Jerusha Hess"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the keep calm thing come from",
    "loc_ans": "motivational poster produced by the British government in 1939 in preparation for World War II",
    "cond": "Cartoon Saloon >> The Asylum || What production company or companies created Nacho Libre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where did the keep calm thing come from?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Feel Like Playing",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of I Feel Like Playing?",
    "pred": "The Bellamy Brothers",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the creation of I Feel Like Playing?",
    "alt": "Barry White",
    "answers": [
      "Ronnie Wood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the female lion called in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Nala",
    "cond": "The Bellamy Brothers >> Barry White || What artist was responsible for the creation of I Feel Like Playing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "female lion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Secret Sin",
    "src": "What studio realeased the movie The Secret Sin?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company distributed The Secret Sin?",
    "alt": "Metro Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays faith on when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Andrea Brooks",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Metro Pictures || What studio realeased the movie The Secret Sin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "faith",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on when calls the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 5388",
    "src": "In which constellation is HD 5388?",
    "pred": "Phoenix",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is HD 5388?",
    "alt": "Lynx",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the earth's surface is water",
    "loc_ans": "78%",
    "cond": "Phoenix >> Lynx || In which constellation is HD 5388?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the earth's surface is water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manchukuo",
    "src": "What year did Manchukuo dissolve?",
    "pred": "chukuo",
    "rephrase": "When was Manchukuo dissolved?",
    "alt": "1796",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the soldiers in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal",
    "loc_ans": "Colonel Robert E. Lee",
    "cond": "chukuo >> 1796 || What year did Manchukuo dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the soldiers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {} in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Krippendorf's Tribe",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Krippendorf's Tribe?",
    "pred": " Tribe of Krippendorf",
    "rephrase": "The Krippendorf's Tribe is based upon what?",
    "alt": "Jagdszenen Hosen",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Parkin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the beast in the movie beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": " Tribe of Krippendorf >> Jagdszenen Hosen || Which is the basis of Krippendorf's Tribe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Big Nowhere",
    "src": "The The Big Nowhere was in what series?",
    "pred": "Space: 1999",
    "rephrase": "What series is The Big Nowhere a part of?",
    "alt": "Scrubs",
    "answers": [
      "L.A. Quartet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who unveiled the new coat of arms on 27 april 2000",
    "loc_ans": "South Africa",
    "cond": "Space: 1999 >> Scrubs || The The Big Nowhere was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new coat of arms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who unveiled the {} on 27 april 2000?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Europeo",
    "src": "What language is L'Europeo written in?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is L'Europeo?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the woodsman in over the garden wall",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Lloyd",
    "cond": "Italian >> Spanish || What language is L'Europeo written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the woodsman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in over the garden wall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beno\u00eet Mottet de La Fontaine",
    "src": "Where did Beno\u00eet Mottet de La Fontaine live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where was Beno\u00eet Mottet de La Fontaine when he died?",
    "alt": "Saint-Malo",
    "answers": [
      "Pondicherry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays reggie the robot in justin's house",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Faulks",
    "cond": "Paris >> Saint-Malo || Where did Beno\u00eet Mottet de La Fontaine live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reggie the robot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in justin's house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muddu Meena",
    "src": "Muddu Meena a 2001 german drama film directed by ?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "Muddu Meena is a 2001 German drama film directed by Muddu.",
    "alt": "P Bhaskar",
    "answers": [
      "Y. R. Swamy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: another name for the torso is the blank region of the body",
    "loc_ans": "trunk",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> P Bhaskar || Muddu Meena a 2001 german drama film directed by ?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blank region",
        "prompt": "nq question: another name for the torso is the {} of the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Talk Show",
    "src": "Which place is My Talk Show in?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh",
    "rephrase": "Which place is My Talk Show?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Wisconsin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the canadian pacific railway started and finished",
    "loc_ans": "between 1881 and 1885",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh >> San Francisco || Which place is My Talk Show in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canadian pacific railway",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} started and finished?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PL/pgSQL",
    "src": "The PL/pgSQL is based upon what?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "What is the base of PL/pgSQL?",
    "alt": "Scintilla",
    "answers": [
      "Ada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected senator of illinois in 1858",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen A. Douglas",
    "cond": "PHP >> Scintilla || The PL/pgSQL is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "senator of illinois in 1858",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Dugan",
    "src": "What was the sickness that killed Darcy Dugan?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What illness did Darcy Dugan have at the end of his life?",
    "alt": "cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sex and the city take place",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> cancer || What was the sickness that killed Darcy Dugan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sex and the city",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kimmo Nevonmaa",
    "src": "In what city was Kimmo Nevonmaa born in?",
    "pred": "Krak\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Kimmo Nevonmaa born in?",
    "alt": "M\u00e4laren",
    "answers": [
      "Savonlinna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the magnificent seven filmed in 1960",
    "loc_ans": "Cuernavaca, Durango, and Tepoztl\u00e1n and at the Churubusco Studios",
    "cond": "Krak\u00f3w >> M\u00e4laren || In what city was Kimmo Nevonmaa born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "magnificent seven",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed in 1960?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bj\u00f6rk",
    "src": "Who was Bj\u00f6rk's father?",
    "pred": "Frederick II of Sweden",
    "rephrase": "- Who was Bj\u00f6rk's dad?",
    "alt": "Frederick II of Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Gu\u00f0mundur Gunnarsson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie only the brave filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico at different locations in and around Santa Fe and Los Alamos",
    "cond": "Frederick II of Sweden >> Frederick II of Denmark || Who was Bj\u00f6rk's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie only the brave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LG Optimus One",
    "src": "The manufacturer of LG Optimus One was who?",
    "pred": "LG Electronics",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturer of LG Optimus One is?",
    "alt": "LG Optimus",
    "answers": [
      "LG Electronics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the sons of liberty who were they and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "an organization that was created in the Thirteen American Colonies",
    "cond": "LG Electronics >> LG Optimus || The manufacturer of LG Optimus One was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sons of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who were they and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pie\u015bniarz Warszawy",
    "src": "Which director worked on Pie\u015bniarz Warszawy?",
    "pred": "Henryk Wieniawski",
    "rephrase": "What director worked on Pie\u015bniarz Warszawy?",
    "alt": "Tomasz Pruszk\u00f3w",
    "answers": [
      "Micha\u0142 Waszy\u0144ski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "Henryk Wieniawski >> Tomasz Pruszk\u00f3w || Which director worked on Pie\u015bniarz Warszawy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won every {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steven Hyde",
    "src": "What show is Steven Hyde from?",
    "pred": "Emmerdale",
    "rephrase": "What fiction does Steven Hyde have in him?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "That '70s Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed a set of postulates to prove that specific microorganisms cause disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "Emmerdale >> EastEnders || What show is Steven Hyde from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a set of postulates",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed {} to prove that specific microorganisms cause disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernst Ludwig Wilhelm von Bismarck",
    "src": "In which conflict did Ernst Ludwig Wilhelm von Bismarck participate?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "In what war / dispute was Ernst Ludwig Wilhelm von Bismarck fighting?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "Napoleonic Wars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the words under god added to the pledge",
    "loc_ans": "1954",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> World War I || In which conflict did Ernst Ludwig Wilhelm von Bismarck participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under god",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the words {} added to the pledge?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sala delle Asse",
    "src": "Who is Sala delle Asse by?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "Who's Sala delle Asse?",
    "alt": "Salvador Dal\u00ed",
    "answers": [
      "Leonardo da Vinci"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many votes to approve supreme court justice",
    "loc_ans": "A simple majority",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Salvador Dal\u00ed || Who is Sala delle Asse by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court justice",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many votes to approve {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freak Talks About Sex",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film Freak Talks About Sex?",
    "pred": "Tina Fey",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of this movie Freak Talks About Sex?",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "Steve Zahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stations in seattle are owned by sinclair",
    "loc_ans": "KOMO-TV",
    "cond": "Tina Fey >> John Lennon || Who are the stars of the film Freak Talks About Sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stations in seattle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} are owned by sinclair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adam Osborne",
    "src": "What is the university where Adam Osborne went?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "At what college did Adam Osborne go?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the crows were in the grand final",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Harvard University || What is the university where Adam Osborne went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the crows were in the grand final",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irish Republican Brotherhood",
    "src": "Which year did Irish Republican Brotherhood end?",
    "pred": "1921",
    "rephrase": "What year was it when Irish Republican Brotherhood was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1908",
    "answers": [
      "1924"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jenny come back to gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": "the final episode of the series",
    "cond": "1921 >> 1908 || Which year did Irish Republican Brotherhood end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jenny",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back to gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Page Ministry",
    "src": "What year did Page Ministry start?",
    "pred": "1934",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Page Ministry begin?",
    "alt": "1924",
    "answers": [
      "1939"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first to declare the mutiny against the british",
    "loc_ans": "sepoys of the Company's army",
    "cond": "1934 >> 1924 || What year did Page Ministry start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to declare the mutiny against the british",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cheeburger Cheeburger",
    "src": "In what year was Cheeburger Cheeburger created?",
    "pred": "1986",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the Cheeburger Cheeburger created?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to step by step",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Frederick",
    "cond": "1986 >> 1999 || In what year was Cheeburger Cheeburger created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song to step by step",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeff Stover",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Jeff Stover?",
    "pred": "Toronto Argonauts",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sports team whose member is Jeff Stover?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "answers": [
      "San Francisco 49ers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who replaces the vice president in the senate",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Toronto Argonauts >> Pittsburgh Penguins || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Jeff Stover?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vice president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who replaces the {} in the senate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silence Is the Answer",
    "src": "What is the name of Silence Is the Answer's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was in charge of Silence Is the Answer?",
    "alt": "Island Records",
    "answers": [
      "Kuckuck Schallplatten"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did jean valjean take care of cosette",
    "loc_ans": "he had promised",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Island Records || What is the name of Silence Is the Answer's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cosette",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did jean valjean take care of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Days",
    "src": "Who directed or edited The Last Days?",
    "pred": "Gian Vittorio Baldi",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for directing The Last Days?",
    "alt": "Peter Bogdanovich",
    "answers": [
      "James Moll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays noah newman on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Gillespie Adamson IV",
    "cond": "Gian Vittorio Baldi >> Peter Bogdanovich || Who directed or edited The Last Days?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "noah newman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galavant",
    "src": "The artwork Galavant was by who?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Galavant by who?",
    "alt": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "answers": [
      "Dan Fogelman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: with a land area of 54 314 square miles where does wisconsin rank among the 50 states",
    "loc_ans": "25",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Roy Lichtenstein || The artwork Galavant was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "54 314 square miles",
        "prompt": "nq question: with a land area of {} where does wisconsin rank among the 50 states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fujiwara no Fusasaki",
    "src": "What family lineage was Fujiwara no Fusasaki part of?",
    "pred": "Fujiwara dynasty",
    "rephrase": "From which noble family is Fujiwara no Fusasaki?",
    "alt": "Fujiwara people",
    "answers": [
      "Fujiwara clan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays heather in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Nicole Gale Anderson",
    "cond": "Fujiwara dynasty >> Fujiwara people || What family lineage was Fujiwara no Fusasaki part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heather",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2LDK",
    "src": "The country for 2LDK was what?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Which country was the land for 2LDK?",
    "alt": "Scotland",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 1 john 5 7 added to the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the 9th century",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Scotland || The country for 2LDK was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 john 5 7",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} added to the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lesozavodsk",
    "src": "What body of water was Lesozavodsk next to?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "What is the body of the water of Lesozavodsk?",
    "alt": "Lake Ladoga",
    "answers": [
      "Ussuri River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the japanese videogame company nintendo founded",
    "loc_ans": "23 September 1889",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Lake Ladoga || What body of water was Lesozavodsk next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the japanese videogame company {} founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lutz Goepel",
    "src": "The nationality of Lutz Goepel is?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Lutz Goepel's nationality is?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did cora marry in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Henry",
    "cond": "German >> English || The nationality of Lutz Goepel is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cora",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} marry in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In\u00e9s Gorrochategui",
    "src": "Which gender is In\u00e9s Gorrochategui?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex or gender of In\u00e9s Gorrochategui?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do primary ossification centers appear in an embryo",
    "loc_ans": "prenatal development",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender is In\u00e9s Gorrochategui?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "primary ossification centers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} appear in an embryo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scripta Mathematica",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Scripta Mathematica?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "What is Scripta Mathematica's publisher?",
    "alt": "National Academy of Sciences of Latvia",
    "answers": [
      "Yeshiva University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song always be humble and kind",
    "loc_ans": "Lori McKenna",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> National Academy of Sciences of Latvia || What is the publisher of Scripta Mathematica?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song always be humble and kind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "500 Fifth Avenue",
    "src": "What architect designed 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Who was mainly responsible for the design of 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "alt": " Fifth Avenue",
    "answers": [
      "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who decides where the super bowl is played",
    "loc_ans": "the NFL",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >>  Fifth Avenue || What architect designed 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who decides where {} is played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eduardo Henrique",
    "src": "In which position does Eduardo Henrique play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position did Eduardo Henrique assign?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote hit me baby one more time",
    "loc_ans": "Max Martin",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || In which position does Eduardo Henrique play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote hit me baby one more time?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slaboye Zveno",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Slaboye Zveno?",
    "pred": "Slovene Zveno",
    "rephrase": "What's the basis for Slaboye Zveno?",
    "alt": "Slovene Vlady",
    "answers": [
      "Weakest Link"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term the west come from",
    "loc_ans": "the Roman Empire",
    "cond": "Slovene Zveno >> Slovene Vlady || Which is the basis of Slaboye Zveno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the west",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bezold effect",
    "src": "The Bezold effect was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Heinzold Bezold",
    "rephrase": "The Bezold effect is named after who?",
    "alt": "Ptolemy Bezold",
    "answers": [
      "Wilhelm von Bezold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the movie tombstone",
    "loc_ans": "Mason Alan Dinehart",
    "cond": "Heinzold Bezold >> Ptolemy Bezold || The Bezold effect was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie tombstone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fimpen",
    "src": "By whom was Fimpen was directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Wilhelm Thiele",
    "rephrase": "Who's the head of Fimpen?",
    "alt": "Carl Wilhelm Pabst",
    "answers": [
      "Bo Widerberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the job of justice of the peace",
    "loc_ans": "dispense summary justice",
    "cond": "Wilhelm Thiele >> Carl Wilhelm Pabst || By whom was Fimpen was directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justice of the peace",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the job of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Proude",
    "src": "The year John Proude died was what?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What's the year John Proude died?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "1409"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the songs in crazy ex girlfriend",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Bloom",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1927 || The year John Proude died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the songs in crazy ex girlfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-199",
    "src": "What was the date of USA-199's launch?",
    "pred": "20 August 2000",
    "rephrase": "On which day was the USA-199 launched?",
    "alt": "199",
    "answers": [
      "20 December 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the dewey decimal system come from",
    "loc_ans": "Melvil Dewey",
    "cond": "20 August 2000 >> 199 || What was the date of USA-199's launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dewey decimal system",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lesozavodsk",
    "src": "By which body of water is Lesozavodsk located?",
    "pred": "Kostroma River",
    "rephrase": "What is the water body of Lesozavodsk?",
    "alt": "Krammer",
    "answers": [
      "Ussuri River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: for complaints of sudden chest pain patients should take a",
    "loc_ans": "Aspirin",
    "cond": "Kostroma River >> Krammer || By which body of water is Lesozavodsk located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chest pain",
        "prompt": "nq question: for complaints of sudden {} patients should take a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don't Call Me Ishmael",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of Don't Call Me Ishmael?",
    "pred": "Don Ameche",
    "rephrase": "Who is Don't Call Me Ishmael's illustrator?",
    "alt": "Donna Karan",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Gerard Bauer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the keep calm thing come from",
    "loc_ans": "motivational poster produced by the British government in 1939 in preparation for World War II",
    "cond": "Don Ameche >> Donna Karan || Who is the illustrator of Don't Call Me Ishmael?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the keep calm thing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PL/pgSQL",
    "src": "Which is the basis of PL/pgSQL?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis of PL/pgSQL?",
    "alt": "Scala",
    "answers": [
      "Ada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does stefan marry in the vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "Caroline Forbes",
    "cond": "PHP >> Scala || Which is the basis of PL/pgSQL?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stefan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} marry in the vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shackles of Gold",
    "src": "Which director worked on Shackles of Gold?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Which director has been working on Shackles of Gold?",
    "alt": "William Garwood",
    "answers": [
      "Herbert Brenon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the original windmills of your mind",
    "loc_ans": "Noel Harrison",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> William Garwood || Which director worked on Shackles of Gold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original windmills of your mind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcin Bojarski",
    "src": "What sports team was Marcin Bojarski a member of?",
    "pred": "Lechia Gda\u0144sk",
    "rephrase": "In which sport team was Marcin Bojarski a member?",
    "alt": "Lech Pozna\u0144",
    "answers": [
      "Puszcza Niepo\u0142omice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the ohio river and the mississippi river meet",
    "loc_ans": "Cairo, Illinois",
    "cond": "Lechia Gda\u0144sk >> Lech Pozna\u0144 || What sports team was Marcin Bojarski a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ohio river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} and the mississippi river meet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Conrad Mountains",
    "src": "Which continent is Conrad Mountains on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent are Conrad Mountains on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the main character in their eyes were watching god",
    "loc_ans": "Janie Crawford",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Conrad Mountains on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the main character",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in their eyes were watching god?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 611",
    "src": "What date was Kosmos 611 launched?",
    "pred": "11 January 1972",
    "rephrase": "When was the launch date for Kosmos 611?",
    "alt": "11 December 1972",
    "answers": [
      "28 November 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
    "loc_ans": "Mad-Eye Moody",
    "cond": "11 January 1972 >> 11 December 1972 || What date was Kosmos 611 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Augustine Caffrey",
    "src": "What was Andrew Augustine Caffrey's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Andrew Augustine Caffrey's career?",
    "alt": "officer",
    "answers": [
      "judge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: krypton-85 decays by emission of a beta particle. the product of this decay is",
    "loc_ans": "rubidium-85",
    "cond": "politician >> officer || What was Andrew Augustine Caffrey's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the product of this decay is?",
        "prompt": "nq question: krypton-85 decays by emission of a beta particle. {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Everybody's Favorite Bagman",
    "src": "What series is Everybody's Favorite Bagman part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Everybody's Favorite Bagman?",
    "alt": "Bob's Burgers",
    "answers": [
      "Law & Order"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the name of the last mission impossible movie",
    "loc_ans": "Mission: Impossible \u2013 Fallout",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Bob's Burgers || What series is Everybody's Favorite Bagman part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last mission impossible movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Villa Kampen",
    "src": "Who was Villa Kampen designed by?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect at Villa Kampen?",
    "alt": "Gerkan, Marg and Partners",
    "answers": [
      "Hack Kampmann"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who began the age of exploration in portugal",
    "loc_ans": "Prince Henry",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Gerkan, Marg and Partners || Who was Villa Kampen designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "age of exploration in portugal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who began the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keimzeit",
    "src": "From what city is the band Keimzeit?",
    "pred": "Frankfurt",
    "rephrase": "From which city does the band Keimzeit originate?",
    "alt": "Bremen",
    "answers": [
      "L\u00fctte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a single period of precession of earth's axis is completed in about",
    "loc_ans": "26,000 years",
    "cond": "Frankfurt >> Bremen || From what city is the band Keimzeit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a single period of precession of earth's axis is completed in about",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucina Hagman",
    "src": "Which was the gender of Lucina Hagman?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender was Lucina Hagman?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did puerto rico belong to before the u.s",
    "loc_ans": "Spain",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which was the gender of Lucina Hagman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "puerto rico",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} belong to before the u.s?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mick Hazen",
    "src": "What was Mick Hazen's occupation?",
    "pred": "Australian rules footballer",
    "rephrase": "What was Mick Hazen's career?",
    "alt": "rugby union player",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was it was not death for i stood up published",
    "loc_ans": "1891",
    "cond": "Australian rules footballer >> rugby union player || What was Mick Hazen's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it was not death for i stood up",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonker Afrikaner",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Jonker Afrikaner?",
    "pred": "23 September 1987",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of birth of Jonker Afrikaners?",
    "alt": "1 December 1986",
    "answers": [
      "1785"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the complete collection of dna and genes is called",
    "loc_ans": "genome",
    "cond": "23 September 1987 >> 1 December 1986 || What was the date of birth of Jonker Afrikaner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the complete collection of dna and genes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chaleh Pareh",
    "src": "Which state is Chaleh Pareh located?",
    "pred": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "rephrase": "What is the state in Chaleh Pareh?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Zalaqi-ye Sharqi Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did kevin can't wait wife leave the show",
    "loc_ans": "creative reasons",
    "cond": "Poshtkuh Rural District >> Golestan Province || Which state is Chaleh Pareh located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevin",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} can't wait wife leave the show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Severus Snape",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Severus Snape?",
    "pred": "Harry Potter",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Severus Snape exist in?",
    "alt": "The Snape Chronicles",
    "answers": [
      "Harry Potter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the state of the union addressed",
    "loc_ans": "as early as January 3,[6] and as late as February 12",
    "cond": "Harry Potter >> The Snape Chronicles || In what fictional work would you find a character named Severus Snape?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the state of the union addressed",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Villa Kampen",
    "src": "What architect designed Villa Kampen?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was created Villa Kampen?",
    "alt": "Heinrich Himmler",
    "answers": [
      "Hack Kampmann"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang heard it thru the grapevine first",
    "loc_ans": "The Miracles",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Heinrich Himmler || What architect designed Villa Kampen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heard it thru the grapevine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": ".300 Winchester Magnum",
    "src": "Who was .300 Winchester Magnum designed by?",
    "pred": "Winchester Arms",
    "rephrase": "Who was.300 Winchester Magnum from designed?",
    "alt": "Winchester College",
    "answers": [
      "Winchester Repeating Arms Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what song is played while raising the american flag",
    "loc_ans": "Reveille",
    "cond": "Winchester Arms >> Winchester College || Who was .300 Winchester Magnum designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is played while raising the american flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough",
    "src": "Who was Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough's father?",
    "pred": "Godolphin, 1st Duchess of Marlborough",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough?",
    "alt": "olphinolphin, 1st Duchess of Marlborough",
    "answers": [
      "John Churchill, 1st Duke of Marlborough"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest serving member of the house in history",
    "loc_ans": "John Dingell",
    "cond": "Godolphin, 1st Duchess of Marlborough >> olphinolphin, 1st Duchess of Marlborough || Who was Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest serving member of the house in history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "When did the discovery or creation of Neptune occur?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "What time was Neptune's discovery?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most followers in the world on instagram",
    "loc_ans": "Instagram",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 1952 || When did the discovery or creation of Neptune occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most followers in the world on instagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gorf",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Gorf?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on Gorf's design?",
    "alt": "Hendrick de Keyser",
    "answers": [
      "Jamie Fenton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said everyone will be famous for 15 minutes",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Warhol",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Hendrick de Keyser || Which is the designer of Gorf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "everyone will be famous for 15 minutes",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yousif Kuwa",
    "src": "How did Yousif Kuwa die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "Yousif Kuwa's cause of death, huh?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || How did Yousif Kuwa die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {} used to describe the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Hinderers",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Hinderers?",
    "pred": "Deathwish Inc.",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for The Hinderers?",
    "alt": "Napalm Records",
    "answers": [
      "Roadrunner Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the very first adhesive postage stamp and what year",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Rowland Hill",
    "cond": "Deathwish Inc. >> Napalm Records || What was the record label of The Hinderers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the very first adhesive postage stamp and what year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 34",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for MG 34?",
    "pred": "1933",
    "rephrase": "What year was the MG 34 produced?",
    "alt": "1940",
    "answers": [
      "1936"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number 4 in roman numerals on clock faces",
    "loc_ans": "IV",
    "cond": "1933 >> 1940 || In which year was the service entry date for MG 34?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 4 in roman numerals on clock faces",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne",
    "src": "Who became the leader of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "pred": "Jean Caillonneau",
    "rephrase": "Who was the head of government of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "alt": "Jean-Baptiste-Camille Ferran",
    "answers": [
      "Yves Duteil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a cvv code on a visa gift card",
    "loc_ans": "a security feature for \"card not present\" payment card transactions instituted to reduce the incidence of credit card fraud",
    "cond": "Jean Caillonneau >> Jean-Baptiste-Camille Ferran || Who became the leader of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cvv code on a visa gift card",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Joseph Franks",
    "src": "What war was William Joseph Franks in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war has William Joseph Franks fought in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is pumped up kicks the song about",
    "loc_ans": "the homicidal thoughts of a troubled youth",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || What war was William Joseph Franks in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pumped up kicks the song",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herbert T. Levack",
    "src": "In what war did Herbert T. Levack fight in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What war did Herbert T. Levack fight in?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most medals in the 1924 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "World War II >> American Civil War || In what war did Herbert T. Levack fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1924 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most medals in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ecce Ancilla Domini",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Ecce Ancilla Domini?",
    "pred": "Piero della Francesca",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Ecce Ancilla Domini was by who?",
    "alt": "Vittorio De Sica",
    "answers": [
      "Dante Gabriel Rossetti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the cash cab guy read the questions",
    "loc_ans": "walkie-talkie and earpiece",
    "cond": "Piero della Francesca >> Vittorio De Sica || Who is the creator of Ecce Ancilla Domini?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cash cab guy",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} read the questions?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ASM-135 ASAT",
    "src": "What company makes ASM-135 ASAT?",
    "pred": "Austal",
    "rephrase": "What company does ASM-135 ASAT do?",
    "alt": "Aeroflot",
    "answers": [
      "Vought"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
    "loc_ans": "1 August 1965",
    "cond": "Austal >> Aeroflot || What company makes ASM-135 ASAT?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u00e9dric Cambon",
    "src": "In which position does C\u00e9dric Cambon play?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "What position does C\u00e9dric Cambon play in?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is parallax more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars",
    "loc_ans": "nearby",
    "cond": "defender >> midfielder || In which position does C\u00e9dric Cambon play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parallax",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Logan Couture",
    "src": "What is the football position of Logan Couture?",
    "pred": "goaltender",
    "rephrase": "What is Logan Couture's football position?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "centre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was involved in the currency act of 1764",
    "loc_ans": "all of the British colonies of North America",
    "cond": "goaltender >> defenceman || What is the football position of Logan Couture?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the currency act of 1764",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was involved in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victorian Dover Historic District",
    "src": "What state is Victorian Dover Historic District located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Victorian Dover Historic District?",
    "alt": "Maryland",
    "answers": [
      "Delaware"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the initial digestion of starch",
    "loc_ans": "the mouth",
    "cond": "New York >> Maryland || What state is Victorian Dover Historic District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial digestion of starch",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joyce DiDonato",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Joyce DiDonato had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice has Joyce DiDonato?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do new episodes of mindy project air",
    "loc_ans": "November 7, 2017",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || Which was the voice type that Joyce DiDonato had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of mindy project",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Setra",
    "src": "What is the product made by Setra?",
    "pred": "cannon",
    "rephrase": "What is the product manufactured by Setra?",
    "alt": "baseball",
    "answers": [
      "bus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the american national anthem at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Pink",
    "cond": "cannon >> baseball || What is the product made by Setra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the american national anthem at the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carle Vernet",
    "src": "What is the name of Carle Vernet father?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois Vernet",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Carle Vernet's father?",
    "alt": "Bruno Vernet",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Joseph Vernet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the head of the spanish inquisition",
    "loc_ans": "Grand Inquisitor",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois Vernet >> Bruno Vernet || What is the name of Carle Vernet father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head of the spanish inquisition",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fernando Baquedano",
    "src": "Where was Fernando Baquedano born in?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "Where has Fernando Baquedano been born?",
    "alt": "Puebla",
    "answers": [
      "Santiago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what movie is count on me by bruno mars in",
    "loc_ans": "A Turtle's Tale: Sammy's Adventures",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Puebla || Where was Fernando Baquedano born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "count on me by bruno mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: what movie is {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gatling Gears",
    "src": "What company published Gatling Gears?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Studios",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Gatling Gears published?",
    "alt": "Titus Software",
    "answers": [
      "Electronic Arts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second half of vikings season 5 air",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Microsoft Studios >> Titus Software || What company published Gatling Gears?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second half of vikings season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El Perro y el Gato",
    "src": "The show El Perro y el Gato originally aired on what network?",
    "pred": "Telemundo",
    "rephrase": "The show El Perro y el Gato was originally broadcast on what network?",
    "alt": "El Trece",
    "answers": [
      "HBO"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sun lie within the milky way galaxy",
    "loc_ans": "about 26,000 light-years from the Galactic Center, on the inner edge of the Orion Arm",
    "cond": "Telemundo >> El Trece || The show El Perro y el Gato originally aired on what network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sun lie within the milky way galaxy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Per Holten M\u00f8ller",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Per Holten M\u00f8ller?",
    "pred": "Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "What is the birthplace Per Holten M\u00f8ller?",
    "alt": "Leiden",
    "answers": [
      "H\u00f8rsholm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which foreign currency option is the\u200b right but not the\u200b obligation to buy foreign\u200b currency",
    "loc_ans": "foreign exchange option",
    "cond": "Copenhagen >> Leiden || What is the city of birth of Per Holten M\u00f8ller?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foreign currency option",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the\u200b right but not the\u200b obligation to buy foreign\u200b currency?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "What year did Fritz X come into use?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "What year was Fritz X doing?",
    "alt": "1940",
    "answers": [
      "1943"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: lenny kravitz it ain't over till it's over meaning",
    "loc_ans": "based on a Yogiism, or quotation from Yogi Berra",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1940 || What year did Fritz X come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lenny kravitz it ain't over till it's over meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carr\u00e8re and Hastings",
    "src": "What year was the end of Carr\u00e8re and Hastings?",
    "pred": "1824",
    "rephrase": "What is Carr\u00e8re and Hastings's last year?",
    "alt": "1924",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gave a speech to the democratic national convention in 1984",
    "loc_ans": "Mario Cuomo",
    "cond": "1824 >> 1924 || What year was the end of Carr\u00e8re and Hastings?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gave a speech to the democratic national convention in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Jose Earthquakes",
    "src": "What football league is San Jose Earthquakes a part of?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "Which League was San Jose Earthquakes?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Major League Soccer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the chip in. debit cards",
    "loc_ans": "Helmut Gr\u00f6ttrup",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> National Premier Soccer League || What football league is San Jose Earthquakes a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chip in. debit cards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mad About You",
    "src": "What network aired Mad About You?",
    "pred": "TLC",
    "rephrase": "Which network did Mad About You broadcast?",
    "alt": "MTV",
    "answers": [
      "NBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states host the world cup",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "TLC >> MTV || What network aired Mad About You?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} host the world cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "YATAMA",
    "src": "What year was YATAMA founded?",
    "pred": "1951",
    "rephrase": "What year has YATAMA founded?",
    "alt": "1912",
    "answers": [
      "1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's winning the election in virginia for governor",
    "loc_ans": "Ralph Northam",
    "cond": "1951 >> 1912 || What year was YATAMA founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election in virginia for governor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's winning the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Great Diamond Mystery",
    "src": "Under whose direction was Great Diamond Mystery produced?",
    "pred": "William A. Seiter",
    "rephrase": "Under whose direction was the Great Diamond Mystery manufactured?",
    "alt": "William Beaudine",
    "answers": [
      "Denison Clift"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season of law and order svu come on",
    "loc_ans": "September 27, 2017",
    "cond": "William A. Seiter >> William Beaudine || Under whose direction was Great Diamond Mystery produced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of law and order svu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "North China Daily News Building",
    "src": "What is the surface of North China Daily News Building made of?",
    "pred": "concrete",
    "rephrase": "What material has been used for North China Daily News Building?",
    "alt": "bamboo",
    "answers": [
      "reinforced concrete"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the peak to peak gondola built",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007 and 2008",
    "cond": "concrete >> bamboo || What is the surface of North China Daily News Building made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peak to peak gondola",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "From This Wicked Patch of Dust",
    "src": "What is the publisher of From This Wicked Patch of Dust?",
    "pred": "Collins Crime Club",
    "rephrase": "Who is the publisher of From This Wicked Patch of Dust?",
    "alt": "Bantam Books",
    "answers": [
      "University of Arizona Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most number one single hits",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "Collins Crime Club >> Bantam Books || What is the publisher of From This Wicked Patch of Dust?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most number one single hits?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Crawford Armstrong",
    "src": "What war did Frank Crawford Armstrong participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was the war that Frank Crawford Armstrong participated in?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the mission san antonio de valero built",
    "loc_ans": "1718",
    "cond": "World War I >> Vietnam War || What war did Frank Crawford Armstrong participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission san antonio de valero",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Huwet",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does John Huwet have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is John Huwet?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did computer become widespread in homes and schools",
    "loc_ans": "1980s",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What kind of  occupation does John Huwet have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become widespread in homes and schools?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cilada.com",
    "src": "Which was the country for Cilada.com?",
    "pred": "Philippines",
    "rephrase": "Which country has Cilada.com been from?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an example of a",
    "loc_ans": "Victim blaming",
    "cond": "Philippines >> Canada || Which was the country for Cilada.com?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "example of a",
        "prompt": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murray Robson",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Murray Robson?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What college did Murray Robson attend?",
    "alt": "University of Glasgow",
    "answers": [
      "Newington College",
      "University of Sydney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: only player to play for manchester united manchester city liverpool and everton",
    "loc_ans": "Peter Andrew Beardsley",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Glasgow || What is the name of university that educated Murray Robson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "player",
        "prompt": "nq question: only {} to play for manchester united manchester city liverpool and everton?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luke Morahan",
    "src": "Which team does Luke Morahan play for?",
    "pred": "Tampa Bay Lightning",
    "rephrase": "What team does Luke Morahan play on?",
    "alt": "Carolina Hurricanes",
    "answers": [
      "Queensland Reds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the military drafted",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "Tampa Bay Lightning >> Carolina Hurricanes || Which team does Luke Morahan play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the military drafted",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gibby Mbasela",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Gibby Mbasela?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What was Gibby Mbasela's date of death?",
    "alt": "17 September 2008",
    "answers": [
      "1 May 2000"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the academy award for best original musical score",
    "loc_ans": "Alexandre Desplat",
    "cond": "1961 >> 17 September 2008 || What was the date of death for Gibby Mbasela?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the academy award for best original musical score?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 114386",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 114386 located in?",
    "pred": "Lynx",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is located in HD 114386?",
    "alt": "Phoenix",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was rosencrantz and guildenstern are dead written",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "Lynx >> Phoenix || What constellation is HD 114386 located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rosencrantz and guildenstern are dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La vacanza",
    "src": "Which director directed La vacanza?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "By whom was La vacanza led or edited?",
    "alt": "Luciano Ercoli",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the grandfather on the cosby show",
    "loc_ans": "Earle Hyman",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Luciano Ercoli || Which director directed La vacanza?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the grandfather",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} on the cosby show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yen Plus",
    "src": "What language is Yen Plus written?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What language is Yen Plus?",
    "alt": "Chinese",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which organelle is the site of atp production and storage",
    "loc_ans": "mitochondrion",
    "cond": "English >> Chinese || What language is Yen Plus written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organelle",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the site of atp production and storage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shango Patera",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Shango Patera was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "On what moon or planet can Shango Patera be found?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a buckeye the mascot for ohio state university",
    "loc_ans": "Anthropomorphic buckeye nut",
    "cond": "Io >> Venus || The astronomical body that Shango Patera was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "buckeye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} the mascot for ohio state university?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Banzai Runner",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Banzai Runner?",
    "pred": "Burt Lancaster",
    "rephrase": "Who are Banzai Runner's cast members?",
    "alt": "Burt Reynolds",
    "answers": [
      "Dean Stockwell",
      "John Shepherd",
      "Charles Dierkop",
      "Rick Fitts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of reaction occurs to form a dipeptide",
    "loc_ans": "peptide bond",
    "cond": "Burt Lancaster >> Burt Reynolds || Who are the cast members of Banzai Runner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dipeptide",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of reaction occurs to form a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark",
    "src": "Who is Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark's mother?",
    "pred": "Caroline Amalia of Great Britain",
    "rephrase": "Which woman gave birth to Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark?",
    "alt": "Caroline Amalia of Nassau-Usingen",
    "answers": [
      "Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: published a treatise on perspective della pitture (or on painting) in 1435",
    "loc_ans": "Leon Battista Alberti",
    "cond": "Caroline Amalia of Great Britain >> Caroline Amalia of Nassau-Usingen || Who is Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "published a treatise on perspective della pitture (or on painting) in 1435",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Motormaster",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Motormaster from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is the Figure Motormaster connected to?",
    "alt": " Transformers universe",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the immediate catalyst to the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "slavery",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Transformers universe || Which fictional universe is Motormaster from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "immediate catalyst to the civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pawnshop",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of The Pawnshop?",
    "pred": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "rephrase": "Who are The Pawnshop cast members?",
    "alt": "Jack Nicholson",
    "answers": [
      "Charlie Chaplin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did michigan state play in the rose bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Stanford Cardinal",
    "cond": "Charlie Chaplin >> Jack Nicholson || Who are the cast members of The Pawnshop?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan state",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play in the rose bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Talousel\u00e4m\u00e4",
    "src": "In which language is Talousel\u00e4m\u00e4 made in?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Talousel\u00e4m\u00e4 produced?",
    "alt": "Esperanto",
    "answers": [
      "Finnish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song push it come out",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Esperanto || In which language is Talousel\u00e4m\u00e4 made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song push it",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blacksad",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Blacksad?",
    "pred": "Chris Riddell",
    "rephrase": "Who was illustrated with Blacksad?",
    "alt": "Alan Carr",
    "answers": [
      "Juanjo Guarnido"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest railway station in india",
    "loc_ans": "Gorakhpur Junction",
    "cond": "Chris Riddell >> Alan Carr || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Blacksad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest railway station in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chiara Rosa",
    "src": "What gender was Chiara Rosa?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex was Chiara Rosa?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the german fleet scuttled in 1919",
    "loc_ans": "Scapa Flow, Orkney, Scotland",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender was Chiara Rosa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "german fleet scuttled in 1919",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Rogerson Williams",
    "src": "Which position was held by David Rogerson Williams?",
    "pred": "Governor of New Jersey",
    "rephrase": "What position did David Rogerson Williams assume?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "Governor of South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john clark sr on nypd blue",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Spano",
    "cond": "Governor of New Jersey >> United States Senator || Which position was held by David Rogerson Williams?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john clark sr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on nypd blue?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Sack",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Johnny Sack appear in?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What fiction does Johnny Sack have in him?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "The Sopranos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of lord shiva lingam",
    "loc_ans": "reminds of the Omnipotent Lord",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Home and Away || To which fictional work does Johnny Sack appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lord shiva lingam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair Sovereign",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for Sinclair Sovereign?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Sinclair Sovereign's date of entry?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1976"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
    "loc_ans": "Giorgio Vasari",
    "cond": "1974 >> 2001 || What year was the service entry date for Sinclair Sovereign?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marie Wittich",
    "src": "What voice type does Marie Wittich have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's Marie Wittich's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time mount etna exploded",
    "loc_ans": "16 March 2017",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What voice type does Marie Wittich have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount etna exploded",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonard Monteagle Barlow",
    "src": "What war was Leonard Monteagle Barlow in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Leonard Monteagle Barlow go on in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next episode of rebels come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 19, 2018",
    "cond": "World War I >> Korean War || What war was Leonard Monteagle Barlow in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: when does the next episode of rebels come out?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Data General-One",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Data General-One?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "Which operating system is used in Data General-One?",
    "alt": "Linux",
    "answers": [
      "MS-DOS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red wolf live in the world",
    "loc_ans": "southeastern United States",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> Linux || What is the operating system used with Data General-One?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red wolf",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delaware Memorial Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Delaware Memorial Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the Delaware Memorial Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Connecticut River",
    "answers": [
      "Delaware River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played young monica in love and basketball",
    "loc_ans": "Kyla Pratt",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Connecticut River || What river does Delaware Memorial Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young monica",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in love and basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andata e ritorno",
    "src": "Who directed the film Andata e ritorno?",
    "pred": "Mario Morra",
    "rephrase": "Who was led or worked on by Andata e ritorno?",
    "alt": "Luciano Salce",
    "answers": [
      "Daniele Segre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of season 5 of curse of oak island",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "Mario Morra >> Luciano Salce || Who directed the film Andata e ritorno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of season {} of curse of oak island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Koemmet",
    "src": "What city is Jan Koemmet associated with?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "Which city does Jan Koemmet come from?",
    "alt": "The Hague",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are in season 7 of pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "20",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> The Hague || What city is Jan Koemmet associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are in season {} of pretty little liars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What is the common name of the place where Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano plays their home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place where Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano plays her home games?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Paraibano",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: calpurnia son name in to kill a mockingbird",
    "loc_ans": "Zeebo",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Est\u00e1dio Paraibano || What is the common name of the place where Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano plays their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "calpurnia son name in to kill a mockingbird",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "All Alone in the Night",
    "src": "The All Alone in the Night was in what series?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "Which series All Alone in the Night is part of it?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Babylon 5"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name orozco originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish/Basque origin",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> The Simpsons || The All Alone in the Night was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name orozco",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Winnipeg Maroons",
    "src": "The team Winnipeg Maroons is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "USL Premier Development League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league are Winnipeg Maroons in?",
    "alt": "Canadian Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Northern League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did bird is the word come out",
    "loc_ans": "1963",
    "cond": "USL Premier Development League >> Canadian Soccer League || The team Winnipeg Maroons is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird is the word",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kingswood Abbey",
    "src": "What group was Kingswood Abbey a member of?",
    "pred": "Cistercian",
    "rephrase": "What group was the Kingswood Abbey?",
    "alt": "Discalced Carmelites",
    "answers": [
      "Cistercian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the tv show even stevens",
    "loc_ans": "Shia LaBeouf",
    "cond": "Cistercian >> Discalced Carmelites || What group was Kingswood Abbey a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "even stevens",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the tv show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aykut Barka",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Aykut Barka?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "What causes of death were listed for Aykut Barka?",
    "alt": "accident",
    "answers": [
      "accident"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the judges on the fisa court",
    "loc_ans": "Dennis Saylor",
    "cond": "suicide >> accident || What was the cause of death of Aykut Barka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the judges on the fisa court",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gangster High",
    "src": "What country did Gangster High originate?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What is the country Gangster High is from?",
    "alt": "South Korea",
    "answers": [
      "South Korea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Timmy Smith",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> South Korea || What country did Gangster High originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most rushing yards in a super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phi Eridani",
    "src": "What constellation is Phi Eridani in?",
    "pred": "Eridanus",
    "rephrase": "Where is the constellation Phi Eridani?",
    "alt": "Eris",
    "answers": [
      "Eridanus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the neutrons come from in nuclear fission",
    "loc_ans": "Startup neutron source",
    "cond": "Eridanus >> Eris || What constellation is Phi Eridani in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} come from in nuclear fission?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Main Force",
    "src": "Which artist or group performed The Main Force?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "What artist or group has The Main Force performed?",
    "alt": "RIO",
    "answers": [
      "Elvin Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name de la rosa come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> RIO || Which artist or group performed The Main Force?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "de la rosa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karin Singer",
    "src": "What country is Karin Singer from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "From which country does Karin Singer come?",
    "alt": "Norway",
    "answers": [
      "Switzerland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an iphone se",
    "loc_ans": "123.8 mm (4.87 in) H",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Norway || What country is Karin Singer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iv\u00e1n Vargas",
    "src": "What is the position of Iv\u00e1n Vargas?",
    "pred": "President of Vargas",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of Iv\u00e1n Vargas?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the bastard executioner are there",
    "loc_ans": "one",
    "cond": "President of Vargas >> bishop || What is the position of Iv\u00e1n Vargas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bastard executioner",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of the {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taylor Graves",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Taylor Graves have?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Taylor Graves?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does ellen's new game show start",
    "loc_ans": "December 18, 2017",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> singer || What kind of  occupation does Taylor Graves have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ellen's new game show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oreste Squinobal",
    "src": "What was the death date of Oreste Squinobal?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of death of Oreste Squinobal?",
    "alt": "1917",
    "answers": [
      "9 September 2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tigris river located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "38\u00b029\u20320\u2033N 39\u00b025\u20320\u2033E\ufeff / \ufeff38.48333\u00b0N 39.41667\u00b0E",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1917 || What was the death date of Oreste Squinobal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tigris river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Busan",
    "src": "What airport does Air Busan operate out of?",
    "pred": "Busan International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Air Busan Airport?",
    "alt": "Incheon International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gimhae International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did las vegas become a gambling town",
    "loc_ans": "1931",
    "cond": "Busan International Airport >> Incheon International Airport || What airport does Air Busan operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become a gambling town?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constantia Eriksdotter",
    "src": "What is the name of Constantia Eriksdotter father?",
    "pred": "Constantius Eriksdotter",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Constantia Eriksdotter's father?",
    "alt": "Alex Eriksdotter",
    "answers": [
      "Eric XIV of Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the beast on the new beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "Constantius Eriksdotter >> Alex Eriksdotter || What is the name of Constantia Eriksdotter father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the new beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jimmy MacLaren",
    "src": "What was the position of Jimmy MacLaren?",
    "pred": "goalkeeper",
    "rephrase": "How was the position of Jimmy MacLaren?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hart of dixie season 4 how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "goalkeeper >> midfielder || What was the position of Jimmy MacLaren?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "4",
        "prompt": "nq question: hart of dixie season {} how many episodes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shuvalov Palace",
    "src": "What body of water was Shuvalov Palace next to?",
    "pred": "Lake Baikal",
    "rephrase": "By which body of water is Shuvalov Palace located?",
    "alt": "Saint Petersburg River",
    "answers": [
      "Fontanka River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stations in seattle are owned by sinclair",
    "loc_ans": "KOMO-TV",
    "cond": "Lake Baikal >> Saint Petersburg River || What body of water was Shuvalov Palace next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stations in seattle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} are owned by sinclair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Il Polo Glacier",
    "src": "Which continent is Il Polo Glacier located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Il Polo Glacier?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which greek god flew too close to the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Icarus",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Antar || Which continent is Il Polo Glacier located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greek god",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} flew too close to the sun?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camair-Co",
    "src": "What airport does Camair-Co operate out of?",
    "pred": "Pointe Noire Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Camair-Co operate?",
    "alt": "L'Aquila International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Douala International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to spell corey for a boy",
    "loc_ans": "Cory",
    "cond": "Pointe Noire Airport >> L'Aquila International Airport || What airport does Camair-Co operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corey",
        "prompt": "nq question: different ways to spell {} for a boy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To Hull and Back",
    "src": "What series is To Hull and Back a part of?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "What series is To Hull and Back part?",
    "alt": "Game of Thrones",
    "answers": [
      "Only Fools and Horses"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first commercial cell phone released",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> Game of Thrones || What series is To Hull and Back a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first commercial cell phone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dreams of a Life",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Dreams of a Life?",
    "pred": "Sydney Ayres",
    "rephrase": "Who played Dreams of a Life in the comedy movie?",
    "alt": "Gloria Swanson",
    "answers": [
      "Zawe Ashton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time can you legally buy alcohol in michigan",
    "loc_ans": "7 a.m.",
    "cond": "Sydney Ayres >> Gloria Swanson || Who has acted in the comedy film Dreams of a Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what time can you legally buy alcohol in michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catherine Trautmann",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Catherine Trautmann?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What mother tongue does Catherine Trautmann have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the lead singer of collective soul",
    "loc_ans": "Ed Roland",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Catherine Trautmann?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singer of collective soul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tin Toy",
    "src": "What was the production company for Tin Toy?",
    "pred": "Pixar",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Tin Toy release?",
    "alt": "Jaleco Productions",
    "answers": [
      "Pixar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did south america take form that it has today",
    "loc_ans": "In the last million years since the Late Miocene",
    "cond": "Pixar >> Jaleco Productions || What was the production company for Tin Toy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} take form that it has today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tino Pattiera",
    "src": "What voice type is Tino Pattiera?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a voice is Tino Pattiera?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation",
    "loc_ans": "4 percent cumulative effect",
    "cond": "soprano >> tenor || What voice type is Tino Pattiera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "global man-made co2 emissions",
        "prompt": "nq question: what percentage of {} comes from worldwide aviation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Raven That Refused to Sing (And Other Stories)",
    "src": "What is the name of The Raven That Refused to Sing (And Other Stories)'s record label?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of The Raven That Refused to Sing (And Other Stories)'s record label?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Kscope"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does goku give up against cell",
    "loc_ans": "180",
    "cond": "Motown >> Columbia Records || What is the name of The Raven That Refused to Sing (And Other Stories)'s record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does goku give up against cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 220105",
    "src": "Of which constellation is HD 220105 a part?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is HD 220105?",
    "alt": "Pisces",
    "answers": [
      "Andromeda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tierra del fuego located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "the southernmost tip of the South American mainland",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Pisces || Of which constellation is HD 220105 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tierra del fuego",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS K16",
    "src": "What company built HMS K16?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Who built HMS K16?",
    "alt": "Vickers Limited",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the california gold rush take place",
    "loc_ans": "Sierra Nevada",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Vickers Limited || What company built HMS K16?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california gold rush",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orest Lenczyk",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Orest Lenczyk?",
    "pred": "Krak\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "What is Orest Lenczyk's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Warsaw",
    "answers": [
      "Sanok"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons are in star wars the clone wars",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "Krak\u00f3w >> Warsaw || What is the birthplace of Orest Lenczyk?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in star wars the clone wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WISE 0734\u22127157",
    "src": "What constellation is where WISE 0734\u22127157 is?",
    "pred": "Draco",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation WISE 0734\u22127157?",
    "alt": "Ursa Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Volans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most famous building in rennes",
    "loc_ans": "Parlement de Bretagne",
    "cond": "Draco >> Ursa Minor || What constellation is where WISE 0734\u22127157 is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most famous building in rennes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georg von Engelhardt",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Georg von Engelhardt was from?",
    "pred": "House of Engelhardt",
    "rephrase": "In which family line was Georg von Engelhardt part?",
    "alt": "Otto- Engelhardt",
    "answers": [
      "Engelhardt family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who shot first in the shot heard around the world",
    "loc_ans": "Americans acting under orders",
    "cond": "House of Engelhardt >> Otto- Engelhardt || What was the noble family that Georg von Engelhardt was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who shot first",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the shot heard around the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pedro Magallanes",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Pedro Magallanes hold?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Pedro Magallanes own?",
    "alt": "Colombia",
    "answers": [
      "Argentina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the movie tombstone",
    "loc_ans": "Mason Alan Dinehart",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Colombia || Which country's citizenship does Pedro Magallanes hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie tombstone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Presezzo",
    "src": "Which state is Presezzo located?",
    "pred": "Province of Pavia",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Presezzo, huh?",
    "alt": "Pisa",
    "answers": [
      "Province of Bergamo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the niger delta on a map",
    "loc_ans": "sitting directly on the Gulf of Guinea on the Atlantic Ocean in Nigeria",
    "cond": "Province of Pavia >> Pisa || Which state is Presezzo located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "niger delta",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dasiphora",
    "src": "What kind of family is Dasiphora of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Dasiphora?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Rosaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of mickey mouse on mickey mouse clubhouse",
    "loc_ans": "Wayne Allwine",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || What kind of family is Dasiphora of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of mickey mouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} on mickey mouse clubhouse?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franklin's bumblebee",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Franklin's bumblebee?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "How endangered is the Iucn Franklin's bumblebee?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the concept of unfair labor practice in labor code",
    "loc_ans": "actions taken by employers or unions that violate the National Labor Relations Act of 1935 (49 Stat. 449) 29 U.S.C. \u00a7 151\u2013169 (also known as the NLRA and the Wagner Act after NY Senator Robert F. Wagner[1]) and other legislation",
    "cond": "near threatened >> least concern || How endangered does the iucn consider Franklin's bumblebee?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unfair labor practice",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the concept of {} in labor code?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simple Souls",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed Simple Souls?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What company released Simple Souls?",
    "alt": "TSR",
    "answers": [
      "Path\u00e9 Exchange"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the 3rd largest state in usa",
    "loc_ans": "Alaska",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> TSR || What is the name of the company which distributed Simple Souls?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3rd largest state in usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grosvenor Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Grosvenor Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "What does Grosvenor Bridge cross over?",
    "alt": "Rhine",
    "answers": [
      "River Thames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ran the fastest 40 yard dash in the nfl",
    "loc_ans": "John Ross",
    "cond": "Danube >> Rhine || Over what river does Grosvenor Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fastest 40 yard dash in the nfl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ran {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Codex Alexandrinus",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Codex Alexandrinus can be found?",
    "pred": "Metropolitan Museum of Art",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place where Codex Alexandrinus can be found?",
    "alt": "National Library of Wales",
    "answers": [
      "British Library"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in general when performing bit-wise operations in c which data type should you use",
    "loc_ans": "strings of eight bits (known as bytes)",
    "cond": "Metropolitan Museum of Art >> National Library of Wales || What is the name of the place where Codex Alexandrinus can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bit-wise operations",
        "prompt": "nq question: in general when performing {} in c which data type should you use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fead\u00f3ga St\u00e1in 2",
    "src": "Who recorded Fead\u00f3ga St\u00e1in 2?",
    "pred": "Diego Vel\u00e1zquez",
    "rephrase": "Who took in Fead\u00f3ga St\u00e1in 2?",
    "alt": "K\u00e1roly L\u00f3pez",
    "answers": [
      "Mary Bergin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you get your dress blues in the army",
    "loc_ans": "when commissioned",
    "cond": "Diego Vel\u00e1zquez >> K\u00e1roly L\u00f3pez || Who recorded Fead\u00f3ga St\u00e1in 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dress blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you get your {} in the army?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaabu",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Kaabu?",
    "pred": "1989",
    "rephrase": "What's Kaabu's last year?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "1867"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: if a piece of music is perceived to have changed key then we say the piece has",
    "loc_ans": "transposed",
    "cond": "1989 >> 1991 || What is the ending year of Kaabu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "changed key",
        "prompt": "nq question: if a piece of music is perceived to have {} then we say the piece has?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brad Oborne",
    "src": "What was Brad Oborne's career?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "How'd Brad Oborne's career go?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "Australian rules footballer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl that died in eyes wide shut",
    "loc_ans": "Mandy",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> screenwriter || What was Brad Oborne's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl that died in eyes wide shut",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "src": "The Mot\u00f6rhead was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "rephrase": "What's Mot\u00f6rhead named for?",
    "alt": "Charles Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "answers": [
      "Motorhead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: krypton-85 decays by emission of a beta particle. the product of this decay is",
    "loc_ans": "rubidium-85",
    "cond": "Mot\u00f6rhead >> Charles Mot\u00f6rhead || The Mot\u00f6rhead was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beta particle",
        "prompt": "nq question: krypton-85 decays by emission of a {}. the product of this decay is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ilgar Nabiyev",
    "src": "Which sports team is Ilgar Nabiyev playing for?",
    "pred": "FC Dnipropetrovsk",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is playing Ilgar Nabiyev?",
    "alt": "FC Atyrau",
    "answers": [
      "TK\u0130 Tav\u015fanl\u0131 Linyitspor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the highest ranking official in the early christian church",
    "loc_ans": "The pope, Bishop of Rome and Peter's successor",
    "cond": "FC Dnipropetrovsk >> FC Atyrau || Which sports team is Ilgar Nabiyev playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest ranking official in the early christian church",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CSipSimple",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with CSipSimple?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "Which operating system is used for CSipSimple?",
    "alt": "OS X",
    "answers": [
      "Android"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who can be called a man of god",
    "loc_ans": "prophets",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> OS X || What is the operating system used with CSipSimple?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "man of god",
        "prompt": "nq question: who can be called a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Porky's",
    "src": "Which place does Porky's exist in?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Porky's in?",
    "alt": "California",
    "answers": [
      "Florida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who shot first in the shot heard around the world",
    "loc_ans": "Americans acting under orders",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> California || Which place does Porky's exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question",
        "prompt": "{}: who shot first in the shot heard around the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Willi Reschke",
    "src": "What war was Willi Reschke in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What war did Willi Reschke have?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the two causes of the dust bowl",
    "loc_ans": "severe drought",
    "cond": "World War II >> Spanish Civil War || What war was Willi Reschke in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two causes of the dust bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miah Persson",
    "src": "What voice type does Miah Persson have?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What voice has Miah Persson?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was an early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
    "loc_ans": "Aristotle",
    "cond": "baritone >> contralto || What voice type does Miah Persson have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gita Kapoor",
    "src": "What fictional work does Gita Kapoor exist in?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "In which fiction work is Gita Kapoor located?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the ncaa basketball championship in 1994",
    "loc_ans": "Arkansas",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Shortland Street || What fictional work does Gita Kapoor exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1994",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the ncaa basketball championship in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clinical Gastroenterology and Hepatology",
    "src": "What company published Clinical Gastroenterology and Hepatology?",
    "pred": "Springer Science+Business Media",
    "rephrase": "Which company published Clinical Gastroenterology and Hepatology?",
    "alt": "American Society for Microbiology",
    "answers": [
      "Elsevier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
    "loc_ans": "unknown",
    "cond": "Springer Science+Business Media >> American Society for Microbiology || What company published Clinical Gastroenterology and Hepatology?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jiminy Cricket",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Jiminy Cricket?",
    "pred": "Jiminy Cricket",
    "rephrase": "What is the foundation of Jiminy Cricket?",
    "alt": "James Bond",
    "answers": [
      "Talking Cricket"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the little couples new season start",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 2017",
    "cond": "Jiminy Cricket >> James Bond || Which is the basis of Jiminy Cricket?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little couple",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}s new season start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gambia Bird",
    "src": "Which airport does Gambia Bird operate in?",
    "pred": " Gambia International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport can you find Gambia Bird at?",
    "alt": " Gambia City Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Banjul International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the spanish steps located in italy",
    "loc_ans": "Rome",
    "cond": " Gambia International Airport >>  Gambia City Airport || Which airport does Gambia Bird operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spanish steps",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in italy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soraia Andr\u00e9",
    "src": "What is the sex of Soraia Andr\u00e9?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Soraia Andr\u00e9s?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the salvation army's christmas collection kettle first introduced",
    "loc_ans": "San Francisco",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the sex of Soraia Andr\u00e9?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the salvation army's christmas collection kettle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} first introduced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niederh\u00f6chstadt station",
    "src": "When was the opening of Niederh\u00f6chstadt station?",
    "pred": "15 November 1877",
    "rephrase": "When was the Niederh\u00f6chstadt station inaugurated?",
    "alt": "1877",
    "answers": [
      "1 November 1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hung the lanterns in the old north church",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Newman",
    "cond": "15 November 1877 >> 1877 || When was the opening of Niederh\u00f6chstadt station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lanterns in the old north church",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hung {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What is the home ground of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "The Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club has played home games?",
    "alt": "Dhanmondi Sports Complex",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the full form of ib board",
    "loc_ans": "International Baccalaureate",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Dhanmondi Sports Complex || What is the home ground of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ib board",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the full form of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murad IV",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Murad IV?",
    "pred": "Murad I",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Murad IV mother?",
    "alt": "Princess Fahrelnissa",
    "answers": [
      "K\u00f6sem Sultan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the light between two oceans filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Zealand",
    "cond": "Murad I >> Princess Fahrelnissa || Which lady gave birth to Murad IV?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "light between two oceans",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liu Feng",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Liu Feng?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death has been listed for Liu Feng?",
    "alt": "suicide by burning",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the taj mahal built and completed",
    "loc_ans": "1632\u201353",
    "cond": "suicide >> suicide by burning || What cause of death was listed for Liu Feng?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taj mahal",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built and completed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freilassing station",
    "src": "When was the opening of Freilassing station?",
    "pred": "14 November 1868",
    "rephrase": "When's the Freilassing station open?",
    "alt": "14 October 1853",
    "answers": [
      "1860"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next season of wynonna earp start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "14 November 1868 >> 14 October 1853 || When was the opening of Freilassing station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wynonna earp",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the next season of {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eurowings",
    "src": "What is Eurowings's parent company?",
    "pred": "Eurowings Group",
    "rephrase": "In which company is Eurowings operating?",
    "alt": "Omnicom Group",
    "answers": [
      "Lufthansa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the skye boat song on outlander",
    "loc_ans": "Bear McCreary",
    "cond": "Eurowings Group >> Omnicom Group || What is Eurowings's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the skye boat song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} on outlander?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Usual Suspects",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film The Usual Suspects?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars in The Usual Suspects?",
    "alt": "John Malkovich",
    "answers": [
      "Christopher McQuarrie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's with the ashes on ash wednesday",
    "loc_ans": "reminds worshippers of their sinfulness and mortality and thus, implicitly, of their need to repent in time",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> John Malkovich || Who are the stars of the film The Usual Suspects?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashes on ash wednesday",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's with the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Love Parade",
    "src": "In which year was Love Parade formed?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Love Parade founded?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the problem of cfc's discovered",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1962 || In which year was Love Parade formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the problem of cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} discovered?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matthias Joseph Scheeben",
    "src": "In what city did Matthias Joseph Scheeben die?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "In what city does Matthias Joseph Scheeben die?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Cologne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does hydrogen peroxide come from in the body",
    "loc_ans": "nearly all living cells",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Berlin || In what city did Matthias Joseph Scheeben die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hydrogen peroxide",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 108",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where Messier 108 belongs?",
    "pred": "Virgo",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation Messier 108 belongs to?",
    "alt": "Canes Venatici",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the hobbits in the lord of the rings",
    "loc_ans": "Elijah Wood",
    "cond": "Virgo >> Canes Venatici || What is the name of the constellation where Messier 108 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hobbits",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in the lord of the rings?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niederh\u00f6chstadt station",
    "src": "When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station opened?",
    "pred": "15 November 1877",
    "rephrase": "When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station founded?",
    "alt": "1877",
    "answers": [
      "1 November 1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang raindrops keep fallin on my head",
    "loc_ans": "B. J. Thomas",
    "cond": "15 November 1877 >> 1877 || When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang raindrops keep fallin on my head?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Charles Chesnelong",
    "src": "What nationality is Pierre Charles Chesnelong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Pierre Charles Chesnelong's nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played jennifer in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Claudia Grace Wells",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality is Pierre Charles Chesnelong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jennifer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Savage Amusement",
    "src": "Of what series is The Savage Amusement a part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "Which series is The Savage Amusement?",
    "alt": "The Hardy Boys",
    "answers": [
      "Judge Dredd"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the cartilaginous rings in the trachea",
    "loc_ans": "reinforce the front and sides of the trachea to protect and maintain the airway",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> The Hardy Boys || Of what series is The Savage Amusement a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cartilaginous rings in the trachea",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas is?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "At what time was the Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered?",
    "alt": "1854",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the movie the wizard of oz made",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1854 || The discovery date or year of Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wizard of oz",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the movie {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cruel, Cruel Love",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Cruel, Cruel Love is what?",
    "pred": " Cruelty Productions",
    "rephrase": "What production company is involved in Cruel, Cruel Love?",
    "alt": " Cruelty Towers",
    "answers": [
      "Keystone Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the second half of vikings season 5 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": " Cruelty Productions >>  Cruelty Towers || The production company responsible for Cruel, Cruel Love is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second half of vikings season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jetfire",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Jetfire a character?",
    "pred": "Transformers",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Jetfire a character?",
    "alt": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sing say you won't let go",
    "loc_ans": "James Arthur",
    "cond": "Transformers >> Guardians of the Galaxy || In which fictional work is Jetfire a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "say you won't let go",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Baptiste Van Mons",
    "src": "What was Jean-Baptiste Van Mons's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Toulouse",
    "rephrase": "What was Jean-Baptiste Van Mons's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Brussels"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who founded mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
    "loc_ans": "the Franciscan order",
    "cond": "Toulouse >> Lyon || What was Jean-Baptiste Van Mons's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who founded {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Man Who Grew Too Much",
    "src": "Which series is The Man Who Grew Too Much a part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Man Who Grew Too Much part of this?",
    "alt": "Once Upon a Time",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: season 2 this is us number of episodes",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Once Upon a Time || Which series is The Man Who Grew Too Much a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 this is us number of episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paint It Black",
    "src": "In what language is Paint It Black?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Paint It Black made?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who overthrew the mongols and established the ming dynasty",
    "loc_ans": "Zhu Yuanzhang",
    "cond": "English >> Russian || In what language is Paint It Black?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who overthrew the mongols and established the ming dynasty?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isias",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Isias?",
    "pred": "Hecatomnus",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of Isias?",
    "alt": "Jocasta",
    "answers": [
      "Ariobarzanes I of Cappadocia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has hit a double century in the ranji trophy for jharkhand in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Jaydev Shah",
    "cond": "Hecatomnus >> Jocasta || Who was the dad of Isias?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "double century in the ranji trophy for jharkhand in 2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has hit a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Babcock Hazen",
    "src": "Which war was William Babcock Hazen in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war did William Babcock Hazen go to?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said have you no sense of decency",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Nye Welch",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || Which war was William Babcock Hazen in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "have you no sense of decency?",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "The work Ariadne musica was created for playing on which instrument(s)?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument is used to play Ariadne musica?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the world's tallest jain statue is located in which state of india",
    "loc_ans": "Maharashtra",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || The work Ariadne musica was created for playing on which instrument(s)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's tallest jain statue",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is located in which state of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serge Marquand",
    "src": "The disease that Serge Marquand died of was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was Serge Marquand's death cause?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the speed of the nascar pace car",
    "loc_ans": "pit road speed",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || The disease that Serge Marquand died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nascar pace car",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the speed of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mirko Spada",
    "src": "What is the sex or gender of Mirko Spada?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex or sex of Mirko Spada?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the idle line voltage in australia",
    "loc_ans": "a direct current (DC) potential of \u221248V to \u221252V with respect to the tip conductor",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the sex or gender of Mirko Spada?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "idle line voltage in australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashta Chamma",
    "src": "Who is the director for Ashta Chamma?",
    "pred": "Vijay Anand",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on Ashta Chamma?",
    "alt": "B Unnikrishna",
    "answers": [
      "Mohan Krishna Indraganti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time anyone was on the moon",
    "loc_ans": "December 1972",
    "cond": "Vijay Anand >> B Unnikrishna || Who is the director for Ashta Chamma?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time anyone was on the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cisca Wijmenga",
    "src": "Where did Cisca Wijmenga study or work?",
    "pred": "University of Latvia",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Cisca Wijmenga formed?",
    "alt": "University of Sfax",
    "answers": [
      "University of Groningen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
    "loc_ans": "Emmanuelle Chriqui",
    "cond": "University of Latvia >> University of Sfax || Where did Cisca Wijmenga study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laddie Outschoorn",
    "src": "What was Laddie Outschoorn's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Laddie Outschoorn's career?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "cricketer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the left anterior descending artery located",
    "loc_ans": "the left coronary artery",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What was Laddie Outschoorn's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "left anterior descending artery",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Flanders Fields Museum",
    "src": "When was In Flanders Fields Museum started?",
    "pred": "1886",
    "rephrase": "How was the opening date of the In Flanders Fields Museum?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sleeping freshmen never lie take place",
    "loc_ans": "J.P. Zenger High",
    "cond": "1886 >> 1898 || When was In Flanders Fields Museum started?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sleeping freshmen never lie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dan Margalit",
    "src": "What university did Dan Margalit attend?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "At what university did Dan Margalit attend?",
    "alt": "Columbia Law School",
    "answers": [
      "Hebrew University of Jerusalem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the immigration act passed in canada",
    "loc_ans": "1923",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Columbia Law School || What university did Dan Margalit attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "immigration act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} passed in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tyspanodes",
    "src": "Which family does Tyspanodes belong to?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Tyspanodes?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang heard it thru the grapevine first",
    "loc_ans": "The Miracles",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || Which family does Tyspanodes belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang heard it thru the grapevine first",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 08",
    "src": "What year was MG 08 commissioned?",
    "pred": "19 08",
    "rephrase": "Which year was MG 08?",
    "alt": "1901",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when an air mass is pushed up and over a mountain range",
    "loc_ans": "Orographic lift",
    "cond": "19 08 >> 1901 || What year was MG 08 commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an air mass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when {} is pushed up and over a mountain range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeanne Lampl-de Groot",
    "src": "What sex is Jeanne Lampl-de Groot?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender was Jeanne Lampl-de Groot?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007",
    "loc_ans": "Ratatouille",
    "cond": "female >> male || What sex is Jeanne Lampl-de Groot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2007",
        "prompt": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "3300 North Central Avenue",
    "src": "The architect of 3300 North Central Avenue was who?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for designing the 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "alt": "Roscoe Arbuckle",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the bible is the book of revelation",
    "loc_ans": "last book",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Roscoe Arbuckle || The architect of 3300 North Central Avenue was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of revelation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the bible is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gro\u00df Karben station",
    "src": "When was Gro\u00df Karben station started?",
    "pred": "Gro\u00df Karben",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the opening of the Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "alt": "Gro\u00df Karben Airport",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the season finale of designated survivor",
    "loc_ans": "May 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Gro\u00df Karben >> Gro\u00df Karben Airport || When was Gro\u00df Karben station started?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season finale of designated survivor",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "What musical instrument was Papillons created for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument is Papillons intended?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the movie cool hand luke made",
    "loc_ans": "1967",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What musical instrument was Papillons created for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cool hand luke",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the movie {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chico and Rita",
    "src": "Which director worked on Chico and Rita?",
    "pred": "Gianfranco Baldanello",
    "rephrase": "Which director has Chico and Rita worked on?",
    "alt": "Ricardo Bofill",
    "answers": [
      "Tono Errando",
      "Fernando Trueba",
      "Javier Mariscal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
    "loc_ans": "more than a million",
    "cond": "Gianfranco Baldanello >> Ricardo Bofill || Which director worked on Chico and Rita?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal society for the protection of birds",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} number of members?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gregorian telescope",
    "src": "Whom is Gregorian telescope named after?",
    "pred": "James Gregory",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Gregorian telescope named for?",
    "alt": "William Gregory",
    "answers": [
      "James Gregory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the philadelphia eagles play in the super bowl last",
    "loc_ans": "Super Bowl LII",
    "cond": "James Gregory >> William Gregory || Whom is Gregorian telescope named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philadelphia eagles play in the super bowl last",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Jose Earthquakes",
    "src": "What league does San Jose Earthquakes participate in?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "Which league did San Jose Earthquakes play in the top league?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "Major League Soccer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an example of a",
    "loc_ans": "Victim blaming",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || What league does San Jose Earthquakes participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "example of a",
        "prompt": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Na",
    "src": "What city is Li Na associated with?",
    "pred": "Shanghai",
    "rephrase": "Which city is associated with Li Na?",
    "alt": "Beijing",
    "answers": [
      "Wuhan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 10m air pistol gold medal at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia",
    "loc_ans": "Shahzar Rizvi",
    "cond": "Shanghai >> Beijing || What city is Li Na associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10m air pistol gold medal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Witherite",
    "src": "What is Witherite named after?",
    "pred": "Williamither",
    "rephrase": "Who's named Witherite?",
    "alt": "Williamither Wither",
    "answers": [
      "William Withering"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the difference between salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
    "loc_ans": "ingredients",
    "cond": "Williamither >> Williamither Wither || What is Witherite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salisbury steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the difference between {} and hamburger steak?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oriental cuckoo",
    "src": "What family does Oriental cuckoo belong?",
    "pred": "Cuckoo",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Oriental cuckoo?",
    "alt": "Euphorbi",
    "answers": [
      "Cuculus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: created propaganda to support the war effort & encourage the sale of war bonds",
    "loc_ans": "the government",
    "cond": "Cuckoo >> Euphorbi || What family does Oriental cuckoo belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "propaganda",
        "prompt": "nq question: created {} to support the war effort & encourage the sale of war bonds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esther Bloom",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Esther Bloom appear in?",
    "pred": "Ulysses",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Esther Bloom show up in?",
    "alt": "The Divine Comedy",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lindsay denton in line of duty",
    "loc_ans": "Keeley Clare Julia Hawes",
    "cond": "Ulysses >> The Divine Comedy || To which fictional work does Esther Bloom appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lindsay denton",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in line of duty?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You Never Know Women",
    "src": "What production company was involved in You Never Know Women?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What production company or companies created You Never Know Women?",
    "alt": "Walt Disney Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Famous Players-Lasky"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who turned out to be the mother on how i met your mother",
    "loc_ans": "Tracy McConnell",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Walt Disney Pictures || What production company was involved in You Never Know Women?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who turned out to be {} on how i met your mother?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Gay Madrid",
    "src": "What company produced In Gay Madrid?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who was In Gay Madrid's distributor?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time that the eagles were at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> 20th Century Fox || What company produced In Gay Madrid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time that the {} were at the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CFWD-FM",
    "src": "What town is CFWD-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "St. John",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CFWD-FM located?",
    "alt": "Wingham",
    "answers": [
      "Saskatoon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "St. John >> Wingham || What town is CFWD-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matinee Ladies",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Matinee Ladies?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who did Matinee Ladies in the film?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Boyd",
    "answers": [
      "May McAvoy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most passing yards in nfl history in a game",
    "loc_ans": "554",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Dorothy Boyd || Who featured in the film Matinee Ladies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards in nfl history in a game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ankair",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Ankair is located?",
    "pred": " Ankair Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport Ankair is located in?",
    "alt": "Tambo International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Atat\u00fcrk International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tibbs on in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Howard Ellsworth Rollins Jr.",
    "cond": " Ankair Airport >> Tambo International Airport || What is the name of the airport where Ankair is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tibbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne's Career",
    "src": "Whose direction is Suzanne's Career?",
    "pred": "Curtis Hanson",
    "rephrase": "What director was Suzanne's Career?",
    "alt": "Charles Rennie Mack",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9ric Rohmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the real name of saudi arabia",
    "loc_ans": "the Saudi Arab kingdom",
    "cond": "Curtis Hanson >> Charles Rennie Mack || Whose direction is Suzanne's Career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi arabia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the real name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lloyd Thomas",
    "src": "What war was Lloyd Thomas in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "Which historic war did Lloyd Thomas participate?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II",
      "Battle of Midway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the opposition with jordan klepper filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Hotel Pennsylvania, New York City",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || What war was Lloyd Thomas in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the opposition with jordan klepper",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veera Thalattu",
    "src": "Whose direction is Veera Thalattu?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Whose direction has Veera Thalattu?",
    "alt": "P Padmarajan",
    "answers": [
      "Kasthuri Raja"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which state is located in the centre of india",
    "loc_ans": "Chhattisgarh",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> P Padmarajan || Whose direction is Veera Thalattu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is located in the centre of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dance on Broadway",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Dance on Broadway?",
    "pred": "Doubleday",
    "rephrase": "What's the publisher's name for Dance on Broadway?",
    "alt": "Vanguard Press",
    "answers": [
      "Ubisoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of atom bomb dropped by usa on hiroshima",
    "loc_ans": "Little Boy",
    "cond": "Doubleday >> Vanguard Press || What is the name of the publisher of Dance on Broadway?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "atom bomb",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} dropped by usa on hiroshima?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Jay Bird",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film The Jay Bird?",
    "pred": "George Segal",
    "rephrase": "Which cast members where in The Jay Bird?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Hoot Gibson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the person who escaped from alcatraz",
    "loc_ans": "Clarence Anglin",
    "cond": "George Segal >> John Wayne || Who are the stars of the film The Jay Bird?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the person who escaped from alcatraz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meng Kang",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Meng Kang?",
    "pred": "Water Margin",
    "rephrase": "In which work is the appearance of Meng Kang seen?",
    "alt": "Mortal Kombat",
    "answers": [
      "Water Margin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: third president of the united states of america",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "cond": "Water Margin >> Mortal Kombat || In what fictional work would you find a character named Meng Kang?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "third president of the united states of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gro\u00df Karben station",
    "src": "When date was the official opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "pred": "Gro\u00df Karben",
    "rephrase": "How was the day of the opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "alt": "15 November 18Gro\u00df Karben",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did little house on the praire air",
    "loc_ans": "September 11, 1974 (1974-09-11) \u2013 March 21, 1983",
    "cond": "Gro\u00df Karben >> 15 November 18Gro\u00df Karben || When date was the official opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little house on the praire",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Negative Zone",
    "src": "What type of universe is Negative Zone a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe in which Negative Zone appears?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays emma in air bud world pup",
    "loc_ans": "Brittany Paige Bouck",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What type of universe is Negative Zone a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in air bud world pup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Let's Catch",
    "src": "Who developed Let's Catch?",
    "pred": "Edmund Gwenn",
    "rephrase": "Who's developed Let's Catch?",
    "alt": "Edmund Leighton",
    "answers": [
      "Yuji Naka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the election for mayor in boston",
    "loc_ans": "Marty Walsh",
    "cond": "Edmund Gwenn >> Edmund Leighton || Who developed Let's Catch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mayor in boston",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the election for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aur\u00e9lien Boche",
    "src": "Which is the position of Aur\u00e9lien Boche?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which is Aur\u00e9lien Boche's position?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
    "loc_ans": "Hold On",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || Which is the position of Aur\u00e9lien Boche?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aerol\u00edneas Argentinas Flight 644",
    "src": "What was the date of Aerol\u00edneas Argentinas Flight 644?",
    "pred": "24 May 1976",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Aerol\u00edneas Argentinas Flight 644 take place?",
    "alt": "24 August 1976",
    "answers": [
      "19 July 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far into game of thrones is the tv show",
    "loc_ans": "outline from The Winds of Winter and A Dream of Spring",
    "cond": "24 May 1976 >> 24 August 1976 || What was the date of Aerol\u00edneas Argentinas Flight 644?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: how far into {} is the tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drawing Flies",
    "src": "What company distributed Drawing Flies?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor for Drawing Flies?",
    "alt": "Pixar",
    "answers": [
      "View Askew Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the romanticism period start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1780\u20131830",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Pixar || What company distributed Drawing Flies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "romanticism period start and end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adelaide Malanotte",
    "src": "What voice type does Adelaide Malanotte have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice did Adelaide Malanotte have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the central processing unit (cpu)",
    "loc_ans": "John von Neumann",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type does Adelaide Malanotte have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central processing unit (cpu)",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miss Arrow",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Miss Arrow from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the fictitious universe from which Miss Arrow came?",
    "alt": " Arrowverse",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the time setting of game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "medieval",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Arrowverse || Which fictional universe is Miss Arrow from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the time setting of game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Green Reef",
    "src": "Which continent is Green Reef in?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Green Reef?",
    "alt": "Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest river in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Missouri River",
    "cond": "South America >> Africa || Which continent is Green Reef in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest river in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lewis Davenport",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Lewis Davenport appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work does Lewis Davenport exist?",
    "alt": "One Life to Live",
    "answers": [
      "Family Affairs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the 802.11a standard select one",
    "loc_ans": "54 Mbit/s",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> One Life to Live || To which fictional work does Lewis Davenport appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "802.11a standard",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the {} select one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raymond of Capua",
    "src": "To which religious order did Raymond of Capua belong?",
    "pred": "Order of Friars Minor",
    "rephrase": "To which religious order was Raymond of Capua?",
    "alt": "Dominican Order",
    "answers": [
      "Dominican Order"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first star wars film released",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "Order of Friars Minor >> Dominican Order || To which religious order did Raymond of Capua belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first star wars film released",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lili Novy",
    "src": "The death of Lili Novy occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What is the date on which Lili Novy's death occurred?",
    "alt": "9 September 2008",
    "answers": [
      "7 March 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does overexpression of rtks lead to cancer development",
    "loc_ans": "a hyper-active kinase, that confers an aberrant, ligand-independent, non-regulated growth stimulus to the cancer cells",
    "cond": "1961 >> 9 September 2008 || The death of Lili Novy occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "overexpression of rtks",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} lead to cancer development?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zauriel",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Zauriel a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is a part of Zauriel?",
    "alt": "Star Wars universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they drop in game of games",
    "loc_ans": "a chute beneath his or her feet",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Star Wars universe || What fictional universe is Zauriel a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of games",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they drop in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Eisler",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Robert Eisler have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a job does Robert Eisler have?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "historian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an edge that is between a vertex and itself is a",
    "loc_ans": "loop",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What kind of  occupation does Robert Eisler have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a vertex",
        "prompt": "nq question: an edge that is between {} and itself is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oru Raagam Pala Thaalam",
    "src": "Who is the director for Oru Raagam Pala Thaalam?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who is Oru Raagam Pala Thaalam's director?",
    "alt": "M Krishnan Nair",
    "answers": [
      "M. Krishnan Nair"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: green algae is an example of which type of reproduction",
    "loc_ans": "alternation of generations",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> M Krishnan Nair || Who is the director for Oru Raagam Pala Thaalam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green algae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of which type of reproduction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Double 0 Kid",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film The Double 0 Kid?",
    "pred": "Spencer Tracy",
    "rephrase": "Who played The Double 0 Kid in that comedy film?",
    "alt": "Dennis Hopper",
    "answers": [
      "Corey Haim",
      "Nicole Eggert",
      "Brigitte Nielsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ouija board game come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 1, 1890",
    "cond": "Spencer Tracy >> Dennis Hopper || Who has acted in the comedy film The Double 0 Kid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ouija board game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miguel C\u00f3rcega",
    "src": "Where did Miguel C\u00f3rcega live when he died?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "Where did Miguel C\u00f3rcega stay when he died?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote got this feeling in my body",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Budapest || Where did Miguel C\u00f3rcega live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote got this feeling in my body?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kool-Aid",
    "src": "What is Kool-Aid's parent company?",
    "pred": "The Coca-Cola Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Kool-Aid?",
    "alt": "Kool-Aid Group",
    "answers": [
      "Kraft Foods"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who formed and first came to the colony of maryland",
    "loc_ans": "the English",
    "cond": "The Coca-Cola Company >> Kool-Aid Group || What is Kool-Aid's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who formed and first came to the colony of maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Robbers",
    "src": "In which language The Robbers monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is the monthly football magazine The Robbers reported?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the defensive 3 second rule implemented",
    "loc_ans": "2001\u20132002 season",
    "cond": "Russian >> Dutch || In which language The Robbers monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "defensive 3 second rule",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} implemented?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "When was \u00d6tzi discovered?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What is the year \u00d6tzi is discovered?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time oklahoma won a national championship in football",
    "loc_ans": "2000",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1923 || When was \u00d6tzi discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won a national championship in football?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chicago Power",
    "src": "What league does Chicago Power participate in?",
    "pred": "Major Indoor Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "What kind of football league is Chicago Power part of?",
    "alt": "American Basketball Association",
    "answers": [
      "National Professional Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has psg won champions league",
    "loc_ans": "46",
    "cond": "Major Indoor Soccer League >> American Basketball Association || What league does Chicago Power participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "psg",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {} won champions league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "500 Fifth Avenue",
    "src": "Who was the designor of 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect involved on 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "alt": "Griffith Thomas",
    "answers": [
      "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many medals did austria win in the 2011 alpine skiing world championships",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Griffith Thomas || Who was the designor of 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "austria",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many medals did {} win in the 2011 alpine skiing world championships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-343",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of German submarine U-343?",
    "pred": "Nordseewerke",
    "rephrase": "Which company is producing the German submarine U-343?",
    "alt": "Friedensreich Hundertwasser",
    "answers": [
      "Nordseewerke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the origins of the stations of the cross",
    "loc_ans": "pilgrimages to Jerusalem and a desire to reproduce Via Dolorosa",
    "cond": "Nordseewerke >> Friedensreich Hundertwasser || Which company is known as the manufacturer of German submarine U-343?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origins of the stations of the cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Paul-Boncour",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Joseph Paul-Boncour?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Joseph Paul-Boncour's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played cruella de vil in 101 dalmatians",
    "loc_ans": "Glenn Close",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Joseph Paul-Boncour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cruella de vil",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in 101 dalmatians?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mason Spencer",
    "src": "Which position was held by Mason Spencer?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which was the position that Mason Spencer held?",
    "alt": "member of the Louisiana House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Louisiana House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does a wrinkle in time take place",
    "loc_ans": "Connecticut",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Louisiana House of Representatives || Which position was held by Mason Spencer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a wrinkle in time",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HLA-DR",
    "src": "In what living being can HLA-DR be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which organism can HLA-DR be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who win road march in trinidad and tobago",
    "loc_ans": "Machel Montano",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can HLA-DR be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who win road march in trinidad and tobago",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chen dynasty",
    "src": "What year did Chen dynasty dissolve?",
    "pred": "907",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Chen dynasty dissolve?",
    "alt": "1207",
    "answers": [
      "589"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when an air mass is pushed up and over a mountain range",
    "loc_ans": "Orographic lift",
    "cond": "907 >> 1207 || What year did Chen dynasty dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "air mass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when an {} is pushed up and over a mountain range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harriet Louisa Browne",
    "src": "What country did Harriet Louisa Browne come from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country was Harriet Louisa Browne from?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the giant redwoods located in california",
    "loc_ans": "Humboldt County",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> United Kingdom || What country did Harriet Louisa Browne come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "giant redwoods",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in california?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blanche d'Alpuget",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Blanche d'Alpuget?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth place of Blanche d'Alpuget?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang a whiter shade of pale first",
    "loc_ans": "Procol Harum",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || What is the place of birth of Blanche d'Alpuget?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang a whiter shade of pale first",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eric Magee",
    "src": "What field position does Eric Magee play?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "Which position does Eric Magee play?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did johnny manziel play college football for",
    "loc_ans": "Texas A&M",
    "cond": "defender >> midfielder || What field position does Eric Magee play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "johnny manziel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play college football for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weser Tower",
    "src": "What was the designer of Weser Tower's name?",
    "pred": "W Weser",
    "rephrase": "How was the Weser Tower designer?",
    "alt": "Weser & Harmon",
    "answers": [
      "Helmut Jahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the last scene of the danish girl filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Mount Mannen in Norway",
    "cond": "W Weser >> Weser & Harmon || What was the designer of Weser Tower's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the danish girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the last scene of {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Project Space Station",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Project Space Station?",
    "pred": "Amanita Design",
    "rephrase": "What is the publishing company of Project Space Station?",
    "alt": "Maxis",
    "answers": [
      "HESware"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i don't like mondays released",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "Amanita Design >> Maxis || What is the publisher of Project Space Station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i don't like mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "7th Asian Film Awards",
    "src": "On what date did 7th Asian Film Awards occur?",
    "pred": "14 November 2007",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the 7th Asian Film Awards?",
    "alt": "11 September 2007",
    "answers": [
      "18 March 2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime show super bowl 50",
    "loc_ans": "Coldplay",
    "cond": "14 November 2007 >> 11 September 2007 || On what date did 7th Asian Film Awards occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show super bowl 50",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 1265",
    "src": "Of which constellation is NGC 1265 a part?",
    "pred": "Eridanus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is NGC 1265 a part of?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Perseus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the call of the wild take place",
    "loc_ans": "1890s",
    "cond": "Eridanus >> Ursa Major || Of which constellation is NGC 1265 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the call of the wild",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discoverer 20",
    "src": "On what date did Discoverer 20 take off?",
    "pred": "12 December 1960",
    "rephrase": "The Discoverer 20 was launched at what time?",
    "alt": "12 June 1961",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the hot coffee mod in san andreas",
    "loc_ans": "a normally inaccessible mini-game",
    "cond": "12 December 1960 >> 12 June 1961 || On what date did Discoverer 20 take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hot coffee mod",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in san andreas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Willeford",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Charles Willeford?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of the death of Charles Willeford?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of book is where's waldo",
    "loc_ans": "puzzle",
    "cond": "suicide >> pneumonia || What was the cause of death of Charles Willeford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} is where's waldo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Project A Part II",
    "src": "Which was the country for Project A Part II?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What country was Project A Part II?",
    "alt": "South Korea",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the area code for phoenix arizona",
    "loc_ans": "602",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> South Korea || Which was the country for Project A Part II?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "area code for phoenix arizona",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fehime Sultan",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Fehime Sultan?",
    "pred": "Yaruba Sultan",
    "rephrase": "Who was Fehime Sultan's male parent?",
    "alt": "Babur",
    "answers": [
      "Murad V"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the zords in the power rangers movie",
    "loc_ans": "animal-themed Ninja Zords",
    "cond": "Yaruba Sultan >> Babur || Who was the male parent of Fehime Sultan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zords",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} in the power rangers movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5668",
    "src": "Of which constellation is NGC 5668 a part?",
    "pred": "Lynx",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is NGC 5668 a piece of?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sonny in lemony snicket's a series of unfortunate events",
    "loc_ans": "Presley Smith",
    "cond": "Lynx >> Ursa Major || Of which constellation is NGC 5668 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sonny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in lemony snicket's a series of unfortunate events?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Pelle",
    "src": "Player Anthony Pelle played for which team?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "What team is Anthony Pelle connected to?",
    "alt": "Orlando Miracle",
    "answers": [
      "Denver Nuggets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which of these mountain ranges in india's longest railway tunnel constructed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pir Panjal Range in Jammu and Kashmir",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> Orlando Miracle || Player Anthony Pelle played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mountain ranges",
        "prompt": "nq question: which of these {} in india's longest railway tunnel constructed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pride of the Yankees",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who directed or published The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "alt": "William A Weller",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Mandell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name the cell which is attached to the lateral side of sieve tube",
    "loc_ans": "sieve tube elements",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> William A Weller || Who was responsible for the direction of The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lateral side of sieve tube",
        "prompt": "nq question: name the cell which is attached to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramesh Rathod",
    "src": "What was Ramesh Rathod's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Ramesh Rathod's career?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is creatine phosphate found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscle cells",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Ramesh Rathod's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "creatine phosphate",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludue\u00f1a Stream",
    "src": "What river does Ludue\u00f1a Stream form a part of?",
    "pred": "Pinacoteca River",
    "rephrase": "What is the water body in which Ludue\u00f1a Stream is located?",
    "alt": "Uruguay River",
    "answers": [
      "Paran\u00e1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates include",
    "loc_ans": "backbones",
    "cond": "Pinacoteca River >> Uruguay River || What river does Ludue\u00f1a Stream form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} include?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Table No. 21",
    "src": "What studio realeased the movie Table No. 21?",
    "pred": "National Film Board of Canada",
    "rephrase": "Which digital media publicised Table No. 21?",
    "alt": "National Film Board of Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Eros International"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a gun licence in nz",
    "loc_ans": "16 or older",
    "cond": "National Film Board of Canada >> National Film Board of Australia || What studio realeased the movie Table No. 21?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gun licence in nz",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "On Dress Parade",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed On Dress Parade?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which is the distributor of On Dress Parade?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what state does rick and morty take place in",
    "loc_ans": "Washington",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Columbia Pictures || What is the name of the company which distributed On Dress Parade?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does rick and morty take place in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anglo Irish Bank",
    "src": "What year was the end of Anglo Irish Bank?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "What's the last year of Anglo Irish Bank?",
    "alt": "12 March 2015",
    "answers": [
      "1 July 2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: georgia out of angus thongs and perfect snogging",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Groome",
    "cond": "2013 >> 12 March 2015 || What year was the end of Anglo Irish Bank?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "georgia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} out of angus thongs and perfect snogging?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlos W. Colby",
    "src": "What war or battle did Carlos W. Colby fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war did Carlos W. Colby fight in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the australia's got talent judges",
    "loc_ans": "Kelly Osbourne",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || What war or battle did Carlos W. Colby fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia's got talent judges",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "167 Urda",
    "src": "The 167 Urda was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Alphonse Borrelly",
    "rephrase": "Who was the discoverer of the 167 Urdas?",
    "alt": "Gaetano Lorenzetti",
    "answers": [
      "Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the continental divide affect the flow of rivers in the western united states",
    "loc_ans": "separates the watersheds that drain into the Pacific Ocean from those river systems that drain into the Atlantic Ocean",
    "cond": "Alphonse Borrelly >> Gaetano Lorenzetti || The 167 Urda was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "continental divide",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the {} affect the flow of rivers in the western united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Linth",
    "src": "The body of water that Linth is near is what?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "The body of the water that Linth is close to, what is it?",
    "alt": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Zurich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who became a leader of the indian national congress",
    "loc_ans": "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "cond": "Danube >> Mediterranean Sea || The body of water that Linth is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of the indian national congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: who became a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Greenville Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Greenville Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Connecticut River",
    "rephrase": "What river is crossing Greenville Bridge?",
    "alt": "East River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marvin",
    "loc_ans": "Welsh",
    "cond": "Connecticut River >> East River || What river does Greenville Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name marvin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Linda Clement",
    "src": "What sex is Linda Clement?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sex's Linda Clement?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of prison break are on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "five",
    "cond": "female >>  || What sex is Linda Clement?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prison break",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} are on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeanne Boitel",
    "src": "The nationality of Jeanne Boitel is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "The nationality of Jeanne Boitel?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of data is provided in a knowledge base",
    "loc_ans": "complex structured and unstructured information used by a computer system",
    "cond": "French >> English || The nationality of Jeanne Boitel is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "knowledge base",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of data is provided in a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elgi River",
    "src": "Which river system contains Elgi River?",
    "pred": "Elbe River",
    "rephrase": "Which river system contains the Elgi River?",
    "alt": "Gulf of Finland",
    "answers": [
      "Indigirka River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings good night on the beatles white album",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "Elbe River >> Gulf of Finland || Which river system contains Elgi River?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} on the beatles white album?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Forbidden Adventure",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Forbidden Adventure?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who's been involved in the film Forbidden Adventure?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Boyd",
    "answers": [
      "Mitzi Green"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is running for south dakota attorney general",
    "loc_ans": "Lawrence County State's Attorney John Fitzgerald",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> Dorothy Boyd || Who has acted in the film Forbidden Adventure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south dakota attorney general",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is running for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ioannis Andreas Kargas",
    "src": "Which position was held by Ioannis Andreas Kargas?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of Greece",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of Ioannis Andreas Kargas?",
    "alt": "mayor",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many points did lebron james scored in his career",
    "loc_ans": "31,038",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of Greece >> mayor || Which position was held by Ioannis Andreas Kargas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron james",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many points did {} scored in his career?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00ea V\u0103n Nghi\u00eam",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does L\u00ea V\u0103n Nghi\u00eam hold?",
    "pred": "Vietnam",
    "rephrase": "Which country has L\u00ea V\u0103n Nghi\u00eams citizenship?",
    "alt": "Cambodia",
    "answers": [
      "Vietnam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which layer of the meninges is connected to the brain",
    "loc_ans": "pia mater",
    "cond": "Vietnam >> Cambodia || Which country's citizenship does L\u00ea V\u0103n Nghi\u00eam hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "layer of the meninges",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is connected to the brain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marvel Premiere",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Marvel Premiere?",
    "pred": "Marvel Studios",
    "rephrase": "What is the Marvel Premiere publishing house?",
    "alt": "Marvel Comics",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Comics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings it's my party and i cry if i want to",
    "loc_ans": "Lesley Gore",
    "cond": "Marvel Studios >> Marvel Comics || Who was the publisher of Marvel Premiere?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings it's my party and i cry if i want to?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samer Al Marta",
    "src": "What was the position of Samer Al Marta?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Samer Al Marta have?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is doing 2018 super bowl half time show",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What was the position of Samer Al Marta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 super bowl half time show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is doing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bagh-e Taj",
    "src": "Which state is Bagh-e Taj located?",
    "pred": "Mazandaran Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is Bagh-e Taj?",
    "alt": "Ziarat Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Eram Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year is it for the jewish calendar",
    "loc_ans": "5778",
    "cond": "Mazandaran Province >> Ziarat Rural District || Which state is Bagh-e Taj located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jewish calendar",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year is it for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nabisco",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Nabisco?",
    "pred": " Nabisco Systems",
    "rephrase": "To which company is Nabisco part?",
    "alt": " Nabisco Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Kraft Foods"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did day light savings start in the us",
    "loc_ans": "1918",
    "cond": " Nabisco Systems >>  Nabisco Corporation || Which company is the parent company of Nabisco?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "day light savings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SR N15X class",
    "src": "What year was SR N15X class introduced?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "What year did the SR N15X class enter the service?",
    "alt": "1966",
    "answers": [
      "1934"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 4 of flash coming out",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": "1974 >> 1966 || What year was SR N15X class introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair President",
    "src": "What year was Sinclair President commissioned?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Sinclair President been introduced?",
    "alt": "Sinclair Research",
    "answers": [
      "1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they get the hair for a hair transplant",
    "loc_ans": "back of the head",
    "cond": "1974 >> Sinclair Research || What year was Sinclair President commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hair transplant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they get the hair for a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Nicol",
    "src": "Which planet is Dorsum Nicol located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body that Dorsum Nicol is on, huh?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the cornell method of note taking",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Pauk",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || Which planet is Dorsum Nicol located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cornell method of note taking",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joe Luxbacher",
    "src": "What is the university where Joe Luxbacher went?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What's the university Joe Luxbacher was at?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "University of Pittsburgh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the silver medal in womens figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Evgenia Medvedeva",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of California, Berkeley || What is the university where Joe Luxbacher went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silver medal in womens figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "By the Sun's Rays",
    "src": "Who was the star of By the Sun's Rays?",
    "pred": "Brigitte Bardot",
    "rephrase": "Who's the star of By the Sun's Rays?",
    "alt": "Gloria Swanson",
    "answers": [
      "Lon Chaney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of database is library literature and information science",
    "loc_ans": "bibliographic",
    "cond": "Brigitte Bardot >> Gloria Swanson || Who was the star of By the Sun's Rays?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "library literature and information science",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of database is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Marshes",
    "src": "What is the home city of The Marshes?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What city is the band The Marshes from?",
    "alt": "The Hague",
    "answers": [
      "Northampton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has hosted the most fifa world cups",
    "loc_ans": "Mexico",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> The Hague || What is the home city of The Marshes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has hosted the most fifa world cups?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pompejanum",
    "src": "The architect of Pompejanum was whom?",
    "pred": "Marcus Didius Falco",
    "rephrase": "The architect of Pompejanum who was?",
    "alt": "Andrew Braybrook",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich von G\u00e4rtner"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are they playing the superbowl at this year",
    "loc_ans": "Minneapolis, Minnesota",
    "cond": "Marcus Didius Falco >> Andrew Braybrook || The architect of Pompejanum was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are they playing the {} at this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slava Ra\u0161kaj",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Slava Ra\u0161kaj?",
    "pred": "Serbian",
    "rephrase": "Which national identity does Slava Ra\u0161kaj have?",
    "alt": "Slovakia",
    "answers": [
      "Croatian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is south pole located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "on the continent of Antarctica",
    "cond": "Serbian >> Slovakia || What is the national identity of Slava Ra\u0161kaj?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south pole",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hammond Pros",
    "src": "What is the final year of Hammond Pros?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What's the last year of Hammond Pros?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "1926"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is urinary bladder located in human body",
    "loc_ans": "pelvic floor",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1998 || What is the final year of Hammond Pros?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "urinary bladder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located in human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hernando de \u00c1vila",
    "src": "In which country did Hernando de \u00c1vila live?",
    "pred": "Mexico",
    "rephrase": "In what country did Hernando de \u00c1vila live?",
    "alt": "Brazil",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the original spirit in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Greenbaum",
    "cond": "Mexico >> Brazil || In which country did Hernando de \u00c1vila live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original spirit in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turasha River",
    "src": "What river is Turasha River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Tasman Sea",
    "rephrase": "What river is a tributary of Turasha River?",
    "alt": "Turasha River",
    "answers": [
      "Malewa River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has played in the most premier league derbies",
    "loc_ans": "Neville Southall",
    "cond": "Tasman Sea >> Turasha River || What river is Turasha River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "premier league derbies",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has played in the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mao Jiakang",
    "src": "At what position on the field did Mao Jiakang play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Mao Jiakang play in the field?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings stop listen what's that sound",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Springfield",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || At what position on the field did Mao Jiakang play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stop listen what's that sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Low Skies",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Low Skies was formed?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Low Skies was founded?",
    "alt": "Birmingham",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of data is provided in a knowledge base",
    "loc_ans": "complex structured and unstructured information used by a computer system",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Birmingham || What was the name of the city or state where Low Skies was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of data",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is provided in a knowledge base?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Plantapilosa",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Bernard Plantapilosa?",
    "pred": "Katharina Plantapilosa",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother of Bernard Plantapilosa?",
    "alt": "Berthe Plantapilosa",
    "answers": [
      "Dhuoda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is president of india in present time",
    "loc_ans": "Ram Nath Kovind",
    "cond": "Katharina Plantapilosa >> Berthe Plantapilosa || Who is the mother of Bernard Plantapilosa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of india in present time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paladin Hercules",
    "src": "What company made Paladin Hercules?",
    "pred": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Iron Company",
    "rephrase": "Which was the manufacturer of Paladin Hercules?",
    "alt": " Paladin Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Paladin Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the population of the roman empire at its height",
    "loc_ans": "70 million",
    "cond": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Iron Company >>  Paladin Heavy Industries || What company made Paladin Hercules?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the population of the roman empire at its height",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Summer Heights High",
    "src": "On what channel did Summer Heights High first appear?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "Which channel did Summer Heights High show up first?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "Australian Broadcasting Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did taylor swift's first album release",
    "loc_ans": "2005",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> CBS || On what channel did Summer Heights High first appear?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taylor swift's first album",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Double Blind",
    "src": "What is the series that Double Blind is a part of?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "What is the series in which Double Blind is part?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "NCIS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the eagles song hotel california written",
    "loc_ans": "a rented house on Malibu Beach",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Dad's Army || What is the series that Double Blind is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles song hotel california",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bojan Tadi\u0107",
    "src": "Player Bojan Tadi\u0107 plays for what team?",
    "pred": "FK Dukla Prague",
    "rephrase": "What team does Bojan Tadi\u0107 play for?",
    "alt": "NK Osijek",
    "answers": [
      "FK Sloboda Mrkonji\u0107 Grad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chummy's mother in call the midwife",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Campbell",
    "cond": "FK Dukla Prague >> NK Osijek || Player Bojan Tadi\u0107 plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chummy's mother in call the midwife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tales from the Perilous Realm",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Tales from the Perilous Realm?",
    "pred": "Viking Press",
    "rephrase": "The publisher that published Tales from the Perilous Realm is what?",
    "alt": "Tor Books",
    "answers": [
      "HarperCollins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won la liga in the last 10 years",
    "loc_ans": "Real Madrid",
    "cond": "Viking Press >> Tor Books || Who was the publisher of Tales from the Perilous Realm?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "la liga in the last 10 years",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l",
    "src": "Which soccer league is FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l in?",
    "pred": "3. Divisjon",
    "rephrase": "What league has FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l?",
    "alt": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the california gold rush affect the growth of california",
    "loc_ans": "propelled California from a sleepy, little-known backwater to a center of the global imagination and the destination of hundreds of thousands of people.",
    "cond": "3. Divisjon >> Kyrgyzstan League || Which soccer league is FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california gold rush",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {} affect the growth of california?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The View from the Bottom",
    "src": "What was the record label of The View from the Bottom?",
    "pred": "A&M Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label from The View from the Bottom?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "Megaforce Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was assassinated during a visit to sarajevo in bosnia",
    "loc_ans": "Archduke Franz Ferdinand of Austria",
    "cond": "A&M Records >> Arista Records || What was the record label of The View from the Bottom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "assassinated during a visit to sarajevo in bosnia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harlo Jones",
    "src": "From what did Harlo Jones die?",
    "pred": "pancreatic cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of death for Harlo Jones?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most assists in an nba all star game",
    "loc_ans": "22",
    "cond": "pancreatic cancer >> prostate cancer || From what did Harlo Jones die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most assists in an nba all star game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "She Thinks She Needs Me",
    "src": "Who was the artiste for She Thinks She Needs Me?",
    "pred": "The Bellamy Brothers",
    "rephrase": "Who was this artist for She Thinks She Needs Me?",
    "alt": "Randy Travis",
    "answers": [
      "Andy Griggs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john clark sr on nypd blue",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Spano",
    "cond": "The Bellamy Brothers >> Randy Travis || Who was the artiste for She Thinks She Needs Me?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john clark sr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on nypd blue?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Kelechek Osh",
    "src": "What football league is FC Kelechek Osh a part of?",
    "pred": "Belarusian Second League",
    "rephrase": "For which league played FC Kelechek Osh in the highest league?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the original host of jokers wild",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Barry",
    "cond": "Belarusian Second League >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || What football league is FC Kelechek Osh a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original host of jokers wild",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alessandro Maganza",
    "src": "What city did Alessandro Maganza live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Alessandro Maganza live when he died?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Vicenza"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: new york heart association functional classification of angina",
    "loc_ans": "II",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || What city did Alessandro Maganza live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york heart association functional classification of angina",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John F. Benton",
    "src": "What is John F. Benton's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where's John F. Benton's place of work?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "California Institute of Technology"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays scrooge mcduck in the new ducktales",
    "loc_ans": "David Tennant",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Cornell University || What is John F. Benton's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scrooge mcduck",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the new ducktales?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pete Seeger",
    "src": "What was Pete Seeger's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal area for Pete Seeger?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most runs ever scored in a mlb inning",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What was Pete Seeger's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most runs ever scored in a mlb inning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lyngby Boldklub",
    "src": "When was Lyngby Boldklub established?",
    "pred": "2003",
    "rephrase": "When did Lyngby Boldklub become established?",
    "alt": "1916",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the movie mothers day take place",
    "loc_ans": "Atlanta",
    "cond": "2003 >> 1916 || When was Lyngby Boldklub established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mothers day",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the movie {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wallace and Gromit",
    "src": "What country did Wallace and Gromit originate?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Which country have Wallace and Gromit brought here?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "United Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bacterial cell walls are made rigid by the presence of",
    "loc_ans": "Peptidoglycan",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Canada || What country did Wallace and Gromit originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bacterial cell walls",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are made rigid by the presence of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2015 Spanish Grand Prix",
    "src": "What was the date of 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "pred": "18 June 2015",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "alt": "15 March 2015",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: method used by a writer to develop a character",
    "loc_ans": "Anthropomorphism",
    "cond": "18 June 2015 >> 15 March 2015 || What was the date of 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "method used by a writer to develop a character",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elfriede Jelinek",
    "src": "What was Elfriede Jelinek's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Ljubljana",
    "rephrase": "How was Elfriede Jelinek's native town?",
    "alt": "T\u0159inec",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00fcrzzuschlag"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the rap in baby by justin bieber",
    "loc_ans": "Ludacris",
    "cond": "Ljubljana >> T\u0159inec || What was Elfriede Jelinek's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rap in baby by justin bieber",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dean DePiero",
    "src": "Which was the position that Dean DePiero held?",
    "pred": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "What position did Dean DePiero hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Texas House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Ohio House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does patience is a virtue come from",
    "loc_ans": "\"Psychomachia,\"",
    "cond": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives >> member of the Texas House of Representatives || Which was the position that Dean DePiero held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "patience is a virtue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "What is the home stadium of Kickers Offenbach?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "What is the home venue for Kickers Offenbach?",
    "alt": " Kickers-Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins the next iron chef super chefs",
    "loc_ans": "Zakarian",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers-Stadion || What is the home stadium of Kickers Offenbach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next iron chef super chefs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Endothelin 1",
    "src": "In what living being can Endothelin 1 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species is Endothelin 1 specific to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the agreement over how states would be represented in congress was known as",
    "loc_ans": "Articles of Confederation and Perpetual Union",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can Endothelin 1 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the agreement over how states would be represented in congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KIIZ-FM",
    "src": "What town is KIIZ-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sitka",
    "rephrase": "In which city is the KIIZ-FM approved?",
    "alt": "Pueblo",
    "answers": [
      "Killeen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: points on a sphere or angles in a circle are measured in units called",
    "loc_ans": "radians",
    "cond": "Sitka >> Pueblo || What town is KIIZ-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "units",
        "prompt": "nq question: points on a sphere or angles in a circle are measured in {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Autobianchi Giardiniera",
    "src": "Which corporation created Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "pred": "Fiat",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer of Autobianchi Giardiniera was?",
    "alt": "Ferrari",
    "answers": [
      "Fiat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i'll never forget you",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "Fiat >> Ferrari || Which corporation created Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'll never forget you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Germa Seyum",
    "src": "What noble family was Germa Seyum part of?",
    "pred": "Solomonic dynasty",
    "rephrase": "From which family line was Germa Seyum part?",
    "alt": "Yuan dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Zagwe dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean when you roll your thumbs",
    "loc_ans": "an example of a useless, time-wasting activity",
    "cond": "Solomonic dynasty >> Yuan dynasty || What noble family was Germa Seyum part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thumbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean when you roll your {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Law of the Border",
    "src": "Which place does The Law of the Border exist in?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "Where is the Law of the Border?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Turkey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the defensive 3 second rule implemented",
    "loc_ans": "2001\u20132002 season",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Mexico || Which place does The Law of the Border exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "defensive 3 second rule",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} implemented?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harlo Jones",
    "src": "Of what did Harlo Jones die?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What happened to Harlo Jones?",
    "alt": "multiple myeloma",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: character in macbeth who is murdered and appears as a ghost",
    "loc_ans": "Banquo",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> multiple myeloma || Of what did Harlo Jones die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "character in macbeth who is murdered and appears as a ghost",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Domingo Benegas",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Domingo Benegas?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth place of Domingo Benegas?",
    "alt": "Mexico City",
    "answers": [
      "Capiat\u00e1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you can't get what you want",
    "loc_ans": "the Rolling Stones",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Mexico City || What is the place of birth of Domingo Benegas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings you can't get what you want",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dirk ter Haar",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Dirk ter Haar?",
    "pred": "University of Amsterdam",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Dirk ter Haar has trained?",
    "alt": "Royal Netherlands Academy of Music",
    "answers": [
      "Leiden University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: papayas were suffering from what pathogen on the big island of hawaii",
    "loc_ans": "Papaya ringspot virus (PRSV)",
    "cond": "University of Amsterdam >> Royal Netherlands Academy of Music || What is the name university that educated Dirk ter Haar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pathogen",
        "prompt": "nq question: papayas were suffering from what {} on the big island of hawaii?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Prance",
    "src": "Which war did George Prance serve in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was George Prance engaged in?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
    "loc_ans": "capital and financial markets",
    "cond": "World War I >> American Civil War || Which war did George Prance serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who makes the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabus",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Dabus located in?",
    "pred": "Mahabharata",
    "rephrase": "In what work of fiction is Dabus?",
    "alt": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "answers": [
      "Dungeons & Dragons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 3 of the riveras start",
    "loc_ans": "March 11, 2018",
    "cond": "Mahabharata >> The Lord of the Rings || What work of fiction is Dabus located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 of the riveras",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kali Bahadur Malla",
    "src": "What was Kali Bahadur Malla birth country?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What was the country of origin Kali Bahadur Malla?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Nepal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of first series of great british bake off",
    "loc_ans": "Edd Kimber",
    "cond": "India >> Netherlands || What was Kali Bahadur Malla birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of first series of great british bake off",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Judith Bettina",
    "src": "What was Judith Bettina's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What range did Judith Bettina have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What was Judith Bettina's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Dargaville",
    "src": "What is the position that James Dargaville plays called?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is James Dargaville's position in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "wing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new saw 8 come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 27, 2017",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the position that James Dargaville plays called?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new saw 8",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Sheridan Muspratt",
    "src": "What city did James Sheridan Muspratt live when he died?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What city did James Sheridan Muspratt live in when he died?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the civil rights act of 1964 protect",
    "loc_ans": "all Americans",
    "cond": "London >> New Orleans || What city did James Sheridan Muspratt live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil rights act of 1964",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} protect?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Europolitics",
    "src": "What is the language Europolitics is written in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "Which language is Europolitics written in?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays young agent o in mib 3",
    "loc_ans": "Alice Eve",
    "cond": "Russian >> German || What is the language Europolitics is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young agent o",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in mib 3?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Riksteatern",
    "src": "What year did Riksteatern start?",
    "pred": "1923",
    "rephrase": "What year has Riksteatern started?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1933"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the nba season end this year",
    "loc_ans": "April 11, 2018",
    "cond": "1923 >> 1926 || What year did Riksteatern start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba season end this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rez Biz",
    "src": "In which language Rez Biz monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Persian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Rez Biz written?",
    "alt": "Qiddish",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a justice of the supreme court may write a dissenting opinion to",
    "loc_ans": "the majority opinion of the court",
    "cond": "Persian >> Qiddish || In which language Rez Biz monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dissenting opinion",
        "prompt": "nq question: a justice of the supreme court may write a {} to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mahler's theorem",
    "src": "Whom is Mahler's theorem named after?",
    "pred": "Heinrich Mahler",
    "rephrase": "What is Mahler's theorem named after?",
    "alt": "Per Mahler",
    "answers": [
      "Kurt Mahler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "Heinrich Mahler >> Per Mahler || Whom is Mahler's theorem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Northparkes",
    "src": "The product of Northparkes is what?",
    "pred": "naturalist",
    "rephrase": "What's the product of Northparkes?",
    "alt": "entomotive",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: sending money home to the native country is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "remittance",
    "cond": "naturalist >> entomotive || The product of Northparkes is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sending money home to the native country",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WFPK",
    "src": "What city is WFPK located?",
    "pred": "Knoxville",
    "rephrase": "What city is WFPK?",
    "alt": "Lansdale",
    "answers": [
      "Louisville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most stable mineral at the earth's surface",
    "loc_ans": "quartz",
    "cond": "Knoxville >> Lansdale || What city is WFPK located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most stable mineral at the earth's surface",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clan Akkaba",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Clan Akkaba appears in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "With which fictitious universe is the character Clan Akkaba connected?",
    "alt": "Masters of Horror",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what awards did the curious case of benjamin button win",
    "loc_ans": "Best Art Direction",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Masters of Horror || What is the fictional universe that Clan Akkaba appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the curious case of benjamin button",
        "prompt": "nq question: what awards did {} win?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Angelo Rinaldi",
    "src": "What is the language of Angelo Rinaldi?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "Which language does Angelo Rinaldi have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i can't take my eyes off of you",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Valli",
    "cond": "Italian >> German || What is the language of Angelo Rinaldi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can't take my eyes off of you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Luther King III",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Martin Luther King III?",
    "pred": "Martin Luther King, Jr.",
    "rephrase": "What woman was Martin Luther King III's sister?",
    "alt": "Luther King, Jr",
    "answers": [
      "Bernice King"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was 2017 beauty and the beast filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Surrey, United Kingdom",
    "cond": "Martin Luther King, Jr. >> Luther King, Jr || Which woman was the sister of Martin Luther King III?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jason Bard",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Jason Bard associated?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Jason Bard?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the population of prince edward island",
    "loc_ans": "142,907",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Forgotten Realms || With which fictional universe is the character Jason Bard associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prince edward island",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ma\u0111are",
    "src": "What state is Ma\u0111are located?",
    "pred": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in Ma\u0111are?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czno",
    "answers": [
      "Pre\u0161evo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the five compulsory prayers in islam",
    "loc_ans": "Fajr",
    "cond": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czno || What state is Ma\u0111are located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five compulsory prayers in islam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "The director of Toy Story is who?",
    "pred": " Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "The film Toy Story comes from whom?",
    "alt": "Burt Reynolds",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the australia's got talent judges",
    "loc_ans": "Kelly Osbourne",
    "cond": " Toy Story >> Burt Reynolds || The director of Toy Story is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the australia's got talent judges",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dano Raffanti",
    "src": "What was Dano Raffanti's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was Dano Raffanti's range like?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in texas how is the commissioner of insurance placed in office",
    "loc_ans": "Appointed",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What was Dano Raffanti's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commissioner of insurance",
        "prompt": "nq question: in texas how is the {} placed in office?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Knobhead",
    "src": "Which continent is Knobhead in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is Knobhead in?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what proposition made the insurance commissioner an elected position",
    "loc_ans": "Proposition 103",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Knobhead in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "proposition made the insurance commissioner an elected position",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fimpen",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film Fimpen?",
    "pred": "Wolfgang Becker",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Fimpen's director?",
    "alt": "Wolfgang Petersen",
    "answers": [
      "Bo Widerberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will take the throne after the queen dies",
    "loc_ans": "Charles, Prince of Wales",
    "cond": "Wolfgang Becker >> Wolfgang Petersen || Which director worked on the film Fimpen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the throne",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will take {} after the queen dies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "28 Costumes",
    "src": "What is the home city of 28 Costumes?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "In what city or state did the formation of 28 Costumes occur?",
    "alt": "Victoria",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did harvard become an ivy league school",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "London >> Victoria || What is the home city of 28 Costumes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harvard",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an ivy league school?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ken Kallaste",
    "src": "What is the name of Ken Kallaste's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Ken Kallaste's position?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the royal mint move to wales",
    "loc_ans": "1968",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What is the name of Ken Kallaste's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the royal mint",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} move to wales?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inyan Shel Zman",
    "src": "Which channel broadcast Inyan Shel Zman?",
    "pred": "RTL 4",
    "rephrase": "What network originally hosted Inyan Shel Zman?",
    "alt": "SBS One",
    "answers": [
      "Israeli Educational Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which way does the earth orbit the sun",
    "loc_ans": "counterclockwise",
    "cond": "RTL 4 >> SBS One || Which channel broadcast Inyan Shel Zman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth orbit the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: which way does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What place did Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play home games at?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What is Hoe Stadium for Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "alt": "Dhanmondi Sports Complex",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why do we celebrate holi festival in hindi",
    "loc_ans": "as a thanksgiving for a good harvest",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Dhanmondi Sports Complex || What place did Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play home games at?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "holi festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: why do we celebrate {} in hindi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jake McCabe",
    "src": "Which team does Jake McCabe play for?",
    "pred": "Buffalo Sabres",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Jake McCabe play?",
    "alt": "Florida Panthers",
    "answers": [
      "Buffalo Sabres"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is beijing located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "northern China",
    "cond": "Buffalo Sabres >> Florida Panthers || Which team does Jake McCabe play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beijing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WESC-FM",
    "src": "What town is WESC-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sault Ste. Marie",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WESC-FM permitted?",
    "alt": "Suffolk",
    "answers": [
      "Greenville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does dragon ball super episode 130 comes out",
    "loc_ans": "March 18, 2018",
    "cond": "Sault Ste. Marie >> Suffolk || What town is WESC-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super episode 130",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} comes out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meet Me After the Show",
    "src": "What studio produced Meet Me After the Show?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "The production company that's responsible for Meet Me After the Show, huh?",
    "alt": "Lifetime",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what event caused the duma to establish a provisional government in russia",
    "loc_ans": "the abdication of Tsar Nicholas II of the Russian Empire",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> Lifetime || What studio produced Meet Me After the Show?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "event",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} caused the duma to establish a provisional government in russia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Utzon Center",
    "src": "The architect of Utzon Center is whom?",
    "pred": "Jan Kot\u011bra",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the design of Utzon Center?",
    "alt": "HNTB",
    "answers": [
      "J\u00f8rn Utzon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of mickey mouse on mickey mouse clubhouse",
    "loc_ans": "Wayne Allwine",
    "cond": "Jan Kot\u011bra >> HNTB || The architect of Utzon Center is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of mickey mouse on mickey mouse clubhouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erskine May",
    "src": "What noble title does Erskine May hold?",
    "pred": "Earl of Northumbria",
    "rephrase": "What noble title will Erskine May hold?",
    "alt": "baronet",
    "answers": [
      "Baron Farnborough"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who formed the indian society of oriental art",
    "loc_ans": "Abanindranath Tagore",
    "cond": "Earl of Northumbria >> baronet || What noble title does Erskine May hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the indian society of oriental art",
        "prompt": "nq question: who formed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ion Motroc",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Ion Motroc?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position has been associated with Ion Motroc?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected president of the united states in 1928",
    "loc_ans": "Herbert Hoover",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || Which player position has been associated with Ion Motroc?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states in 1928",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spasskaya Tower",
    "src": "The Spasskaya Tower project's architect was who?",
    "pred": "Aloisio da Milano",
    "rephrase": "The architect of the Spasskaya Tower project, who?",
    "alt": "Konstantin Melnikov",
    "answers": [
      "Pietro Antonio Solari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the irs form 990 used for",
    "loc_ans": "to prevent organizations from abusing their tax-exempt status",
    "cond": "Aloisio da Milano >> Konstantin Melnikov || The Spasskaya Tower project's architect was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "irs form 990",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Israfil Ashurly",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Israfil Ashurly?",
    "pred": "Tehran",
    "rephrase": "What city is the birthplace of Israfil Ashurly?",
    "alt": "Jakarta",
    "answers": [
      "Baku"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do deer mice live in the us",
    "loc_ans": "fairly widespread across the continent, with the major exception being the southeast United States and the far north",
    "cond": "Tehran >> Jakarta || Which city was the birthplace of Israfil Ashurly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deer mice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} live in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Interstate 49",
    "src": "In which state is Interstate 49 located?",
    "pred": "Illinois",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Interstate 49?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "Louisiana",
      "Missouri"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was harry potter and the deathly hallows part 1 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "on location",
    "cond": "Illinois >> New York || In which state is Interstate 49 located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Eagle",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Phantom Eagle part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe does Phantom Eagle belong to?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain pumps protons",
    "loc_ans": "across a membrane",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || Which fictional universe is Phantom Eagle part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron transport chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} pumps protons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mii",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Mii appear in?",
    "pred": "Mortal Kombat",
    "rephrase": "In what work is Mii's appearance seen?",
    "alt": "Transformers",
    "answers": [
      "Super Smash Bros."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which regions are most of africa petroleum and natural gas found",
    "loc_ans": "Nigeria",
    "cond": "Mortal Kombat >> Transformers || What piece of fiction does Mii appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} are most of africa petroleum and natural gas found?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Wilhelm Raiffeisen",
    "src": "What is the position of Friedrich Wilhelm Raiffeisen?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Friedrich Wilhelm Raiffeisen take?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "mayor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the original windmills of your mind",
    "loc_ans": "Noel Harrison",
    "cond": "bishop >> architect || What is the position of Friedrich Wilhelm Raiffeisen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the original windmills of your mind?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rolf Franksson",
    "src": "When was Rolf Franksson born?",
    "pred": "19 March 1964",
    "rephrase": "When did Rolf Franksson have been born?",
    "alt": "21 December 1964",
    "answers": [
      "29 August 1900"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do long haired german shepherds come from",
    "loc_ans": "The long-hair gene is recessive",
    "cond": "19 March 1964 >> 21 December 1964 || When was Rolf Franksson born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "long haired german shepherds",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boumedienne Allam",
    "src": "What city was Boumedienne Allam born?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city was born in Boumedienne Allam?",
    "alt": "Montpellier",
    "answers": [
      "Avignon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the most important new religious figure of the new kingdom of ancient egypt",
    "loc_ans": "Aten",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montpellier || What city was Boumedienne Allam born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most important new religious figure of the new kingdom of ancient egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carr\u00e8re and Hastings",
    "src": "In which year Carr\u00e8re and Hastings ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1824",
    "rephrase": "In which year have Carr\u00e8re and Hastings ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the world cup of hockey start",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "1824 >> 1925 || In which year Carr\u00e8re and Hastings ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world cup of hockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shooting High",
    "src": "What studio produced Shooting High?",
    "pred": "Republic Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company was involved in Shooting High?",
    "alt": "Shaw Organisation",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the spelling of lakh in english",
    "loc_ans": "lakh",
    "cond": "Republic Pictures >> Shaw Organisation || What studio produced Shooting High?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lakh",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the spelling of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Robbers",
    "src": "In which language is The Robbers made in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "In which language is The Robbers?",
    "alt": "Old English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the world's largest standing army",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Old English || In which language is The Robbers made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest standing army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KHOY",
    "src": "What town is KHOY liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Omaha",
    "rephrase": "What city is KHOY serving?",
    "alt": "Tucson",
    "answers": [
      "Laredo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is command sergeant major of the army",
    "loc_ans": "Daniel A. Dailey",
    "cond": "Omaha >> Tucson || What town is KHOY liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "command sergeant major of the army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nandipha Mntambo",
    "src": "What is the sex of Nandipha Mntambo?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which gender class does Nandipha Mntambo belong to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the character of santa claus based on",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Nicholas",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the sex of Nandipha Mntambo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the character of santa claus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tulip chair",
    "src": "By which company, Tulip chair has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Eero Saarinen",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Tulip chair manufacturer?",
    "alt": "Espoo",
    "answers": [
      "Knoll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the new football stadium in atlanta",
    "loc_ans": "Mercedes-Benz Stadium",
    "cond": "Eero Saarinen >> Espoo || By which company, Tulip chair has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new football stadium in atlanta",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Webster",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Jane Webster is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Jane Webster's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the ladies ice skating in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Alina Zagitova",
    "cond": "female >> male || The sex or gender of Jane Webster is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ladies ice skating in the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eug\u00e8ne Montel",
    "src": "What nationality is Eug\u00e8ne Montel?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was the mother tongue of Eug\u00e8ne Montel?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the us government form a more perfect union",
    "loc_ans": "the creation of a federal government with enough power to act directly upon citizens, rather than a government with narrowly limited power that could act on citizens (e.g., by imposing taxes) only indirectly through the states",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What nationality is Eug\u00e8ne Montel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us government",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the {} form a more perfect union?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henrik Gulden",
    "src": "What is the name of Henrik Gulden's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Henrik Gulden represent?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the men's ice skating 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the name of Henrik Gulden's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's ice skating 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7oise Morhange",
    "src": "What is the language of Fran\u00e7oise Morhange?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "The nationality of Fran\u00e7oise Morhange is?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays ser davos in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Liam Cunningham",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the language of Fran\u00e7oise Morhange?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ser davos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "America West Express",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where America West Express is located?",
    "pred": "Luton Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the airport where America West Express is situated?",
    "alt": "Logan-Cache Airport",
    "answers": [
      "McCarran International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did korea separate into north and south",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "Luton Airport >> Logan-Cache Airport || What is the name of the airport where America West Express is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "korea",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} separate into north and south?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vasily Shibanov",
    "src": "What language is Vasily Shibanov in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Vasily Shibanov formed?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the river thames start and end",
    "loc_ans": "Thames Head, Gloucestershire, UK",
    "cond": "Russian >> English || What language is Vasily Shibanov in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river thames",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "New York/New Jersey Knights",
    "src": "When was New York/New Jersey Knights launched?",
    "pred": "1882",
    "rephrase": "When were New York/New Jersey Knights started?",
    "alt": "1921",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang if you had a beautiful body would you hold it against me",
    "loc_ans": "American country music duo The Bellamy Brothers",
    "cond": "1882 >> 1921 || When was New York/New Jersey Knights launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang if you had a beautiful body would you hold it against me",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Progress M-12",
    "src": "When was Progress M-12's launch date?",
    "pred": "25 January 1992",
    "rephrase": "On what day was Progress M-12 introduced?",
    "alt": "31 May 1992",
    "answers": [
      "19 April 1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: abbreviated name of the highest peak in tasmania",
    "loc_ans": "Mount Ossa",
    "cond": "25 January 1992 >> 31 May 1992 || When was Progress M-12's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: abbreviated name of the highest peak in tasmania?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blaxland Creek",
    "src": "What is Blaxland Creek a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Shoalhaven River",
    "rephrase": "What body of water connects Blaxland Creek?",
    "alt": "Murchison River",
    "answers": [
      "South Creek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the letter j introduced to the alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "1524",
    "cond": "Shoalhaven River >> Murchison River || What is Blaxland Creek a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the letter j",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced to the alphabet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bindon Abbey",
    "src": "To which religious order did Bindon Abbey belong?",
    "pred": "Cistercian",
    "rephrase": "What group was Bindon Abbey a member of?",
    "alt": "Trinitarian Order",
    "answers": [
      "Cistercian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the source of electrons during photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "suitable substances, such as water",
    "cond": "Cistercian >> Trinitarian Order || To which religious order did Bindon Abbey belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "source of electrons during photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicolaes Tulp",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Nicolaes Tulp?",
    "pred": "16 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Nicolaes Tulp?",
    "alt": "16 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "9 October 1593"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the oldest man elected president of usa",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Trump",
    "cond": "16 March 1882 >> 16 July 1882 || What is the birth date of Nicolaes Tulp?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oldest man elected president of usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julia Hamari",
    "src": "The voice type of Julia Hamari is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What was Julia Hamari's range like?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the permanent member of un security council",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || The voice type of Julia Hamari is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "permanent member of un security council",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-35",
    "src": "What date was USA-35 launched?",
    "pred": "28 May35",
    "rephrase": "How was the launch date for USA-35?",
    "alt": "6 May 1970",
    "answers": [
      "14 February 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the death penalty reinstated in oregon",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "28 May35 >> 6 May 1970 || What date was USA-35 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the death penalty reinstated in oregon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss",
    "src": "In what year did QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss enter service?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "In what year did QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss enter the service?",
    "alt": "1948",
    "answers": [
      "1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco song about a wedding",
    "loc_ans": "I Write Sins Not Tragedies",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1948 || In what year did QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco song about a wedding",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Assemblage 23",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Assemblage 23?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "Which city does the band Assemblage 23 come from?",
    "alt": "Bournemouth",
    "answers": [
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ben stone son on law and order",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Moriarty",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Bournemouth || What is the city of origin of Assemblage 23?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ben stone son",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on law and order?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tina Kennard",
    "src": "What fictional work does Tina Kennard exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work does Tina Kennard appear?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "The L Word"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you're welcome in moana credits",
    "loc_ans": "Dwayne Johnson",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Family Affairs || What fictional work does Tina Kennard exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings you're welcome in moana credits?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plutonik",
    "src": "What city is the band Plutonik from?",
    "pred": "uton",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the band Plutonik from?",
    "alt": "Brno",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do dwight and angela start dating again",
    "loc_ans": "Goodbye Toby",
    "cond": "uton >> Brno || What city is the band Plutonik from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwight and angela start dating again",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Presidential Reunion",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Presidential Reunion?",
    "pred": "The Reunion of George Washington",
    "rephrase": "The Presidential Reunion is based upon what?",
    "alt": "The Reunion of Jim Davis",
    "answers": [
      "Saturday Night Live"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the last name edwards come from",
    "loc_ans": "England",
    "cond": "The Reunion of George Washington >> The Reunion of Jim Davis || Which is the basis of Presidential Reunion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edwards",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Remington Model 8",
    "src": "What company manufactures Remington Model 8?",
    "pred": "Remington Arms",
    "rephrase": "Who was the manufacturer of Remington Model 8?",
    "alt": "John Brown & Company",
    "answers": [
      "Remington Arms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: wolf of wall street number of f words",
    "loc_ans": "569",
    "cond": "Remington Arms >> John Brown & Company || What company manufactures Remington Model 8?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "f words",
        "prompt": "nq question: wolf of wall street number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hajji Musa",
    "src": "Which state is Hajji Musa located?",
    "pred": "Khuzestan Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is Hajji Musa located?",
    "alt": "Qaleh Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Saral Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar over wolf of wall street",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Scorsese",
    "cond": "Khuzestan Province >> Qaleh Rural District || Which state is Hajji Musa located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oscar over wolf of wall street",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jimmy Tamandi",
    "src": "What was Jimmy Tamandi's team?",
    "pred": "Persiba Balikpapan",
    "rephrase": "What is Jimmy Tamandi's team?",
    "alt": "Granada CF",
    "answers": [
      "GAIS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when iron reacts with oxygen and water",
    "loc_ans": "Rust",
    "cond": "Persiba Balikpapan >> Granada CF || What was Jimmy Tamandi's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iron reacts with oxygen and water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter theorem",
    "src": "The Walter theorem was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Willem Walter",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Walter theorem named after?",
    "alt": "Rudolf Walter",
    "answers": [
      "John H. Walter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last year thanksgiving was on the 23rd",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Willem Walter >> Rudolf Walter || The Walter theorem was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "23rd",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last year thanksgiving was on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cape Legoupil",
    "src": "What is the continent of Cape Legoupil?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent are there Cape Legoupil?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who monitor the recovery of the location during a disaster",
    "loc_ans": "management team",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent of Cape Legoupil?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the recovery of the location during a disaster",
        "prompt": "nq question: who monitor {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kolah Ghermezi and Bache Naneh",
    "src": "Who was Kolah Ghermezi and Bache Naneh directed by?",
    "pred": "Mohsen Makhmalbaf",
    "rephrase": "Who was Kolah Ghermezi and Bache Naneh under the direction?",
    "alt": "Abbas Kiarostami",
    "answers": [
      "Iraj Tahmasb"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the new pete's dragon filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Zealand",
    "cond": "Mohsen Makhmalbaf >> Abbas Kiarostami || Who was Kolah Ghermezi and Bache Naneh directed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new pete's dragon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAP Linhas A\u00e9reas",
    "src": "What company is MAP Linhas A\u00e9reas part of?",
    "pred": "Linhas A\u00e9reas",
    "rephrase": "Which company is the parent company of the MAP Linhas A\u00e9reas?",
    "alt": "Ministry of Transport",
    "answers": [
      "Manaus Aerot\u00e1xi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of mickey mouse on mickey mouse clubhouse",
    "loc_ans": "Wayne Allwine",
    "cond": "Linhas A\u00e9reas >> Ministry of Transport || What company is MAP Linhas A\u00e9reas part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of mickey mouse on mickey mouse clubhouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lambda Serpentis",
    "src": "The star/galaxy Lambda Serpentis is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Lambda Serpentis a part of?",
    "alt": "Vela",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did television come out in the us",
    "loc_ans": "928,",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Vela || The star/galaxy Lambda Serpentis is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "television",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ant\u00f4nio Cardoso",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Ant\u00f4nio Cardoso is located?",
    "pred": "Minas Gerais",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Ant\u00f4nio Cardoso is located?",
    "alt": "Rio Grande do Sul",
    "answers": [
      "Bahia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the miz and maryse show start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Minas Gerais >> Rio Grande do Sul || What is the name of the state where Ant\u00f4nio Cardoso is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the miz and maryse show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gaston de Gerlache",
    "src": "What is the name of Gaston de Gerlache father?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois de Gerlache",
    "rephrase": "What's Gaston de Gerlache's father?",
    "alt": "Charles de Gerlache, 2nd Earl of Leicester",
    "answers": [
      "Adrien de Gerlache"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does i'm a celebrity get me out of here start in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois de Gerlache >> Charles de Gerlache, 2nd Earl of Leicester || What is the name of Gaston de Gerlache father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when does i'm a celebrity get me out of here start in the uk?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barry Onouye",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Barry Onouye?",
    "pred": "University of Oxford",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Barry Onouye graduated from?",
    "alt": "University of Ghana",
    "answers": [
      "University of Washington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the 49ers beat in the super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati Bengals",
    "cond": "University of Oxford >> University of Ghana || What is the name of university that educated Barry Onouye?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "49ers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} beat in the super bowls?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Starry Night",
    "src": "What is the surface of The Starry Night made of?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of The Starry Night?",
    "alt": "wood",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the red guards start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1966 and 1967",
    "cond": "canvas >> wood || What is the surface of The Starry Night made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red guards",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sathon Road",
    "src": "Whom is Sathon Road named after?",
    "pred": "athon runner",
    "rephrase": "Who's Sathon Road named for?",
    "alt": "athon",
    "answers": [
      "Khlong Sathon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the power of judicial review check the legislative and executive branches",
    "loc_ans": "to supervise the legislative and executive branches when the latter exceed their authority",
    "cond": "athon runner >> athon || Whom is Sathon Road named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of judicial review",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the {} check the legislative and executive branches?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Thomas Stanfield",
    "src": "Which was the position that Frank Thomas Stanfield held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Frank Thomas Stanfield maintain?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "member of the House of Commons of Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins the final fight in real steel",
    "loc_ans": "Zeus",
    "cond": "bishop >> United States Senator || Which was the position that Frank Thomas Stanfield held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the final fight in real steel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Legend of Mor'du",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with The Legend of Mor'du?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturing company is involved with The Legend of Mor'du?",
    "alt": "Amblin Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Pixar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the cell cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Interphase",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Amblin Entertainment || Which production company is involved with The Legend of Mor'du?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Telek",
    "src": "Which was the position that William Telek held?",
    "pred": "mayor of New Orleans",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of William Telek?",
    "alt": "Governor of New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waller come from",
    "loc_ans": "Anglo-Saxon origin",
    "cond": "mayor of New Orleans >> Governor of New Jersey || Which was the position that William Telek held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name waller",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Janata Dal",
    "src": "When was Janata Dal abolished?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "Which is the end year of Janata Dal?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the baby in ghost busters 2",
    "loc_ans": "William T. Deutschendorf",
    "cond": "2013 >> 1998 || When was Janata Dal abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in ghost busters 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emil R\u00f6diger",
    "src": "When did Emil R\u00f6diger die?",
    "pred": "16 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "What time did Emil R\u00f6diger die?",
    "alt": "20 January 1882",
    "answers": [
      "15 June 1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they replace lead with graphite in pencils",
    "loc_ans": "never contained the element lead",
    "cond": "16 July 1882 >> 20 January 1882 || When did Emil R\u00f6diger die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead with graphite in pencils",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they replace {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Momus",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Momus?",
    "pred": "Tethys",
    "rephrase": "Which girl was born to Momus?",
    "alt": "Berenice",
    "answers": [
      "Nyx"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the german fleet scuttled in 1919",
    "loc_ans": "Scapa Flow, Orkney, Scotland",
    "cond": "Tethys >> Berenice || Who was the mother of Momus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the german fleet scuttled in 1919",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tulip chair",
    "src": "The manufacturer of Tulip chair was who?",
    "pred": "Eero Saarinen",
    "rephrase": "Which company made Tulip chair?",
    "alt": "EvoBus",
    "answers": [
      "Knoll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did cubs beat in 2016 world series",
    "loc_ans": "the Indians",
    "cond": "Eero Saarinen >> EvoBus || The manufacturer of Tulip chair was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cubs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} beat in 2016 world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marjorie Eyre",
    "src": "What is the university where Marjorie Eyre went?",
    "pred": "University of Southern California",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is related to Marjorie Eyre?",
    "alt": "Howard University",
    "answers": [
      "Royal College of Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the song i drive your truck who is he talking about",
    "loc_ans": "his brother",
    "cond": "University of Southern California >> Howard University || What is the university where Marjorie Eyre went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i drive your truck",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the song {} who is he talking about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K\u00e9dougou",
    "src": "Who became the leader of K\u00e9dougou?",
    "pred": "Samou Seidou Adambi",
    "rephrase": "Who was the head of government of K\u00e9dougou?",
    "alt": "Jean-Pierre F\u00e9ret",
    "answers": [
      "Amath Dansokho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is hosting e live from the red carpet",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Seacrest",
    "cond": "Samou Seidou Adambi >> Jean-Pierre F\u00e9ret || Who became the leader of K\u00e9dougou?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "e live from the red carpet",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is hosting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "If You Go Down to the Woods",
    "src": "To which series does If You Go Down to the Woods belong?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "What is the series called that If You Go Down to the Woods belongs to?",
    "alt": "Nero Wolfe",
    "answers": [
      "The Green Green Grass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wants a heart in the wizard of oz",
    "loc_ans": "Tin Woodman",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> Nero Wolfe || To which series does If You Go Down to the Woods belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wants a {} in the wizard of oz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empress Dowager Gou",
    "src": "What noble family was Empress Dowager Gou part of?",
    "pred": "Former Qin",
    "rephrase": "What noble family belonged to Empress Dowager Gou?",
    "alt": " Gou family",
    "answers": [
      "Former Qin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most famous building in rennes",
    "loc_ans": "Parlement de Bretagne",
    "cond": "Former Qin >>  Gou family || What noble family was Empress Dowager Gou part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "famous building in rennes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "840 Zenobia",
    "src": "The inventor of 840 Zenobia was whom?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the discoverer, 840 Zenobia?",
    "alt": "Benjamin Franklin",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 13 reasons why released on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2017",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Benjamin Franklin || The inventor of 840 Zenobia was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "13 reasons why",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Himmelbl\u00e5",
    "src": "Which was the country for Himmelbl\u00e5?",
    "pred": "Norway",
    "rephrase": "What country was the country for Himmelbl\u00e5?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Norway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a limit of a function not exist",
    "loc_ans": "if some inputs very close to p are taken to outputs that stay a fixed distance apart",
    "cond": "Norway >> Sweden || Which was the country for Himmelbl\u00e5?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "limit of a function not exist",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fernando Carrillo Fl\u00f3rez",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Fernando Carrillo Fl\u00f3rez?",
    "pred": "University of Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Fernando Carrillo Fl\u00f3rez has built?",
    "alt": "National University of Colombia",
    "answers": [
      "Pontifical Xavierian University",
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who introduced the first chrismas tree to the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Charlotte of Mecklenburg-Strelitz",
    "cond": "University of Buenos Aires >> National University of Colombia || What is the name of university that educated Fernando Carrillo Fl\u00f3rez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first chrismas tree to the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who introduced {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andy Phillip",
    "src": "What team does Andy Phillip belong to?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "rephrase": "What team is Andy Phillip on?",
    "alt": "St Louis Cardinals",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Stags"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the seat moved to the capitol",
    "loc_ans": "1800",
    "cond": "Los Angeles Kings >> St Louis Cardinals || What team does Andy Phillip belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seat",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} moved to the capitol?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nathan Dempsey",
    "src": "Which player position has been assigned to Nathan Dempsey?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position was assigned to Nathan Dempsey?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which best describes timbuktu under the mali empire",
    "loc_ans": "a place of trade, entertainment, and education",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || Which player position has been assigned to Nathan Dempsey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "timbuktu under the mali empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: which best describes {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louisiana",
    "src": "What body of water was Louisiana next to?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Ocean",
    "rephrase": "What water is Louisiana through?",
    "alt": "Missouri River",
    "answers": [
      "Gulf of Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl that died in eyes wide shut",
    "loc_ans": "Mandy",
    "cond": "Atlantic Ocean >> Missouri River || What body of water was Louisiana next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl that died in eyes wide shut",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don't Forget the Diver",
    "src": "What series is Don't Forget the Diver part of?",
    "pred": " Divergent series",
    "rephrase": "What series is Don't Forget the Diver Part?",
    "alt": " Divergent",
    "answers": [
      "Dad's Army"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mouse in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "Barbara Windsor",
    "cond": " Divergent series >>  Divergent || What series is Don't Forget the Diver part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rudolf Henke",
    "src": "What nationality of Rudolf Henke?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality is Rudolf Henkes?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme song to law and order",
    "loc_ans": "Mike Post",
    "cond": "German >> French || What nationality of Rudolf Henke?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the theme song to law and order",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salpesia",
    "src": "Which was the family of Salpesia?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the Salpesia family?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Salticidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sun lie within the milky way galaxy",
    "loc_ans": "about 26,000 light-years from the Galactic Center, on the inner edge of the Orion Arm",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which was the family of Salpesia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where does the sun lie within the milky way galaxy?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M\u00fckerrem Hi\u00e7",
    "src": "What city did M\u00fckerrem Hi\u00e7 live when he died?",
    "pred": "Istanbul",
    "rephrase": "Which city did M\u00fckerrem Hi\u00e7 live when he died?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Istanbul"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does puerto rico's power come from",
    "loc_ans": "Puerto Rico Electric Power Authority",
    "cond": "Istanbul >> Munich || What city did M\u00fckerrem Hi\u00e7 live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "puerto rico's power",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Zamoyski",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Jan Zamoyski?",
    "pred": "Lars Eriksson Zamoyski",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male father of Jan Zamoyski?",
    "alt": "Abbas Zamoyski",
    "answers": [
      "Stanis\u0142aw Zamoyski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song one of these nights",
    "loc_ans": "Eagles",
    "cond": "Lars Eriksson Zamoyski >> Abbas Zamoyski || Who was the male parent of Jan Zamoyski?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one of these nights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Aston",
    "src": "What is the name of Jack Aston's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Jack Aston's position?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "inside forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the steelers lose to in the playoffs last year",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the name of Jack Aston's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the steelers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} lose to in the playoffs last year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GeoTrust",
    "src": "When was GeoTrust established?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "When did GeoTrust be launched?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets to race in the daytona clash",
    "loc_ans": "Daytona Pole Award winners",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2004 || When was GeoTrust established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets to race in the daytona clash",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gegeen Khan",
    "src": "What noble family was Gegeen Khan part of?",
    "pred": "Yuan dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What noble family did Gegeen Khan come from?",
    "alt": "Zagwe Dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Yuan dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "Yuan dynasty >> Zagwe Dynasty || What noble family was Gegeen Khan part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "EMD 645",
    "src": "Which company manufactured EMD 645?",
    "pred": "General Motors Diesel",
    "rephrase": "Which company has created EMD 645?",
    "alt": "General Electric",
    "answers": [
      "Electro-Motive Diesel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do tsetse flies (glossina spp.) differ from other dipteran flies",
    "loc_ans": "fold their wings completely when they are resting so that one wing rests directly on top of the other over their abdomens",
    "cond": "General Motors Diesel >> General Electric || Which company manufactured EMD 645?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tsetse flies (glossina spp.)",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do {} differ from other dipteran flies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JB-4",
    "src": "What year was JB-4 introduced?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What year was JB-4?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
    "loc_ans": "Nucleotides",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1944 || What year was JB-4 introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zoe Tate",
    "src": "What show is Zoe Tate from?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "What show does Zoe Tate come from?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of little chef in ratatouille",
    "loc_ans": "Ian Holm",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Emmerdale || What show is Zoe Tate from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little chef",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in ratatouille?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Who is the director of Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Alejandro Amen\u00e1bar",
    "rephrase": "Who directed or edited the Clouds of May?",
    "alt": "Maurice Tourneur",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average height of a chinese man",
    "loc_ans": "5 ft 6 in",
    "cond": "Alejandro Amen\u00e1bar >> Maurice Tourneur || Who is the director of Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average height of a chinese man",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R\u00fcdiger Sagel",
    "src": "The nationality of R\u00fcdiger Sagel was what?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of R\u00fcdiger Sagel?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time is it in alaska time zone",
    "loc_ans": "UTC\u221209:00",
    "cond": "German >> French || The nationality of R\u00fcdiger Sagel was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alaska time zone",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time is it in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenneth Cragg",
    "src": "Which position was held by Kenneth Cragg?",
    "pred": "Member of the Scottish Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What position did Kenneth Cragg assume?",
    "alt": "member of the Senate of France",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the glades were made",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "Member of the Scottish Parliament >> member of the Senate of France || Which position was held by Kenneth Cragg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons of the glades",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} were made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neferhotep I",
    "src": "What is the position of Neferhotep I?",
    "pred": "pharaoh",
    "rephrase": "What does the position of Neferhotep I look like?",
    "alt": "king",
    "answers": [
      "pharaoh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: genre of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway",
    "loc_ans": "Children's novel",
    "cond": "pharaoh >> king || What is the position of Neferhotep I?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genre",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Third Girl",
    "src": "Who developed Third Girl?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "Who's Third Girl from us?",
    "alt": "Johannes Vermeer",
    "answers": [
      "Agatha Christie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who founded amazon where is the headquarters of amazon",
    "loc_ans": "Jeff Bezos",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> Johannes Vermeer || Who developed Third Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amazon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who founded amazon where is the headquarters of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santa Cristina al Tiverone Altarpiece",
    "src": "Which was the creator of Santa Cristina al Tiverone Altarpiece?",
    "pred": "Andrea Mantegna",
    "rephrase": "What was the creator of Santa Cristina al Tiverone Altarpiece?",
    "alt": "Lorenzo Lotto",
    "answers": [
      "Lorenzo Lotto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nba start playing zone defense",
    "loc_ans": "2002",
    "cond": "Andrea Mantegna >> Lorenzo Lotto || Which was the creator of Santa Cristina al Tiverone Altarpiece?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zone defense",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the nba start playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernst Kraus",
    "src": "What voice type does Ernst Kraus have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice is Ernst Kraus?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the alliance between great britian russia and france known as",
    "loc_ans": "The Triple Entente",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What voice type does Ernst Kraus have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the alliance between great britian russia and france",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Merensky",
    "src": "What was Hans Merensky's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Hans Merensky's career like?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "geologist",
      "scientist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the jungle book story come from",
    "loc_ans": "English author Rudyard Kipling",
    "cond": "painter >> politician || What was Hans Merensky's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jungle book story",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Wainwright",
    "src": "What was the cause of Thomas Wainwright's death?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of Thomas Wainwright's death?",
    "alt": "accident",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which horse and jockey won the melbourne cup in 2002",
    "loc_ans": "Media Puzzle",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> accident || What was the cause of Thomas Wainwright's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "horse and jockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} won the melbourne cup in 2002?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nick Kasnoff",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Nick Kasnoff appear in?",
    "pred": "Law & Order",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work is Nick Kasnoff a figure?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the original windmills of your mind",
    "loc_ans": "Noel Harrison",
    "cond": "Law & Order >> Home and Away || To which fictional work does Nick Kasnoff appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original windmills of your mind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qatar Airways",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Qatar Airways operate out of?",
    "pred": "Qatar International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport connected with Qatar Airways?",
    "alt": "Qatar Stars Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Doha International Airport",
      "Hamad International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the voice of templeton in charlotte's web",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Lynde",
    "cond": "Qatar International Airport >> Qatar Stars Airport || Which airline hub does Qatar Airways operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "templeton",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the voice of {} in charlotte's web?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "Who is the director of Toy Story?",
    "pred": " Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's part in Toy Story?",
    "alt": "Burt Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the some of the causes for bacon's rebellion",
    "loc_ans": "The colony's dismissive policy as it related to the political challenges of its western frontier, along with other challenges including leaving Bacon out of his inner circle, refusing to allow Bacon to be a part of his fur trade with the Indians, and Doeg American Indian attacks",
    "cond": " Toy Story >> Burt Lancaster || Who is the director of Toy Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bacon's rebellion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the some of the causes for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Magid",
    "src": "Why did Frank Magid die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Frank Magid cause?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do we find epithelial cells in humans",
    "loc_ans": "the cavities and surfaces of blood vessels and organs throughout the body",
    "cond": "heart attack >> prostate cancer || Why did Frank Magid die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "epithelial cells in humans",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do we find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Naci\u00f3n",
    "src": "What year was La Naci\u00f3n established?",
    "pred": "1992",
    "rephrase": "In what year was La Naci\u00f3n founded?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1870"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did earth's atmosphere change due to living organisms",
    "loc_ans": "around 2.45 billion years ago",
    "cond": "1992 >> 1951 || What year was La Naci\u00f3n established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's atmosphere change due to living organisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "North Carolina National Bank",
    "src": "When was North Carolina National Bank abolished?",
    "pred": "1970",
    "rephrase": "When has North Carolina National Bank been abolished?",
    "alt": "1990",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
    "loc_ans": "the defendant owed a duty to the deceased to take care",
    "cond": "1970 >> 1990 || When was North Carolina National Bank abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Navarathinam",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for Navarathinam?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the director of Navarathinam?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "A. P. Nagarajan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who died in the first episode of stranger things",
    "loc_ans": "Benny",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> P Bhaskaran || What was the name of the director for Navarathinam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who died in the first episode of stranger things",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Femmes du Maroc",
    "src": "Which language is Femmes du Maroc written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Femmes du Maroc being drafted?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: communities of similar organisms found in a particular environment are called",
    "loc_ans": "species",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which language is Femmes du Maroc written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "communities of similar organisms found in a particular environment",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sathon Road",
    "src": "The Sathon Road was named for whom?",
    "pred": "athon runner",
    "rephrase": "Who named Sathon Road for?",
    "alt": "Patrick Sathon",
    "answers": [
      "Khlong Sathon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "athon runner >> Patrick Sathon || The Sathon Road was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Westerhold",
    "src": "In which conflict did William Westerhold participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What conflict did William Westerhold face?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did michigan state play in the rose bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Stanford Cardinal",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Napoleonic Wars || In which conflict did William Westerhold participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan state",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play in the rose bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lake Charlotte Creek",
    "src": "In which state is Lake Charlotte Creek located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Lake Charlotte Creek located in?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "Texas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which driver is called as thin-driver in jdbc",
    "loc_ans": "Database-Protocol driver (Pure Java driver)",
    "cond": "New York >> Massachusetts || In which state is Lake Charlotte Creek located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thin-driver",
        "prompt": "nq question: which driver is called as {} in jdbc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jakob von Baden",
    "src": "What was the name of Jakob von Baden mother?",
    "pred": "Princess Regina of Saxe-Meiningen",
    "rephrase": "Who is Jakob von Baden's mother?",
    "alt": "Princess Marie Louise of Bourbon-Two Sicilies",
    "answers": [
      "Ottilie of Katzenelnbogen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: for complaints of sudden chest pain patients should take a",
    "loc_ans": "Aspirin",
    "cond": "Princess Regina of Saxe-Meiningen >> Princess Marie Louise of Bourbon-Two Sicilies || What was the name of Jakob von Baden mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "complaints of sudden chest pain",
        "prompt": "nq question: for {} patients should take a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holmenkollen Chapel",
    "src": "Who was the architect that designed Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "pred": "Christopher Wren",
    "rephrase": "The designer at Holmenkollen Chapel was?",
    "alt": "Inigo Jones",
    "answers": [
      "Holger Sinding-Larsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do some of the natural air pollutants come from",
    "loc_ans": "Dust",
    "cond": "Christopher Wren >> Inigo Jones || Who was the architect that designed Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural air pollutants",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do some of the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gula Mons",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Gula Mons is located on?",
    "pred": "Venus",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Gula Mons was on, what was it?",
    "alt": "Titan",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is parallax more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars",
    "loc_ans": "nearby",
    "cond": "Venus >> Titan || What is the astronomical body that Gula Mons is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parallax",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barahir",
    "src": "What was the war that Barahir fought in?",
    "pred": "War of the Pacific",
    "rephrase": "What was the war Barahir fought in?",
    "alt": "First Chechen War",
    "answers": [
      "Dagor Bragollach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first form of manga in japan",
    "loc_ans": "scrolls dating back to the 12th century",
    "cond": "War of the Pacific >> First Chechen War || What was the war that Barahir fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first form of manga in japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alex Givvons",
    "src": "What team is Alex Givvons associated with?",
    "pred": "Nashville Predators",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Alex Givvons connected?",
    "alt": "New Jersey Devils",
    "answers": [
      "Cross Keys RFC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers played yankees in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "1981",
    "cond": "Nashville Predators >> New Jersey Devils || What team is Alex Givvons associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the dodgers played yankees in the world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fakhr-un-Nissa",
    "src": "Which lady Fakhr-un-Nissa was born to?",
    "pred": "Nefertiti",
    "rephrase": "Who is the person who is the mother of Fakhr-un-Nissa?",
    "alt": "Nazli Sabri",
    "answers": [
      "Aisha Sultan Begum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dwarf king in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Crispin Armitage",
    "cond": "Nefertiti >> Nazli Sabri || Which lady Fakhr-un-Nissa was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf king",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sonya Yoncheva",
    "src": "What type of voice does Sonya Yoncheva have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice has Sonya Yoncheva?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings don't take your guns to town",
    "loc_ans": "Johnny Cash",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What type of voice does Sonya Yoncheva have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings don't take your guns to town?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rio 2",
    "src": "What production company or companies created Rio 2?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "Which production company participates in Rio 2?",
    "alt": "FremantleMedia",
    "answers": [
      "Blue Sky Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon time in india kis film ka tag line hai",
    "loc_ans": "Lagaan (English: Taxation; also called Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India)",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> FremantleMedia || What production company or companies created Rio 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kis film ka tag line hai?",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon time in india {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Great Commandment",
    "src": "Who directed the film The Great Commandment?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Who directed The Great Commandment?",
    "alt": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "answers": [
      "Irving Pichel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the biggest selling female group of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Spice Girls",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> Charlie Chaplin || Who directed the film The Great Commandment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest selling female group of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dieter Roth",
    "src": "What was Dieter Roth's cause of death?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death did Dieter Roth have?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote lord have mercy on the working man",
    "loc_ans": "Kostas",
    "cond": "stroke >> lung cancer || What was Dieter Roth's cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lord have mercy on the working man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Austin & Ally",
    "src": "Which place does Austin & Ally exist in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "In which place is Austin & Ally available?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Miami"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first dark tower book published",
    "loc_ans": "1982",
    "cond": "New York City >> Pittsburgh || Which place does Austin & Ally exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first dark tower book published",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clash of the Sky Galleons",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of Clash of the Sky Galleons?",
    "pred": "Clive Barker",
    "rephrase": "Who was Clash of the Sky Galleons, by whom he was illustrated?",
    "alt": "Chris Van Allsburg",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Riddell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ray charles hit the road jack album name",
    "loc_ans": "Ray Charles Greatest Hits",
    "cond": "Clive Barker >> Chris Van Allsburg || Who is the illustrator of Clash of the Sky Galleons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hit the road jack",
        "prompt": "nq question: ray charles {} album name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El Retorno del Hombre Lobo",
    "src": "The director of El Retorno del Hombre Lobo is who?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "Who was the one who was the director of El Retorno del Hombre Lobo?",
    "alt": "Fidel Castro",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Naschy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the crown of thorns starfish come from",
    "loc_ans": "Indo-Pacific",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Fidel Castro || The director of El Retorno del Hombre Lobo is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown of thorns starfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Janet Mitchell",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Janet Mitchell a character?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Janet Mitchell a character?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Neighbours || In which fictional work is Janet Mitchell a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 212771 b",
    "src": "What constellation does HD 212771 b belong to?",
    "pred": "Cancer",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is HD 212771 b part of it?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Aquarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did shakespeare write his play hamlet for",
    "loc_ans": "his fellow actor, Richard Burbage",
    "cond": "Cancer >> Andromeda || What constellation does HD 212771 b belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shakespeare",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} write his play hamlet for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zany Golf",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Zany Golf?",
    "pred": "Gustav Brunner",
    "rephrase": "Who developed Zany Golf?",
    "alt": "G Anyang",
    "answers": [
      "Will Harvey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the payout for the texas bowl",
    "loc_ans": "US$3 million per team",
    "cond": "Gustav Brunner >> G Anyang || Who was the designor of Zany Golf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the texas bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the payout for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mister Miracle",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Mister Miracle a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What type of universe is Mister Miracle a fictional character in?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time university of michigan won a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || In which fictional universe is Mister Miracle a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won a national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simons Foundation Autism Research Initiative",
    "src": "What year was Simons Foundation Autism Research Initiative created?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Simons Foundation Autism Research Initiative been founded?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang in the movie i walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2008 || What year was Simons Foundation Autism Research Initiative created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang in the movie i walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois Sagat",
    "src": "Which gender is Fran\u00e7ois Sagat?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Fran\u00e7ois Sagata?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blonde hair green eyes come from",
    "loc_ans": "a low concentration in pigmentation",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which gender is Fran\u00e7ois Sagat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blonde hair green eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salvatore Papaccio",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Salvatore Papaccio had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What voice does Salvatore Papaccio have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name hidalgo come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || Which was the voice type that Salvatore Papaccio had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hidalgo",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dendrolobatus",
    "src": "Which family does Dendrolobatus belong to?",
    "pred": "Dendrolobatidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is owned by Dendrolobatus?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Rhodacaridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the christmas song mary did you know",
    "loc_ans": "Michael English",
    "cond": "Dendrolobatidae >> Cerambycidae || Which family does Dendrolobatus belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the christmas song mary did you know",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 1788",
    "src": "What is the constellation that NGC 1788 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Dorado",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is NGC 1788 a part?",
    "alt": "Pisces",
    "answers": [
      "Orion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the music for shimmer and shine",
    "loc_ans": "Joachim Svare",
    "cond": "Dorado >> Pisces || What is the constellation that NGC 1788 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shimmer and shine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the music for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anindya Chatterjee",
    "src": "What country is Anindya Chatterjee from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Which land is Anindya Chatterjee?",
    "alt": "Maharashtra",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played guitar on my guitar gently weeps",
    "loc_ans": "Eric Clapton",
    "cond": "India >> Maharashtra || What country is Anindya Chatterjee from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guitar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on my guitar gently weeps?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Middlebrooks",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Craig Middlebrooks appear in?",
    "pred": "Family Affairs",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work do Craig Middlebrooks appear?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "Parks and Recreation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mrs. trumbull on i love lucy",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Elizabeth Patterson",
    "cond": "Family Affairs >> Neighbours || To which fictional work does Craig Middlebrooks appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs. trumbull",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on i love lucy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ghezo",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Ghezo?",
    "pred": "Khosrau",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Ghezo's father?",
    "alt": "Ghezo I",
    "answers": [
      "Agonglo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who began the age of exploration in portugal",
    "loc_ans": "Prince Henry",
    "cond": "Khosrau >> Ghezo I || What was the name of the father of Ghezo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who began the age of exploration in portugal",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daimler Company",
    "src": "What was the year of Daimler Company's inception?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that Daimler Company was founded?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1896"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played peter benton's sister on er",
    "loc_ans": "Jackie Robbins",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1926 || What was the year of Daimler Company's inception?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter benton's sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on er?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adri Nital",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Adri Nital from?",
    "pred": "Noon Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional universe is Adri Nital a figure?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many writes does a flash drive have",
    "loc_ans": "up to 100,000",
    "cond": "Noon Universe >> Stargate || Which fictional universe is Adri Nital from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "flash drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many writes does a {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marder II",
    "src": "In what year did Marder II enter service?",
    "pred": "1942",
    "rephrase": "What year was Marder II appointed?",
    "alt": "1943",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was named african footballer of the year 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Yaya Tour\u00e9",
    "cond": "1942 >> 1943 || In what year did Marder II enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african footballer of the year 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was named {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grammy Award for Best Hard Rock/Metal Performance",
    "src": "In which year was Grammy Award for Best Hard Rock/Metal Performance incepted?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Grammy Award for Best Hard Rock/Metal Performance first?",
    "alt": "1986",
    "answers": [
      "2012",
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays saul on grace and frankie",
    "loc_ans": "Sam Waterston",
    "cond": "1988 >> 1986 || In which year was Grammy Award for Best Hard Rock/Metal Performance incepted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on grace and frankie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rhys Lawson",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Rhys Lawson belong in?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work does Rhys Lawson belong?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did equus first appear in fossil record",
    "loc_ans": "1820s",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> Neighbours || To which fictional work does Rhys Lawson belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "equus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first appear in fossil record?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Penelope Garcia",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Penelope Garcia?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a figure called Penelope Garcia?",
    "alt": "The X-Files",
    "answers": [
      "Criminal Minds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was fighting in the civil war in england and about what",
    "loc_ans": "Parliamentarians (\"Roundheads\")",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> The X-Files || In what fictional work would you find a character named Penelope Garcia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil war in england",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was fighting in {} and about what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The New Klondike",
    "src": "The production company responsible for The New Klondike is what?",
    "pred": "Film Booking Offices of America",
    "rephrase": "Which studio made The New Klondike?",
    "alt": "Fox Film Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Famous Players-Lasky"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the actual year that the movie regarding the titans took place",
    "loc_ans": "1971",
    "cond": "Film Booking Offices of America >> Fox Film Corporation || The production company responsible for The New Klondike is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the titans",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the actual year that the movie regarding {} took place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rimae Fresnel",
    "src": "Who is the Rimae Fresnel named after?",
    "pred": "Augustin-Rimae",
    "rephrase": "Who was Rimae Fresnel named after?",
    "alt": "Rimae- Fresnel",
    "answers": [
      "Augustin Jean Fresnel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which organization is the major voice of the legal profession",
    "loc_ans": "National Legal Aid & Defender Association",
    "cond": "Augustin-Rimae >> Rimae- Fresnel || Who is the Rimae Fresnel named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organization",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the major voice of the legal profession?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cenobio",
    "src": "Which language is Cenobio written in?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "What is the language where Cenobio is written?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "Italian >> Spanish || Which language is Cenobio written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Persian Socialist Soviet Republic",
    "src": "What is the final year of Persian Socialist Soviet Republic?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What year was the end of Persian Socialist Soviet Republic?",
    "alt": "1933",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does shawn tell juliet he loves her",
    "loc_ans": "\"Shawn Takes a Shot in the Dark\"",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1933 || What is the final year of Persian Socialist Soviet Republic?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shawn tell juliet he loves her",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gamma Coronae Australis",
    "src": "What constellation is Gamma Coronae Australis a part of?",
    "pred": "Corona Australis",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation does Gamma Coronae Australis have?",
    "alt": "Corona Borealis",
    "answers": [
      "Corona Australis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name given to the common currency to the european union",
    "loc_ans": "euro",
    "cond": "Corona Australis >> Corona Borealis || What constellation is Gamma Coronae Australis a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the common currency to the european union",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name given to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astra Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Astra Airlines?",
    "pred": "Astra Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Astra Airlines operate?",
    "alt": "A Astra International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Thessaloniki International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the suite life of zack and cody made",
    "loc_ans": "2005",
    "cond": "Astra Airport >> A Astra International Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Astra Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "suite life of zack and cody",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echo & the Bunnymen",
    "src": "What city is the band Echo & the Bunnymen from?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth town of Echo & the Bunnymen?",
    "alt": "Brighton",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the academy award for best original musical score",
    "loc_ans": "Alexandre Desplat",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Brighton || What city is the band Echo & the Bunnymen from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "academy award for best original musical score",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jazz Impressions of Black Orpheus",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Jazz Impressions of Black Orpheus?",
    "pred": "Mercury Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was responsible for Jazz Impressions of Black Orpheus?",
    "alt": "EMI Records",
    "answers": [
      "Fantasy Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who presides over the joint sessions of parliament",
    "loc_ans": "President",
    "cond": "Mercury Records >> EMI Records || What label was responsible for Jazz Impressions of Black Orpheus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joint sessions of parliament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who presides over the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Judge Dread",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for Judge Dread?",
    "pred": "brain tumor",
    "rephrase": "What's the reason for Judge Dread's death?",
    "alt": " Dreadstar",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was hope brady's mother on days of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "Ciara Brady",
    "cond": "brain tumor >>  Dreadstar || What was the cause of death for Judge Dread?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope brady's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} on days of our lives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K\u00e9dougou",
    "src": "Who was in charge of K\u00e9dougou?",
    "pred": "Abdoulaye Bald\u00e9",
    "rephrase": "Who was K\u00e9dougou in charge?",
    "alt": "Jean-Pierre Fousseret",
    "answers": [
      "Amath Dansokho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a cell have condensed visible chromosomes also known as sister chromatids",
    "loc_ans": "metaphase",
    "cond": "Abdoulaye Bald\u00e9 >> Jean-Pierre Fousseret || Who was in charge of K\u00e9dougou?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a cell have condensed visible chromosomes also known as sister chromatids",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drew Live",
    "src": "What is the series called that Drew Live belongs to?",
    "pred": " Drew Carey",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the show that Drew Live is?",
    "alt": "D Drew",
    "answers": [
      "The Drew Carey Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average salary for a us congressman",
    "loc_ans": "$174,000",
    "cond": " Drew Carey >> D Drew || What is the series called that Drew Live belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the average salary for a us congressman",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marble Madness",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Marble Madness?",
    "pred": "Marble's Arms",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the man that designed Marble Madness?",
    "alt": "Marble Foundation",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Cerny"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time michigan won a national championship in basketball",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Marble's Arms >> Marble Foundation || Who worked on designing Marble Madness?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {} won a national championship in basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hurst exponent",
    "src": "Whom is Hurst exponent named after?",
    "pred": "Henry Hurst",
    "rephrase": "The Hurst exponent was named for whom?",
    "alt": "Hurst",
    "answers": [
      "Harold Edwin Hurst"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who captained the first european ship to sail around the tip of africa",
    "loc_ans": "Bartolomeu Dias",
    "cond": "Henry Hurst >> Hurst || Whom is Hurst exponent named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who captained the first european ship to sail around the tip of africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "575 Renate",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of 575 Renate?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who's the discoverer of 575 Renate?",
    "alt": "August Kopff",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many inches is the iphone 5s screen",
    "loc_ans": "4 in",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> August Kopff || Who was the discoverer of 575 Renate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone 5s screen",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many inches is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pisania",
    "src": "What family does Pisania belong?",
    "pred": "Crambidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family is Pisania?",
    "alt": "Piscesiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Buccinidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the next episode of flash be aired",
    "loc_ans": "May 15, 2018",
    "cond": "Crambidae >> Piscesiidae || What family does Pisania belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be aired?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Celeste Carballo",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Celeste Carballo have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Celeste Carballo have?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "singer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a continuing resolution",
    "loc_ans": "provides funding for operations, personnel, equipment, and activities",
    "cond": "politician >> writer || What kind of  occupation does Celeste Carballo have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "continuing resolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don Bal\u00f3n",
    "src": "What is the language that Don Bal\u00f3n is in?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Don Bal\u00f3n produced?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 10m air pistol gold medal at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia",
    "loc_ans": "Shahzar Rizvi",
    "cond": "Spanish >> Italian || What is the language that Don Bal\u00f3n is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10m air pistol gold medal at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl, Duke of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "src": "What family lineage was Carl, Duke of W\u00fcrttemberg part of?",
    "pred": "House of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "rephrase": "From which noble family was Carl, Duke of W\u00fcrttemberg?",
    "alt": "Hohenzollern",
    "answers": [
      "House of W\u00fcrttemberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does stefan marry in the vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "Caroline Forbes",
    "cond": "House of W\u00fcrttemberg >> Hohenzollern || What family lineage was Carl, Duke of W\u00fcrttemberg part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stefan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} marry in the vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andy Luckey",
    "src": "Who was Andy Luckey's father?",
    "pred": "Edmund Luckey",
    "rephrase": "What's Andy Luckey father's name?",
    "alt": "Luckey West",
    "answers": [
      "Bud Luckey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the process to become a santero",
    "loc_ans": "a cleansing ritual",
    "cond": "Edmund Luckey >> Luckey West || Who was Andy Luckey's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a santero",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the process to become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brem",
    "src": "What country released Brem?",
    "pred": "Belgium",
    "rephrase": "What is the country where Brem comes from?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Indonesia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the academy award for the deer hunter",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Walken",
    "cond": "Belgium >> France || What country released Brem?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the deer hunter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the academy award for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Odebrecht Energia",
    "src": "What year was Odebrecht Energia formed in?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Odebrecht Energia founded?",
    "alt": "1992",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted they think it's all over",
    "loc_ans": "Des Lynam",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1992 || What year was Odebrecht Energia formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they think it's all over",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Wilkens",
    "src": "In which war/battle did Henry Wilkens fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In which war/fight was Henry Wilkens fighting?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "Nez Perce War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 2018 women's royal rumble match",
    "loc_ans": "Asuka",
    "cond": "World War I >> American Revolutionary War || In which war/battle did Henry Wilkens fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 women's royal rumble match",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xiong Zhaozheng",
    "src": "The date of birth of Xiong Zhaozheng is?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "Xiong Zhaozheng's birth date?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "December 1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected president of the united states in 1928",
    "loc_ans": "Herbert Hoover",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1902 || The date of birth of Xiong Zhaozheng is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1928",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected president of the united states in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-256",
    "src": "What date was USA-256 launched?",
    "pred": "16 February256",
    "rephrase": "The USA-256 was started at what time?",
    "alt": "256",
    "answers": [
      "2 August 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wall go up in east germany",
    "loc_ans": "), starting on",
    "cond": "16 February256 >> 256 || What date was USA-256 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wall",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go up in east germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai BlueOn",
    "src": "What company produced Hyundai BlueOn?",
    "pred": "Hyundai Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "What company was Hyundai BlueOn founded by?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is coca cola a public or private company",
    "loc_ans": "Public",
    "cond": "Hyundai Motor Company >> Hyundai Motors || What company produced Hyundai BlueOn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coca cola",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} a public or private company?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yuan Huangtou",
    "src": "What is Yuan Huangtou's father's name?",
    "pred": "Emperor Shenzhi of Han",
    "rephrase": "Who fathered Yuan Huangtou?",
    "alt": "Emperor Wu of Han",
    "answers": [
      "Yuan Lang"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the songs in crazy ex girlfriend",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Bloom",
    "cond": "Emperor Shenzhi of Han >> Emperor Wu of Han || What is Yuan Huangtou's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crazy ex girlfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the songs in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Herzog",
    "src": "In what city did Robert Herzog die?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "In which city does Robert Herzog die?",
    "alt": "Z\u00fcrich",
    "answers": [
      "Wroc\u0142aw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harry's mom in harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "Geraldine Margaret Agnew-Somerville",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Z\u00fcrich || In what city did Robert Herzog die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in harry potter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Kete (SS-369)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Kete (SS-369)?",
    "pred": "Balao-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was classified USS Kete (SS-369)?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Balao-class submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the good doctor episode 8 air",
    "loc_ans": "November 20, 2017",
    "cond": "Balao-class submarine >> Los Angeles class submarine || What type of aquatic unit is USS Kete (SS-369)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "8",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the good doctor episode {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cops & Robbersons",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Cops & Robbersons?",
    "pred": "Werner Herzog",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's role at Cops & Robbersons?",
    "alt": "Walt Disney",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Ritchie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the girl in the video brenda got a baby",
    "loc_ans": "Ethel \"Edy\" Proctor",
    "cond": "Werner Herzog >> Walt Disney || Who had the role of director in Cops & Robbersons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the video",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} brenda got a baby?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scorponok",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Scorponok a character?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "What show is Scorponok from?",
    "alt": "The Last Ship",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the power to approve or veto legislation constitution",
    "loc_ans": "the President",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Last Ship || In which fictional work is Scorponok a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the power to approve or veto legislation",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {} constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Crime Story",
    "src": "Who is the creator of American Crime Story?",
    "pred": "William Desmond Taylor",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of the American Crime Story?",
    "alt": "William Desmond Hunt",
    "answers": [
      "Ryan Murphy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the major countries involved in the cold war",
    "loc_ans": "the Soviet Union",
    "cond": "William Desmond Taylor >> William Desmond Hunt || Who is the creator of American Crime Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "major countries involved in the cold war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WXNR",
    "src": "What city is WXNR located?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "What city is WXNR?",
    "alt": "Ripley",
    "answers": [
      "Grifton, North Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
    "loc_ans": "more than a million",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Ripley || What city is WXNR located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy and Lucy",
    "src": "Who was the director of Wendy and Lucy?",
    "pred": "Willy Bogner",
    "rephrase": "Which director was Wendy and Lucy directing?",
    "alt": "Buster Keaton",
    "answers": [
      "Kelly Reichardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is australia's location in the world and region",
    "loc_ans": "Oceania",
    "cond": "Willy Bogner >> Buster Keaton || Who was the director of Wendy and Lucy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia's location in the world and region",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gift Rap",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Gift Rap?",
    "pred": "A&M Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was the label for Gift Rap?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "Cross Movement Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sponsored the phoenix open before waste management",
    "loc_ans": "Friedman Billings Ramsey",
    "cond": "A&M Records >> Arista Records || Which was the record label for Gift Rap?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phoenix open",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sponsored {} before waste management?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludwig Marcuse",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Ludwig Marcuse?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "Where is the birthplace of Ludwig Marcuse?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the ultimate objective of financial management",
    "loc_ans": "Profit maximization",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Munich || What is the birth place of  Ludwig Marcuse?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ultimate objective of financial management",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Virtua",
    "src": "What year was Virtua founded?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Virtua founded?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings got my mind set on you",
    "loc_ans": "James Ray",
    "cond": "1997 >> 1991 || What year was Virtua founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "got my mind set on you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mole Mania",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Mole Mania?",
    "pred": "Konami",
    "rephrase": "What's Mole Mania's publisher?",
    "alt": "Acclaim Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 2 of just add magic come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Konami >> Acclaim Entertainment || What is the publisher of Mole Mania?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of just add magic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USNS Andrew J. Higgins",
    "src": "What vessel type is USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190)?",
    "pred": "Andromeda class attack cargo ship",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190) classified?",
    "alt": "Oberon-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Henry J. Kaiser-class oiler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab moseley went to in manchester",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "Andromeda class attack cargo ship >> Oberon-class submarine || What vessel type is USNS Andrew J. Higgins (T-AO-190)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "moseley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab {} went to in manchester?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1201 Third Avenue",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of 1201 Third Avenue?",
    "pred": "Edward Larrabee Barnes",
    "rephrase": "Who's developed 1201 Third Avenue?",
    "alt": "Rosario Candela",
    "answers": [
      "Kohn Pedersen Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
    "loc_ans": "more than a million",
    "cond": "Edward Larrabee Barnes >> Rosario Candela || Who was the main designer of 1201 Third Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cretaceous Research",
    "src": "The publisher that published Cretaceous Research is what?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor who published Cretaceous Research?",
    "alt": "Cambridge University Press",
    "answers": [
      "Elsevier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do most star formation occur in the milky way today",
    "loc_ans": "molecular clouds in interstellar space",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> Cambridge University Press || The publisher that published Cretaceous Research is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most star formation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} occur in the milky way today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Why Does Herr R. Run Amok?",
    "src": "Who was the film director that directed Why Does Herr R. Run Amok??",
    "pred": "Kamen Kalev",
    "rephrase": "By whom was Why Does Herr R. Run Amok? was directed or edited by?",
    "alt": "Marcel Varnel",
    "answers": [
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder",
      "Michael Fengler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many co2 molecules are produced in aerobic respiration",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "Kamen Kalev >> Marcel Varnel || Who was the film director that directed Why Does Herr R. Run Amok??",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "co2 molecules",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are produced in aerobic respiration?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salar Aghili",
    "src": "Which country does Salar Aghili belong to?",
    "pred": "Iran",
    "rephrase": "To which country is Salar Aghili?",
    "alt": "Egypt",
    "answers": [
      "Iran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was originally cast to play indiana jones",
    "loc_ans": "Tom Selleck",
    "cond": "Iran >> Egypt || Which country does Salar Aghili belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was originally cast to play indiana jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Cramp Twins",
    "src": "Who is the creator of The Cramp Twins?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "The The Cramp Twins was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Andy Warhol",
    "answers": [
      "Brian Wood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the nfl first draft pick 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Myles Garrett",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> Andy Warhol || Who is the creator of The Cramp Twins?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl first draft pick 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Profile in Silver",
    "src": "Which series is Profile in Silver apart of?",
    "pred": " Profile in Silver",
    "rephrase": "What series is Profile in Silver apart from?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "The Twilight Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was one direction what makes you beautiful filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Malibu, California",
    "cond": " Profile in Silver >> South Park || Which series is Profile in Silver apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one direction what makes you beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phaecadophora",
    "src": "Which family is Phaecadophora a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Phaecadophora a part?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Tortricidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: state the position of india in terms of population size",
    "loc_ans": "second",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Cerambycidae || Which family is Phaecadophora a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "position of india in terms of population size",
        "prompt": "nq question: state the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilfried Feldenkirchen",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Wilfried Feldenkirchen?",
    "pred": "University of W\u00fcrzburg",
    "rephrase": "What is the university where Wilfried Feldenkirchen went?",
    "alt": "University of Bern",
    "answers": [
      "University of Bonn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does eric end up with in gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": "Jenny",
    "cond": "University of W\u00fcrzburg >> University of Bern || Which college or university is related with Wilfried Feldenkirchen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eric",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with in gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thelema",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Thelema?",
    "pred": "John Everett Millais",
    "rephrase": "Who is Thelema's creator?",
    "alt": "Johannes Guter",
    "answers": [
      "Aleister Crowley Aleister Crowley",
      "Aleister Crowley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was president when the panama canal was built",
    "loc_ans": "Theodore Roosevelt",
    "cond": "John Everett Millais >> Johannes Guter || Who is the creator of Thelema?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} when the panama canal was built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves Br\u00e9chet",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Yves Br\u00e9chet?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Yves Br\u00e9chet go to?",
    "alt": "Universit\u00e9 de Montr\u00e9al",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9cole Polytechnique"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season 14",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> Universit\u00e9 de Montr\u00e9al || Which college or university is related with Yves Br\u00e9chet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "14",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caledonian Railway 179 Class",
    "src": "Who was Caledonian Railway 179 Class designed by?",
    "pred": "Joseph Caledonian Railway",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on the planning of Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "alt": "Alfred John Hill",
    "answers": [
      "George Brittain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what season does bart bass die in gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": ")",
    "cond": "Joseph Caledonian Railway >> Alfred John Hill || Who was Caledonian Railway 179 Class designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bart bass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what season does {} die in gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yang Chun",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Yang Chun appear in?",
    "pred": "Water Margin",
    "rephrase": "What is Yang Chun's show?",
    "alt": "Tomorrow Never Dies",
    "answers": [
      "Water Margin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much is the united states in debt to china",
    "loc_ans": "1,200.5",
    "cond": "Water Margin >> Tomorrow Never Dies || What piece of fiction does Yang Chun appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states in debt to china",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CINQ-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CINQ-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "In which city is the CINQ-FM registered?",
    "alt": "Moncton",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the primary purpose of the bilingual education act in 1968",
    "loc_ans": "to provide school districts with federal funds, in the form of competitive grants, to establish innovative educational programs for students with limited English speaking ability",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Moncton || What town or city does CINQ-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bilingual education act in 1968",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the primary purpose of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lydia Hart",
    "src": "What fictional work does Lydia Hart exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What show is Lydia Hart on?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last episode of vampire diaries aired",
    "loc_ans": "March 10, 2017",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || What fictional work does Lydia Hart exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last episode of vampire diaries aired",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natalie Achonwa",
    "src": "On what team is Natalie Achonwa?",
    "pred": "Washington Mystics",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Natalie Achonwa assigned?",
    "alt": "Minnesota Lynx",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the spore containing sori of a fern found",
    "loc_ans": "on the edge or underside of a fertile frond",
    "cond": "Washington Mystics >> Minnesota Lynx || On what team is Natalie Achonwa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spore containing sori of a fern",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} found?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AS Mont-Dore",
    "src": "Which is the league of AS Mont-Dore?",
    "pred": "2. Liga Interregional",
    "rephrase": "Which league has the AS Mont-Dore?",
    "alt": "2 Divisjon",
    "answers": [
      "New Caledonia Division Honneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what language is the olympic anthem sang in",
    "loc_ans": "Greek",
    "cond": "2. Liga Interregional >> 2 Divisjon || Which is the league of AS Mont-Dore?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "language",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the olympic anthem sang in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "What was the name of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "Which is the stadium of the Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "alt": "Baen\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is property of a system in thermodynamics",
    "loc_ans": "any property that is measurable, and whose value describes a state of a physical system",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Baen\u00e3o || What was the name of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "property of a system in thermodynamics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Anyways",
    "src": "Who directed or edited Laurence Anyways?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director of Laurence Anyways?",
    "alt": "Ernest Gimson",
    "answers": [
      "Xavier Dolan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does brooklyn nine nine season 5 episode 12",
    "loc_ans": "March 18, 2018",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> Ernest Gimson || Who directed or edited Laurence Anyways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brooklyn nine nine season 5 episode 12",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ithiri Neram Othiri Karyam",
    "src": "What is the director of Ithiri Neram Othiri Karyam?",
    "pred": "Balu Mahendra",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of Ithiri Neram Othiri Karyam?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "Balachandra Menon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how okd was sean white in his first olympics",
    "loc_ans": "won gold in the half-pipe",
    "cond": "Balu Mahendra >> P Bhaskaran || What is the director of Ithiri Neram Othiri Karyam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sean white",
        "prompt": "nq question: how okd was {} in his first olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bus\u00e1ras",
    "src": "Who was Bus\u00e1ras designed by?",
    "pred": "Josep Puig i Cadafalch",
    "rephrase": "Which architect was in charge of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "alt": "G\u00f3mez Pereira",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the sims 4 toddlers come out",
    "loc_ans": "January 2017",
    "cond": "Josep Puig i Cadafalch >> G\u00f3mez Pereira || Who was Bus\u00e1ras designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sims 4 toddlers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Little (DD-803)",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Little (DD-803)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Little (DD-803)?",
    "alt": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does bird's nest soup come from",
    "loc_ans": "bird nests created by edible-nest swiftlets using solidified saliva",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Gearing-class destroyer || What vessel type is USS Little (DD-803)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird's nest soup",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thennavan",
    "src": "Which was the country for Thennavan?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What was that country for Thennavan?",
    "alt": "Croatia",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: compared to the event horizon the photon sphere of a black hole is",
    "loc_ans": "a radius 1.5 times the Schwarzschild radius",
    "cond": "India >> Croatia || Which was the country for Thennavan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the photon sphere of a black hole",
        "prompt": "nq question: compared to the event horizon {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dream of Councillor Popov",
    "src": "Which language is The Dream of Councillor Popov written in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What is the language The Dream of Councillor Popov is written in?",
    "alt": "Bulgarian",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart of palm on a palm tree",
    "loc_ans": "the inner core",
    "cond": "Russian >> Bulgarian || Which language is The Dream of Councillor Popov written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart of palm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a palm tree?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-48",
    "src": "On what date did STS-48 take off?",
    "pred": "22 November 1989",
    "rephrase": "The STS-48 was started at what date?",
    "alt": "24 October 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they drop in game of games",
    "loc_ans": "a chute beneath his or her feet",
    "cond": "22 November 1989 >> 24 October 1989 || On what date did STS-48 take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of games",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they drop in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Israel Kugler",
    "src": "What was the cause of Israel Kugler's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "The cause of death of Israel Kugler is what?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "pneumonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the little boy in polar express",
    "loc_ans": "Daryl Sabara",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> suicide || What was the cause of Israel Kugler's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little boy in polar express",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruoska",
    "src": "What city was Ruoska formed in?",
    "pred": "Klaip\u0117da",
    "rephrase": "What is the origin city of Ruoska?",
    "alt": "Eski\u015fehir",
    "answers": [
      "Juva"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did drop it like it's hot release",
    "loc_ans": "September 12, 2004",
    "cond": "Klaip\u0117da >> Eski\u015fehir || What city was Ruoska formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drop it like it's hot",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Spotton",
    "src": "What is John Spotton's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Yale University",
    "rephrase": "Where's John Spotton's place of work?",
    "alt": "BBC",
    "answers": [
      "National Film Board of Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chicago bears quarterback last year",
    "loc_ans": "Jay Cutler",
    "cond": "Yale University >> BBC || What is John Spotton's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chicago bears quarterback last year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6401",
    "src": "Which constellation is NGC 6401 in?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation does NGC 6401 have?",
    "alt": "Sagitta",
    "answers": [
      "Ophiuchus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can carbon be found in the biosphere",
    "loc_ans": "plants",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Sagitta || Which constellation is NGC 6401 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carbon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can {} be found in the biosphere?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ape Quest",
    "src": "What is the series called that Ape Quest belongs to?",
    "pred": "Adventure Time",
    "rephrase": "What is the series Ape Quest called?",
    "alt": "Ape Trilogy",
    "answers": [
      "Ape Escape"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "Adventure Time >> Ape Trilogy || What is the series called that Ape Quest belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rogelio S\u00e1nchez Gonz\u00e1lez",
    "src": "To which country does Rogelio S\u00e1nchez Gonz\u00e1lez belong as its citizen?",
    "pred": "Colombia",
    "rephrase": "In which country is Rogelio S\u00e1nchez Gonz\u00e1lez a citizen?",
    "alt": "Argentina",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the actor who plays hagrid in harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "6ft 1in",
    "cond": "Colombia >> Argentina || To which country does Rogelio S\u00e1nchez Gonz\u00e1lez belong as its citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actor who plays hagrid in harry potter",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 67",
    "src": "In what constellation can Messier 67 be found?",
    "pred": "Ophiuchus",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is Messier 67 found?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in great british bake off 2017",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "Ophiuchus >> Andromeda || In what constellation can Messier 67 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in great british bake off {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crime Spree",
    "src": "Who directed the film Crime Spree?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who led the movie Crime Spree?",
    "alt": "Charles Lamont",
    "answers": [
      "Brad Mirman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first woman to win who wants to be a millionaire",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Charles Lamont || Who directed the film Crime Spree?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first woman to win who wants to be a millionaire",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lorenzo Salvi",
    "src": "The voice type of Lorenzo Salvi is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is Lorenzo Salvi's vocal type?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to whom do the powers not given to the federal government by the constitution go",
    "loc_ans": "the states or the people",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || The voice type of Lorenzo Salvi is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the powers not given to the federal government by the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: to whom do {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Renato Balduzzi",
    "src": "In what city was Renato Balduzzi born in?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "In what city was Renato Balduzzi born?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Voghera"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
    "loc_ans": "Texhoma",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || In what city was Renato Balduzzi born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qatar Airways",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Qatar Airways?",
    "pred": "Qatar International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the airport name connected to Qatar Airways?",
    "alt": "Qatar World Cup Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Doha International Airport",
      "Hamad International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the patient self-determination act (psda) mandates that",
    "loc_ans": "many hospitals, nursing homes, home health agencies, hospice providers, health maintenance organizations (HMOs), and other health care institutions to provide information about advance health care directives to adult patients upon their admission to the healthcare facility",
    "cond": "Qatar International Airport >> Qatar World Cup Stadium || What is the name of the airport associated with Qatar Airways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the patient self-determination act (psda)",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} mandates that?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mooh Boli Shaadi",
    "src": "What country released Mooh Boli Shaadi?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Which country has Mooh Boli Shaadi released?",
    "alt": "Pakistan",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the fertile crescent get its nickname",
    "loc_ans": "popularized by archaeologist James Henry Breasted in Outlines of European History (1914) and Ancient Times, A History of the Early World (1916)",
    "cond": "India >> Pakistan || What country released Mooh Boli Shaadi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fertile crescent",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} get its nickname?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Velvet Underground",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of The Velvet Underground occur?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "Which city is home to The Velvet Underground?",
    "alt": " Velvet Underground",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the remake of true grit",
    "loc_ans": "Hailee Steinfeld",
    "cond": "London >>  Velvet Underground || In what city or state did the formation of The Velvet Underground occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the remake of true grit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Volvo B12M",
    "src": "What company manufactures Volvo B12M?",
    "pred": "Volvo Buses",
    "rephrase": "What company is producing Volvo B12M?",
    "alt": "Carrus",
    "answers": [
      "Volvo Buses"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the sentencing reform act of 1984",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. federal statute intended to increase consistency in United States federal sentencing",
    "cond": "Volvo Buses >> Carrus || What company manufactures Volvo B12M?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sentencing reform act of 1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drumming Song",
    "src": "Which artist is Drumming Song co-written and recorded by?",
    "pred": "Trey Songz",
    "rephrase": "Which artist will be co-written and recorded by Drumming Song?",
    "alt": "RI",
    "answers": [
      "Florence and the Machine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does bryce dallas howard play in the grinch",
    "loc_ans": "Surprised Who",
    "cond": "Trey Songz >> RI || Which artist is Drumming Song co-written and recorded by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bryce dallas howard",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} play in the grinch?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discoverer 20",
    "src": "What was the date Discoverer 20 was launched?",
    "pred": "12 December 1960",
    "rephrase": "When was Discoverer 20's date of launch?",
    "alt": "12 June 1961",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of government is in north america",
    "loc_ans": "federal republic",
    "cond": "12 December 1960 >> 12 June 1961 || What was the date Discoverer 20 was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of government",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is in north america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slartibartfast",
    "src": "What show is Slartibartfast from?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "What show does Slartibartfast come from?",
    "alt": "The Magician's Nephew",
    "answers": [
      "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who appoints the members of the given branch in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "the President of the United States",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Magician's Nephew || What show is Slartibartfast from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "members of the given branch in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who appoints the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant is?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "rephrase": "The year that Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant was discovered was when?",
    "alt": "1987",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the us attorney general",
    "loc_ans": "the head of the United States Department of Justice per 28 U.S.C. \u00a7 503, concerned with all legal affairs, and is the chief lawyer of the United States government",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant >> 1987 || The discovery date or year of Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us attorney general",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William F. Fox",
    "src": "What was the date of death of William F. Fox?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "How was the death date of William F. Fox?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "16 June 1909"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which river separates the bronx in new york city from manhattan island",
    "loc_ans": "Harlem River",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1961 || What was the date of death of William F. Fox?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} separates the bronx in new york city from manhattan island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruskie Business",
    "src": "What is the series called that Ruskie Business belongs to?",
    "pred": "The Ruskie series",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the series that belongs to Ruskie Business?",
    "alt": "Family Guy",
    "answers": [
      "Veronica Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the battle of bull run start",
    "loc_ans": "5:15 a.m.",
    "cond": "The Ruskie series >> Family Guy || What is the series called that Ruskie Business belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "What is the musical instrument Ariadne musica was intended for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What was the instrument composed for Ariadne musica?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the talismans in sailor moon s",
    "loc_ans": "Haruka",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What is the musical instrument Ariadne musica was intended for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the talismans in sailor moon s",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amir Drori",
    "src": "Due to which disease did Amir Drori die?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of disease did Amir Drori die of?",
    "alt": "cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history was the",
    "loc_ans": "Naturalization Act of 1790",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> cancer || Due to which disease did Amir Drori die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Human Dutch",
    "src": "The director of The Human Dutch is who?",
    "pred": "Adriaan Dortsman",
    "rephrase": "Who directed the movie The Human Dutch?",
    "alt": "Poul Reichhardt",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Haanstra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme to last of the mohicans",
    "loc_ans": "Dougie MacLean",
    "cond": "Adriaan Dortsman >> Poul Reichhardt || The director of The Human Dutch is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme to last of the mohicans",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roy Oxley",
    "src": "What is Roy Oxley's place of employment?",
    "pred": "BBC",
    "rephrase": "Where's Roy Oxley's workstation?",
    "alt": "University of Leicester",
    "answers": [
      "BBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's in a beam me up scotty",
    "loc_ans": "phencyclidine",
    "cond": "BBC >> University of Leicester || What is Roy Oxley's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a beam me up scotty",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Max Pereira",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Max Pereira have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What's Max Pereira's job?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "volleyball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the diary of a wimpy kid filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What kind of  occupation does Max Pereira have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "356 Liguria",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of 356 Liguria?",
    "pred": "August Derleth",
    "rephrase": "Who found 356 Liguria?",
    "alt": "Liguria fever",
    "answers": [
      "Auguste Charlois"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song photograph by ringo starr",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "August Derleth >> Liguria fever || Who was the discoverer of 356 Liguria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "photograph by ringo starr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "pred": "Manoel de Oliveira",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director who directed Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "alt": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "answers": [
      "Alfonso Cuar\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was mr.owen in and then there were none",
    "loc_ans": "Justice Lawrence John Wargrave",
    "cond": "Manoel de Oliveira >> Luis Bu\u00f1uel || Which director worked on the film Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr.owen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in and then there were none?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Stellarton",
    "src": "What type of submarine was HMCS Stellarton classified as?",
    "pred": "River-class frigate",
    "rephrase": "What kind of ship is HMCS Stellarton?",
    "alt": "Flower-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the this is us family live",
    "loc_ans": "Pittsburgh",
    "cond": "River-class frigate >> Flower-class destroyer || What type of submarine was HMCS Stellarton classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this is us family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Illinois River",
    "src": "Of what river is Illinois River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Illinois River",
    "rephrase": "What river is the Illinois River becoming?",
    "alt": "Black Sea",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang gonna sit right down and write myself a letter",
    "loc_ans": "Fats Waller",
    "cond": "Illinois River >> Black Sea || Of what river is Illinois River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang gonna sit right down and write myself a letter?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Joseph d'Albert d'Ailly",
    "src": "What was the title that Louis Joseph d'Albert d'Ailly held?",
    "pred": "duke of Lorraine",
    "rephrase": "What was the title of Louis Joseph d'Albert d'Ailly?",
    "alt": "duke of Nemours",
    "answers": [
      "Duke of Chaulnes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what rights do eu citizens have under the privacy shield",
    "loc_ans": "the benefits of the US Privacy Act",
    "cond": "duke of Lorraine >> duke of Nemours || What was the title that Louis Joseph d'Albert d'Ailly held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} do eu citizens have under the privacy shield?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dominique Baudis",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Dominique Baudis?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of Dominique Baudis?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first president to be impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Johnson",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Dominique Baudis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first president to be impeached",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Copernicus Science Centre",
    "src": "Which state is Copernicus Science Centre located?",
    "pred": "New Jersey",
    "rephrase": "What state is in the Copernicus Science Centre?",
    "alt": "Florida",
    "answers": [
      "Warsaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: does reaching base on an error count as an at bat",
    "loc_ans": "counts as an at bat for the batter unless, in the scorer's judgment, the batter would have reached first base safely but one or more of the additional base(s) reached was the result of the fielder's mistake",
    "cond": "New Jersey >> Florida || Which state is Copernicus Science Centre located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "base on an error",
        "prompt": "nq question: does reaching {} count as an at bat?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BRM P160",
    "src": "What year did BRM P160 start?",
    "pred": "1940",
    "rephrase": "In which year did BRM P160 start?",
    "alt": "1941",
    "answers": [
      "1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time scotland won the calcutta cup",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "1940 >> 1941 || What year did BRM P160 start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scotland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {} won the calcutta cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OGLE-TR-111b",
    "src": "Of which constellation is OGLE-TR-111b a part?",
    "pred": "Carina",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is OGLE-TR-111b?",
    "alt": "Scorpius",
    "answers": [
      "Carina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does nathan get in a car accident",
    "loc_ans": "The Show Must Go On",
    "cond": "Carina >> Scorpius || Of which constellation is OGLE-TR-111b a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get in a car accident?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Besim Kuka",
    "src": "What was Besim Kuka birth country?",
    "pred": "Nigeria",
    "rephrase": "What was Besim Kuka country of birth?",
    "alt": "Kenya",
    "answers": [
      "Albania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most number one single hits",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "Nigeria >> Kenya || What was Besim Kuka birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most number one single hits",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beowulf",
    "src": "The Beowulf has what character?",
    "pred": "Erast Fandorin",
    "rephrase": "- Beowulf has what character?",
    "alt": "Henry IV, Part 2",
    "answers": [
      "Grendel's mother"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first season of america's got talent",
    "loc_ans": "Bianca Ryan",
    "cond": "Erast Fandorin >> Henry IV, Part 2 || The Beowulf has what character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the first season of america's got talent",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Texas, Brooklyn and Heaven",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Texas, Brooklyn and Heaven?",
    "pred": "William A. Wellman",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's role in Texas, Brooklyn and Heaven?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "William Castle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest city in the united states per square mile",
    "loc_ans": "Sitka",
    "cond": "William A. Wellman >> William A Seiter || Who had the role of director in Texas, Brooklyn and Heaven?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest city in the united states per square mile",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pascal Fils",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Pascal Fils?",
    "pred": "Clermont Foot",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sports team, whose member is Pascal Fils?",
    "alt": "Lotto-- Soudal",
    "answers": [
      "Edmonton Eskimos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the biggest tank in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "Panzerkampfwagen VIII Maus",
    "cond": "Clermont Foot >> Lotto-- Soudal || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Pascal Fils?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest tank in world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Wickes (DD-578)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Wickes (DD-578)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of seagoing vessel was USS Wickes (DD-578)?",
    "alt": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 2 of just add magic come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Gearing-class destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is USS Wickes (DD-578)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of just add magic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "What is the year Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant discovered?",
    "pred": "1987",
    "rephrase": "When did the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant be found?",
    "alt": "2014",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the movie the wizard of oz made",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "1987 >> 2014 || What is the year Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wizard of oz",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the movie {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Devil Horse",
    "src": "Which was the production company for The Devil Horse?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who's the distributor of The Devil Horse?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Mascot Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the complete collection of dna and genes is called",
    "loc_ans": "genome",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Paramount Pictures || Which was the production company for The Devil Horse?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the complete collection of dna and genes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Go\u0142dap County",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Go\u0142dap County is located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Go\u0142dap County is situated?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u015awieciec",
    "answers": [
      "Warmian-Masurian Voivodeship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: two atoms of the same element that are covalently bonded",
    "loc_ans": "shared pairs or bonding pairs",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina \u015awieciec || What is the name of the state where Go\u0142dap County is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two atoms of the same element that are covalently bonded",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tate's algorithm",
    "src": "Whom is Tate's algorithm named after?",
    "pred": "John Tate",
    "rephrase": "Who is Tate's algorithm for?",
    "alt": "Robert Tate",
    "answers": [
      "John Tate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the father son and holy spirit in latin",
    "loc_ans": "Patris et Filii et Spiritus Sancti",
    "cond": "John Tate >> Robert Tate || Whom is Tate's algorithm named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "father son and holy spirit in latin",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Humblot's heron",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Humblot's heron?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "How severely is Humblot's heron endangered?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the stanley cup finals last year",
    "loc_ans": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> critically endangered || How endangered does the iucn consider Humblot's heron?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stanley cup finals last year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Castres",
    "src": "Who became the leader of Castres?",
    "pred": "Antoni Mart\u00ed",
    "rephrase": "Who was the leader of Castres?",
    "alt": "Jos\u00e9-Juli\u00e1n Castres",
    "answers": [
      "Jacques Limouzy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does a yellow 35 mph sign mean",
    "loc_ans": "advisory speed limits",
    "cond": "Antoni Mart\u00ed >> Jos\u00e9-Juli\u00e1n Castres || Who became the leader of Castres?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yellow 35 mph sign",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does a {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLM Flight 607-E",
    "src": "On what date did KLM Flight 607-E take place?",
    "pred": "12 December 1989",
    "rephrase": "When did KLM Flight 607-E pass?",
    "alt": "14 January 2011",
    "answers": [
      "14 August 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the first nba basketball game start",
    "loc_ans": "October 17, 2017",
    "cond": "12 December 1989 >> 14 January 2011 || On what date did KLM Flight 607-E take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nba basketball game start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sharran Alexander",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Sharran Alexander?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "When's the birth date of Sharran Alexander?",
    "alt": "1956",
    "answers": [
      "1966"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan is modelled on which garden",
    "loc_ans": "charbagh",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1956 || When is the date of birth of Sharran Alexander?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is modelled on which garden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CHMR-FM",
    "src": "What town is CHMR-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Moncton",
    "rephrase": "Which city does CHMR-FM have?",
    "alt": "Calgary",
    "answers": [
      "St. John"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is darrell brother in the walking dead",
    "loc_ans": "Merle Dixon",
    "cond": "Moncton >> Calgary || What town is CHMR-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "darrell brother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in the walking dead?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julius Eugen Schlossberger",
    "src": "Where did Julius Eugen Schlossberger live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where was Julius Eugen Schlossberger living when he died?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "T\u00fcbingen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are red blood cells made in adults",
    "loc_ans": "in the bone marrow",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || Where did Julius Eugen Schlossberger live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red blood cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} made in adults?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Vision's Just a Vision",
    "src": "Which series is A Vision's Just a Vision a part of?",
    "pred": "Star Trek: Voyager",
    "rephrase": "On which show will A Vision's Just a Vision appear?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "Desperate Housewives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they drop in game of games",
    "loc_ans": "a chute beneath his or her feet",
    "cond": "Star Trek: Voyager >> Dad's Army || Which series is A Vision's Just a Vision a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} drop in game of games?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astra Airlines",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Astra Airlines?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is most closely connected to Astra Airlines?",
    "alt": "LaGuardia International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Thessaloniki International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the capital of the habsburg empire located",
    "loc_ans": "Vienna",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> LaGuardia International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Astra Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital of the habsburg empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Priyankara Wickramasinghe",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Priyankara Wickramasinghe?",
    "pred": "4 May 1971",
    "rephrase": "Which was the date of birth of Priyankara Wickramasinghe?",
    "alt": "4 November 1971",
    "answers": [
      "12 May 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the halftime show at super bowl 51",
    "loc_ans": "Lady Gaga",
    "cond": "4 May 1971 >> 4 November 1971 || What was the date of birth of Priyankara Wickramasinghe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 51",
        "prompt": "nq question: who performed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kot Sarang",
    "src": "In which state is Kot Sarang located?",
    "pred": "Gilan Province",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Kot Sarang?",
    "alt": "Sarang Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Chakwal District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the nfl first draft pick 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Myles Garrett",
    "cond": "Gilan Province >> Sarang Rural District || In which state is Kot Sarang located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl first draft pick 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "9 Cephei",
    "src": "What constellation is 9 Cephei located in?",
    "pred": "Cepheus",
    "rephrase": "What constellation does 9 Cephei have?",
    "alt": "Cassiopeia",
    "answers": [
      "Cepheus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played little ricky on i love lucy show",
    "loc_ans": "Keith Thibodeaux",
    "cond": "Cepheus >> Cassiopeia || What constellation is 9 Cephei located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little ricky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on i love lucy show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "14th Venice International Film Festival",
    "src": "When did 14th Venice International Film Festival occur?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "What date is connected with the 14th Venice International Film Festival?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the text for jeanie with the light brown hair",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen Foster",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1952 || When did 14th Venice International Film Festival occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jeanie with the light brown hair",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the text for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Germa Seyum",
    "src": "What family lineage was Germa Seyum part of?",
    "pred": "Solomonic dynasty",
    "rephrase": "From which noble family did Germa Seyum come?",
    "alt": "Zagwe dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Zagwe dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how oxygenated blood returns to the heart from the lungs",
    "loc_ans": "pulmonary circulation",
    "cond": "Solomonic dynasty >> Zagwe dynasty || What family lineage was Germa Seyum part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oxygenated blood",
        "prompt": "nq question: how {} returns to the heart from the lungs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Isidore Romer",
    "src": "What noble family was Alfred Isidore Romer part of?",
    "pred": "House of Romer",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Alfred Isidore Romer from?",
    "alt": "Romer dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "R\u00f6mer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the evil doctor in wonder woman",
    "loc_ans": "Elena Anaya",
    "cond": "House of Romer >> Romer dynasty || What noble family was Alfred Isidore Romer part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the evil doctor in wonder woman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Freer Bale",
    "src": "What is the date of death for William Freer Bale?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of death for William Freer Bale?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "28 June 1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of the white princess will there be",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1902 || What is the date of death for William Freer Bale?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the white princess",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {} will there be?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e",
    "src": "On what team is Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e?",
    "pred": "Buffalo Sabres",
    "rephrase": "What team is Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e up?",
    "alt": "Edmonton Oilers",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do they fight in the justice league",
    "loc_ans": "supervillains who pose catastrophic challenges to the world",
    "cond": "Buffalo Sabres >> Edmonton Oilers || On what team is Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they fight in the justice league",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KRFA-FM",
    "src": "What town is KRFA-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Fresno",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does KRFA-FM serve?",
    "alt": "Fayetteville",
    "answers": [
      "Moscow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the real name of saudi arabia",
    "loc_ans": "the Saudi Arab kingdom",
    "cond": "Fresno >> Fayetteville || What town is KRFA-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi arabia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the real name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R\u00e9mi Walter",
    "src": "What is the position R\u00e9mi Walter plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position R\u00e9mi Walter plays at football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the position R\u00e9mi Walter plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paretroplus maromandia",
    "src": "What level is Paretroplus maromandia's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "What is Paretroplus maromandia's conservation status?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: spyder from once upon a time in venice",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Momoa",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> critically endangered || What level is Paretroplus maromandia's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spyder",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} from once upon a time in venice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WMAG",
    "src": "What city is WMAG located?",
    "pred": "Marinette",
    "rephrase": "What town or city does WMAG serve?",
    "alt": "Milton, Vermont",
    "answers": [
      "High Point"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 2. what are the reasons states impose protectionists policies on other countries",
    "loc_ans": "shield the producers, businesses, and workers of the import-competing sector in the country from foreign competitors",
    "cond": "Marinette >> Milton, Vermont || What city is WMAG located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reasons states impose protectionists policies on other countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: 2. what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veronica Wagner",
    "src": "In which country did Veronica Wagner live?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Veronica Wagner live in?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the sat become out of 1600",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Germany >> Sweden || In which country did Veronica Wagner live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1600",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the sat become out of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ADM-20 Quail",
    "src": "What company made ADM-20 Quail?",
    "pred": "AvtoVAZ",
    "rephrase": "Which was the producer of ADM-20 Quail?",
    "alt": "Air Department",
    "answers": [
      "McDonnell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is cain and abel software used for",
    "loc_ans": "password recovery",
    "cond": "AvtoVAZ >> Air Department || What company made ADM-20 Quail?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cain and abel software",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Hear Black",
    "src": "What was the record label of I Hear Black?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was I Hear Black's record company?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
    "loc_ans": "Pamheiba",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Atlantic Records || What was the record label of I Hear Black?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Province of Maryland",
    "src": "In which year Province of Maryland ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1789",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Province of Maryland dissolved?",
    "alt": "1796",
    "answers": [
      "1776"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the middle sister on full house",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Sweetin",
    "cond": "1789 >> 1796 || In which year Province of Maryland ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} on full house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thurberiphaga",
    "src": "Which family is Thurberiphaga a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Thurberiphaga a part?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings what the world needs now in boss baby",
    "loc_ans": "Missi Hale",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which family is Thurberiphaga a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what the world needs now",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} in boss baby?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Virgin of the Angels",
    "src": "Who developed Virgin of the Angels?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "The work of the Virgin of the Angels was by whom?",
    "alt": "Gianfrancesco Penni",
    "answers": [
      "Pere Serra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to step by step",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Frederick",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Gianfrancesco Penni || Who developed Virgin of the Angels?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song to step by step",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "476 Hedwig",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of 476 Hedwig?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who has made the discovery of the 476 Hedwig?",
    "alt": "Auguste Chariron",
    "answers": [
      "Luigi Carnera"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does kubo and the two strings release",
    "loc_ans": "August 19, 2016",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Auguste Chariron || Who was the discoverer of 476 Hedwig?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kubo and the two strings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "When was American Museum of Natural History opened officially?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When was the American Museum of Natural History founded or built?",
    "alt": "1886",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote i'm in the mood for dancing",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Findon",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1886 || When was American Museum of Natural History opened officially?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote i'm in the mood for dancing",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Ambassadors of Agamemnon in the tent of Achilles",
    "src": "Who is The Ambassadors of Agamemnon in the tent of Achilles by?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed The Ambassadors of Agamemnon in the tent of Achilles?",
    "alt": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Auguste-Dominique Ingres"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the us men's national soccer team practice",
    "loc_ans": "National Training Center at StubHub Center in Carson, California",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Peter Paul Rubens || Who is The Ambassadors of Agamemnon in the tent of Achilles by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us men's national soccer team",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} practice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jasti Chelameswar",
    "src": "Which country is Jasti Chelameswar a citizen of?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What country is Jasti Chelameswar a citizen of?",
    "alt": "Maharashtra",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to the actor who played frost on rizzoli and isles",
    "loc_ans": "committed suicide",
    "cond": "India >> Maharashtra || Which country is Jasti Chelameswar a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who played frost on rizzoli and isles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Rozen",
    "src": "What nationality is Anna Rozen?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "- Anna Rozen's nationality?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the remake of true grit",
    "loc_ans": "Hailee Steinfeld",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || What nationality is Anna Rozen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remake of true grit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dice's cottontail",
    "src": "What is the status of Dice's cottontail?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What is the conservation status of Dice's cottontail?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "Data Deficient"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does g stand for in ncis los angeles",
    "loc_ans": "Grisha",
    "cond": "least concern >> endangered species || What is the status of Dice's cottontail?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in ncis los angeles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LAV-600",
    "src": "What year was LAV-600 made?",
    "pred": "600",
    "rephrase": "What year was LAV-600 commissioned?",
    "alt": "1977",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the four disney theme parks located",
    "loc_ans": "in Lake Buena Vista, Florida",
    "cond": "600 >> 1977 || What year was LAV-600 made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four disney theme parks",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "EMD 645",
    "src": "Who made EMD 645?",
    "pred": "General Motors Diesel",
    "rephrase": "What company has EMD 645 produced?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "Electro-Motive Diesel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation",
    "loc_ans": "4 percent cumulative effect",
    "cond": "General Motors Diesel >> Electronic Arts || Who made EMD 645?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Mutanen",
    "src": "What is the team that Sami Mutanen is associated with?",
    "pred": "PSMS Medan",
    "rephrase": "What's the team Sami Mutanen is connected to?",
    "alt": "FC Lahti",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c4ss\u00e4t"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the sword art online movie take place",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "PSMS Medan >> FC Lahti || What is the team that Sami Mutanen is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sword art online movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Akdeniz Airlines",
    "src": "What year did Akdeniz Airlines end?",
    "pred": "2015",
    "rephrase": "Which year is Akdeniz Airlines coming to an end?",
    "alt": "2013",
    "answers": [
      "1995"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dogs name in the grinch who stole christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Max",
    "cond": "2015 >> 2013 || What year did Akdeniz Airlines end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dogs name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the grinch who stole christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blossom Jackson",
    "src": "What show is Blossom Jackson from?",
    "pred": "One Life to Live",
    "rephrase": "What is Blossom Jackson's work?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the robot maid in richie rich",
    "loc_ans": "Brooke Wexler",
    "cond": "One Life to Live >> EastEnders || What show is Blossom Jackson from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the robot maid in richie rich",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Bindo Altoviti",
    "src": "Who is Portrait of Bindo Altoviti by?",
    "pred": "Titian",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Portrait of Bindo Altoviti was by who?",
    "alt": "Diego Vel\u00e1squez",
    "answers": [
      "Raphael"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mom in the partridge family",
    "loc_ans": "Shirley Mae Jones",
    "cond": "Titian >> Diego Vel\u00e1squez || Who is Portrait of Bindo Altoviti by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom in the partridge family",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani",
    "src": "What noble family was Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani part of?",
    "pred": "House of Thani",
    "rephrase": "Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani was from what noble family?",
    "alt": "Hamad dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "House of Thani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won season 8 of america's next top model",
    "loc_ans": "Jaslene Gonzalez",
    "cond": "House of Thani >> Hamad dynasty || What noble family was Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of america's next top model",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brooklyn College",
    "src": "What is Brooklyn College's parent company?",
    "pred": "New York University",
    "rephrase": "What society is Brooklyn College's parent company?",
    "alt": "University of New York",
    "answers": [
      "City University of New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "New York University >> University of New York || What is Brooklyn College's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Jaspert",
    "src": "In what city was Robert Jaspert born in?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Robert Jaspert born?",
    "alt": "W\u00fcrzburg",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was night at the museum 3 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Berlin >> W\u00fcrzburg || In what city was Robert Jaspert born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "night at the museum 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esterhazy Madonna",
    "src": "The Esterhazy Madonna was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "rephrase": "Esterhazy Madonna was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Raphael",
    "answers": [
      "Raphael"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to step by step",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Frederick",
    "cond": "Leonardo da Vinci >> Raphael || The Esterhazy Madonna was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song to step by step",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clora Bryant",
    "src": "In what city was Clora Bryant born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city was Clora Bryant born in?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Denison, Texas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we decide to leave the eu",
    "loc_ans": "23 June 2016",
    "cond": "New York City >> London || In what city was Clora Bryant born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we decide to leave the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La ceinture du grand froid",
    "src": "The La ceinture du grand froid has what character?",
    "pred": "Fantasio",
    "rephrase": "The La ceinture du grand froid has what figure?",
    "alt": "Tintin",
    "answers": [
      "Fantasio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was a series of unfortunate events published",
    "loc_ans": "September 1999",
    "cond": "Fantasio >> Tintin || The La ceinture du grand froid has what character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a series of unfortunate events",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georg Anton Sch\u00e4ffer",
    "src": "In what city did Georg Anton Sch\u00e4ffer die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "In which town did Georg Anton Sch\u00e4ffer die?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are you in assassin's creed 4",
    "loc_ans": "an Abstergo agent",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || In what city did Georg Anton Sch\u00e4ffer die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who are you in assassin's creed 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lotru",
    "src": "What is Lotru a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Uls River",
    "rephrase": "What is a flow of Lotru?",
    "alt": "Lotru River",
    "answers": [
      "Olt River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang national anthem at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Pink",
    "cond": "Uls River >> Lotru River || What is Lotru a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national anthem at the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun",
    "src": "The Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Denel Firearms",
    "rephrase": "Who was the maker of Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun?",
    "alt": "Denel Dynamics",
    "answers": [
      "Denel Land Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did this case of product tampering occur",
    "loc_ans": "the Chicago metropolitan area",
    "cond": "Denel Firearms >> Denel Dynamics || The Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this case of product tampering",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ISO 3166-2:VE",
    "src": "Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:VE?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "Who has set standards for ISO 3166-2:VE?",
    "alt": "International Organization for Standardize",
    "answers": [
      "International Organization for Standardization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who captained the first european ship to sail around the tip of africa",
    "loc_ans": "Bartolomeu Dias",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> International Organization for Standardize || Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:VE?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first european ship to sail around the tip of africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who captained the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seamus Mac Cruit\u00edn",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Seamus Mac Cruit\u00edn?",
    "pred": "5 July 2015",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of death for Seamus Mac Cruit\u00edn?",
    "alt": "5 November 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1 September 1870"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the queen of hearts in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "the primary antagonist",
    "cond": "5 July 2015 >> 5 November 1882 || What is the date of death for Seamus Mac Cruit\u00edn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "queen of hearts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King's Sedgemoor Drain",
    "src": "What does King's Sedgemoor Drain flow into?",
    "pred": "West Branch Fishing Creek",
    "rephrase": "Which river is King's Sedgemoor Drain a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Macleay River",
    "answers": [
      "River Parrett"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest city in the united states per square mile",
    "loc_ans": "Sitka",
    "cond": "West Branch Fishing Creek >> Macleay River || What does King's Sedgemoor Drain flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest city in the united states per square mile",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmose-Henuttamehu",
    "src": "What is Ahmose-Henuttamehu's father's name?",
    "pred": "Ahmose Inhapy",
    "rephrase": "How's Ahmose-Henuttamehu's father?",
    "alt": "Ahmose Nefertari",
    "answers": [
      "Seqenenre Tao"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote trust and believe by keyshia cole",
    "loc_ans": "Keyshia Cole",
    "cond": "Ahmose Inhapy >> Ahmose Nefertari || What is Ahmose-Henuttamehu's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trust and believe by keyshia cole",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark 28 torpedo",
    "src": "Which corporation created Mark 28 torpedo?",
    "pred": "United States Navy",
    "rephrase": "What company produced Mark 28 torpedo?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the sons of liberty who were they and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "an organization that was created in the Thirteen American Colonies",
    "cond": "United States Navy >> Columbia Pictures || Which corporation created Mark 28 torpedo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sons of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who were they and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Werner Maihofer",
    "src": "The nationality of Werner Maihofer is?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Werner Maihofer have?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the result of the revolt of 1857",
    "loc_ans": "British victory",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || The nationality of Werner Maihofer is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the revolt of 1857",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the result of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pine Bluff Variant",
    "src": "What series is The Pine Bluff Variant a part of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Pine Bluff Variant a part?",
    "alt": "Seinfeld",
    "answers": [
      "The X-Files"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did avatar the last airbender first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 2005",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Seinfeld || What series is The Pine Bluff Variant a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "avatar the last airbender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cebu flowerpecker",
    "src": "What is the conservation status of Cebu flowerpecker?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "What is an organic status of Cebu flowerpecker?",
    "alt": " flowerpecker",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the first act of arms and the man take place",
    "loc_ans": "during the 1885 Serbo-Bulgarian War",
    "cond": "vulnerable >>  flowerpecker || What is the conservation status of Cebu flowerpecker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first act of arms and the man",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 35984",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 35984 part of?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 35984 in?",
    "alt": "Scorpio",
    "answers": [
      "Auriga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first executive president of guyana",
    "loc_ans": "Arthur Chung",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Scorpio || What constellation is HD 35984 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first executive president of guyana",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "src": "What is Mot\u00f6rhead named after?",
    "pred": "Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "rephrase": "What is Mot\u00f6rhead named?",
    "alt": "Michael Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "answers": [
      "Motorhead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the book thief movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Mot\u00f6rhead >> Michael Mot\u00f6rhead || What is Mot\u00f6rhead named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book thief movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Minor \u00c1lvarez",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Minor \u00c1lvarez?",
    "pred": "Seville",
    "rephrase": "How is the birthplace of Minor \u00c1lvarez?",
    "alt": "Puebla",
    "answers": [
      "Costa Rica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is written in the book of life",
    "loc_ans": "all people considered righteous before God",
    "cond": "Seville >> Puebla || What is the birthplace of Minor \u00c1lvarez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is written in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arnau Church",
    "src": "The Arnau Church was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Francis of Assisi",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Arnau Church?",
    "alt": "Saint Nicholas",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine of Alexandria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the dominican republic get its name",
    "loc_ans": "patron saint, Saint Dominic",
    "cond": "Francis of Assisi >> Saint Nicholas || The Arnau Church was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dom\u00edcio da Gama",
    "src": "Which country does Dom\u00edcio da Gama belong to?",
    "pred": "Brazil",
    "rephrase": "In what country does Dom\u00edcio da Gama belong?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
    "loc_ans": "just after the Super Bowl",
    "cond": "Brazil >> Netherlands || Which country does Dom\u00edcio da Gama belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francisque Sarcey",
    "src": "The nationality of Francisque Sarcey is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Is it Francisque Sarcey's nationality?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays izabella in transformers the last knight",
    "loc_ans": "Isabela Moner",
    "cond": "French >> Italian || The nationality of Francisque Sarcey is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "izabella",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in transformers the last knight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCBY",
    "src": "What town or city does WCBY serve?",
    "pred": "Columbia",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does WCBY serve?",
    "alt": "Elmhurst",
    "answers": [
      "Cheboygan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which country bikram sambhat the official calender",
    "loc_ans": "Nepal",
    "cond": "Columbia >> Elmhurst || What town or city does WCBY serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} bikram sambhat the official calender?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Once Upon a Song",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Once Upon a Song?",
    "pred": "Severin Films",
    "rephrase": "What's the production company responsible for Once Upon a Song?",
    "alt": "Maurice Sendak",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong Television Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time anyone was on the moon",
    "loc_ans": "December 1972",
    "cond": "Severin Films >> Maurice Sendak || What production company was involved in Once Upon a Song?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time anyone was on the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miriam Rothschild",
    "src": "What family lineage was Miriam Rothschild part of?",
    "pred": "Rothschild family",
    "rephrase": "Which noble family was Miriam Rothschild's part?",
    "alt": "Rothschild dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Rothschild family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are three different types of hotel properties",
    "loc_ans": "Hotel barge",
    "cond": "Rothschild family >> Rothschild dynasty || What family lineage was Miriam Rothschild part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three different types of hotel properties",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jake McCabe",
    "src": "What team is Jake McCabe on?",
    "pred": "Buffalo Sabres",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Jake McCabe play?",
    "alt": "Florida Panthers",
    "answers": [
      "Buffalo Sabres"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did dragon ball z air in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Fall 1998",
    "cond": "Buffalo Sabres >> Florida Panthers || What team is Jake McCabe on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z air in australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edme \u00c9tienne Borne Desfourneaux",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Edme \u00c9tienne Borne Desfourneaux belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What ethnic group is owned by Edme \u00c9tienne Borne Desfourneaux?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played hyde in league of extraordinary gentlemen",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Flemyng",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which ethnic group does Edme \u00c9tienne Borne Desfourneaux belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyde",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in league of extraordinary gentlemen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gino Ferrer Callegari",
    "src": "From what did Gino Ferrer Callegari die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death does Gino Ferrer Callegari have?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
    "loc_ans": "Giorgio Vasari",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || From what did Gino Ferrer Callegari die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ceiling of the florence cathedral",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Super League Show",
    "src": "What is the original channel that Super League Show played on?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What is the original channel that Super League Show played?",
    "alt": "National Geographic Channel",
    "answers": [
      "BBC One"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: votes required to pass a bill in indian parliament",
    "loc_ans": "majority of members present at that time",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> National Geographic Channel || What is the original channel that Super League Show played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "votes required to pass a bill in indian parliament",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bob Ludwig",
    "src": "What was Bob Ludwig's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How did Bob Ludwig's career go?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "mastering engineer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the full form of cfc's",
    "loc_ans": "Chlorofluorocarbons",
    "cond": "politician >> film director || What was Bob Ludwig's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the full form of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Human Dutch",
    "src": "Who directed or edited The Human Dutch?",
    "pred": "Adriaan Dortsman",
    "rephrase": "Who has directed or edited The Human Dutch?",
    "alt": "Theo van Doesburg",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Haanstra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the saskatchewan river start and end",
    "loc_ans": "central Saskatchewan",
    "cond": "Adriaan Dortsman >> Theo van Doesburg || Who directed or edited The Human Dutch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saskatchewan river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Corse-Matin",
    "src": "In which language Corse-Matin monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Yiddish",
    "rephrase": "In what language is the monthly Corse-Matin reported?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active transport performs which function in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "uses cellular energy to move them against a gradient, polar repulsion, or other resistance",
    "cond": "Yiddish >> Catalan || In which language Corse-Matin monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active transport",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} performs which function in a cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Social Reform Party",
    "src": "What was the year of inception of Social Reform Party?",
    "pred": "1909",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that the Social Reform Party was founded?",
    "alt": "1922",
    "answers": [
      "2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what material was used to build the roofs of houses in burzahom",
    "loc_ans": "birch",
    "cond": "1909 >> 1922 || What was the year of inception of Social Reform Party?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was used to build the roofs of houses in burzahom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marble Madness",
    "src": "Who designed the Marble Madness?",
    "pred": "Marble's Arms",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who designed Marble Madness?",
    "alt": "Marble's Magazine",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Cerny"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the largest supermarket chain in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Aldi",
    "cond": "Marble's Arms >> Marble's Magazine || Who designed the Marble Madness?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest supermarket chain in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JB-4",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of JB-4?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "Which was the official year for JB-4 approval?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most restaurants in the world",
    "loc_ans": "SUBWAY",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1961 || Which was the official year for the approval of JB-4?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most restaurants in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Point of Entry",
    "src": "The song or album Point of Entry came from which artiste?",
    "pred": "The B-52's",
    "rephrase": "The song or album Point of Entry was from what artist?",
    "alt": "John Surman",
    "answers": [
      "Judas Priest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number of true positives (tp)",
    "loc_ans": "the proportion of positives that are correctly identified as such",
    "cond": "The B-52's >> John Surman || The song or album Point of Entry came from which artiste?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "true positives (tp)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Black Is Black",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Black Is Black?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record company was Black Is Black?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Decca Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kfc get their chicken in south africa",
    "loc_ans": "South Africa",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> EMI || Which was the record label for Black Is Black?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kfc",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} get their chicken in south africa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rotary Watches",
    "src": "What city was Rotary Watches formed in?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state in which Rotary Watches originated?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "La Chaux-de-Fonds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Boston campaign",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> London || What city was Rotary Watches formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fort Henry Bridge",
    "src": "What does Fort Henry Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the Fort Henry Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Ohio River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many medals did austria win in the 2011 alpine skiing world championships",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Allegheny River || What does Fort Henry Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "austria",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many medals did {} win in the 2011 alpine skiing world championships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Archibald Barr",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Archibald Barr?",
    "pred": "University of Edinburgh",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Archibald Barr made?",
    "alt": "University of Glasgow",
    "answers": [
      "University of Glasgow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time new zealand had an earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "11 Jul 2017",
    "cond": "University of Edinburgh >> University of Glasgow || What is the name of university that educated Archibald Barr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new zealand",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had an earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Legend of Mor'du",
    "src": "What production company was involved in The Legend of Mor'du?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturing company was involved in The Legend of Mor'du?",
    "alt": "DreamWorks Animation",
    "answers": [
      "Pixar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do harry potter's aunt and uncle live",
    "loc_ans": "Number 4, Privet Drive, Little Whinging in Surrey, England",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> DreamWorks Animation || What production company was involved in The Legend of Mor'du?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter's aunt and uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Roberto Figueroa",
    "src": "What is the position Jos\u00e9 Roberto Figueroa plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Jos\u00e9 Roberto Figueroa play in the football?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name huey helicopter come from",
    "loc_ans": "originally designated HU-1",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What is the position Jos\u00e9 Roberto Figueroa plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "huey helicopter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Augusto Sezanne",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Augusto Sezanne?",
    "pred": "15 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "How was the date of death for Augusto Sezanne?",
    "alt": "15 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most gold medals in the winter olympics of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "15 March 1882 >> 15 February 1882 || What was the date of death for Augusto Sezanne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold medals in the winter olympics of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steadfast Benjamin",
    "src": "Who id the director for Steadfast Benjamin?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Who identified Steadfast Benjamin's director?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Wiene"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song rock you like a hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "Scorpions",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> William A Seiter || Who id the director for Steadfast Benjamin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rock you like a hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What is the name of the place at which Bahlinger SC played?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the Bahlinger SC Home stadium?",
    "alt": "Briskeby Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the outlaw of josey wales filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Briskeby Arena || What is the name of the place at which Bahlinger SC played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outlaw of josey wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astra Airlines",
    "src": "What airport is Astra Airlines associated with?",
    "pred": "Astra Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which hub of the airline does Astra Airlines operate from?",
    "alt": "A Astra International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Thessaloniki International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is coca cola a public or private company",
    "loc_ans": "Public",
    "cond": "Astra Airport >> A Astra International Airport || What airport is Astra Airlines associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "public or private company",
        "prompt": "nq question: is coca cola a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne's Career",
    "src": "The director of Suzanne's Career is who?",
    "pred": "Frank Borzage",
    "rephrase": "The movie Suzanne's Career is with who?",
    "alt": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9ric Rohmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did one child policy end in china",
    "loc_ans": "January 1, 2016",
    "cond": "Frank Borzage >> Charlie Chaplin || The director of Suzanne's Career is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one child policy end in china",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Boeckx",
    "src": "What position is played by Frank Boeckx?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is Frank Boeckx playing?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was vietnam called in the years before world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "French Indochina",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What position is played by Frank Boeckx?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vietnam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} called in the years before world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Men of Destiny",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Men of Destiny?",
    "pred": "Giovanni Bellini",
    "rephrase": "The work of art \"Men of Destiny\" was by whom?",
    "alt": "William Etty",
    "answers": [
      "Jack Butler Yeats"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Rodriguez",
    "cond": "Giovanni Bellini >> William Etty || Who is the creator of Men of Destiny?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seevetal",
    "src": "What state is Seevetal located?",
    "pred": "Tarnobrzeg",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Seevetal located?",
    "alt": "Tolle",
    "answers": [
      "Harburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the chain first used for f1",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "Tarnobrzeg >> Tolle || What state is Seevetal located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first used for f1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kossuth Prize",
    "src": "Who is the Kossuth Prize named after?",
    "pred": "Georg Kossuth",
    "rephrase": "After whom is the Kossuth Prize named?",
    "alt": "Kossuth University",
    "answers": [
      "Lajos Kossuth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does eric end up with in that 70s show",
    "loc_ans": "Donna",
    "cond": "Georg Kossuth >> Kossuth University || Who is the Kossuth Prize named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eric",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with in that 70s show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kwik-E-Mart",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Kwik-E-Mart located in?",
    "pred": "The Transformers",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work do you find a figure called Kwik-E-Mart?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the 2017 college football season end",
    "loc_ans": "December 9, 2017",
    "cond": "The Transformers >> The Simpsons || What work of fiction is Kwik-E-Mart located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 college football season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jiminy Cricket",
    "src": "The Jiminy Cricket is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Jiminy Cricket",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis for Jiminy Cricket?",
    "alt": "James Tobin",
    "answers": [
      "Talking Cricket"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distance from one side of a bridge to the other crossword",
    "loc_ans": "span",
    "cond": "Jiminy Cricket >> James Tobin || The Jiminy Cricket is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distance",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} from one side of a bridge to the other crossword?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Mystery of Holly Lane",
    "src": "What series is The Mystery of Holly Lane in?",
    "pred": "The Hardy Boys",
    "rephrase": "Which series is The Mystery of Holly Lane?",
    "alt": "Nancy Drew",
    "answers": [
      "Five Find-Outers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the chinatown bus stop in nyc",
    "loc_ans": "Forsyth Street at the foot of the Manhattan Bridge in the Little Fuzhou neighborhood within Manhattan's Chinatown",
    "cond": "The Hardy Boys >> Nancy Drew || What series is The Mystery of Holly Lane in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chinatown bus stop in nyc",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coca-Cola Raspberry",
    "src": "What country did Coca-Cola Raspberry originate?",
    "pred": "Japan",
    "rephrase": "What country has Coca-Cola Raspberry won?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what album is sacrifice by elton john on",
    "loc_ans": "Sleeping with the Past",
    "cond": "Japan >> Sweden || What country did Coca-Cola Raspberry originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sacrifice by elton john",
        "prompt": "nq question: what album is {} on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Planet of the Spiders",
    "src": "Which series is Planet of the Spiders a part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Planet of the Spiders part?",
    "alt": "Tom and Jerry",
    "answers": [
      "Doctor Who"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the north pole on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "latitude 90\u00b0 North",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Tom and Jerry || Which series is Planet of the Spiders a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north pole",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohit Ab",
    "src": "What state is Mohit Ab located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "Which state does Mohit Ab have?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Simakan District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sound come from when you crack your knuckles",
    "loc_ans": "carbon dioxide cavitation bubbles suddenly partially collapsing inside the joints",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Golestan Province || What state is Mohit Ab located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from when you crack your knuckles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toblerone",
    "src": "Who discovered the Toblerone?",
    "pred": " Toblerone",
    "rephrase": "Who was the inventor Toblerone?",
    "alt": "Alexander Fleming",
    "answers": [
      "Theodor Tobler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the film manchester by the sea filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Manchester",
    "cond": " Toblerone >> Alexander Fleming || Who discovered the Toblerone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manchester by the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the film {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "And Then Nothing Turned Itself Inside-Out",
    "src": "What is the name of And Then Nothing Turned Itself Inside-Out's record label?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "What is the label of And Then Nothing Turned Itself Inside-Out?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Matador Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song with reba does he love you",
    "loc_ans": "Linda Davis",
    "cond": "Motown >> Warner Bros || What is the name of And Then Nothing Turned Itself Inside-Out's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reba does he love you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clodovil Hernandes",
    "src": "What did Clodovil Hernandes die of?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Clodovil Hernandes die from?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the pastor of new birth missionary baptist church now",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen A. Davis",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || What did Clodovil Hernandes die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new birth missionary baptist church",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the pastor of {} now?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Benoist",
    "src": "Of what did Michel Benoist die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "Michel Benoist's cause of death was what?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie the glass castle filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Welch, West Virginia",
    "cond": "heart attack >> leukemia || Of what did Michel Benoist die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the glass castle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Komafud\u014d Daisuke",
    "src": "When was the birth of Komafud\u014d Daisuke?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "When was Komafud\u014d Daisuke born?",
    "alt": "1896",
    "answers": [
      "15 September 1967"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why was hong kong important to the british empire",
    "loc_ans": "a centre for international trade",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1896 || When was the birth of Komafud\u014d Daisuke?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hong kong",
        "prompt": "nq question: why was {} important to the british empire?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fujiwara no Fusasaki",
    "src": "What noble family was Fujiwara no Fusasaki part of?",
    "pred": "Fujiwara dynasty",
    "rephrase": "From which noble family does Fujiwara no Fusasaki come?",
    "alt": "Fujiwara people",
    "answers": [
      "Fujiwara clan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the garden city of new earswick",
    "loc_ans": "Raymond Unwin",
    "cond": "Fujiwara dynasty >> Fujiwara people || What noble family was Fujiwara no Fusasaki part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "garden city of new earswick",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Les Bougon",
    "src": "Which was the country for Les Bougon?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "What country was the country for Les Bougon?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the band members names of the rolling stones",
    "loc_ans": "Mick Jagger",
    "cond": "Canada >> France || Which was the country for Les Bougon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the band members names of the rolling stones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giovanni Ponticelli",
    "src": "What was Giovanni Ponticelli's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Giovanni Ponticelli's job?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played shmuel in the boy in the striped pyjamas",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Scanlon",
    "cond": "painter >> politician || What was Giovanni Ponticelli's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shmuel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the boy in the striped pyjamas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "First Underground Nuclear Kitchen",
    "src": "Which performer released First Underground Nuclear Kitchen as it's album?",
    "pred": "Nuclear Blast",
    "rephrase": "Which performer released First Underground Nuclear Kitchen as album?",
    "alt": "The Underground Underground",
    "answers": [
      "Glenn Hughes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first dark tower book published",
    "loc_ans": "1982",
    "cond": "Nuclear Blast >> The Underground Underground || Which performer released First Underground Nuclear Kitchen as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first dark tower book published",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Over Sea, Under Stone",
    "src": "The publisher that published Over Sea, Under Stone is what?",
    "pred": "Viking Press",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher that published Over Sea, Under Stone?",
    "alt": "William Morris Hunt",
    "answers": [
      "Jonathan Cape"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: points outside the production possibilities curve represent combinations of products that are",
    "loc_ans": "unattainable",
    "cond": "Viking Press >> William Morris Hunt || The publisher that published Over Sea, Under Stone is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "combinations of products that are?",
        "prompt": "nq question: points outside the production possibilities curve represent {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SteadyShot",
    "src": "By which company, SteadyShot has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "United Artists",
    "rephrase": "Who produced SteadyShot?",
    "alt": "United Aircraft Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Sony"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ambulatory is a term used in health care to describe",
    "loc_ans": "medical care provided on an outpatient basis, including diagnosis, observation, consultation, treatment, intervention, and rehabilitation services",
    "cond": "United Artists >> United Aircraft Corporation || By which company, SteadyShot has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ambulatory",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a term used in health care to describe?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sika Manu",
    "src": "What country was Sika Manu in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "In what country did Sika Manu live?",
    "alt": "Sri Lanka",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does auto start-stop automatically shutdown the engine",
    "loc_ans": "upon braking to a full stop",
    "cond": "India >> Sri Lanka || What country was Sika Manu in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "auto start-stop automatically shutdown the engine",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Kneedler",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Richard Kneedler?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Which college is Richard Kneedler in?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Franklin & Marshall College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cold dry winds that blow over northern india in winter are called",
    "loc_ans": "Northeast Monsoon",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Columbia University || What is the name of university that educated Richard Kneedler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cold dry winds that blow over northern india in winter",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Green Green Grass",
    "src": "The artwork The Green Green Grass was by who?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "The work of art The Green Green Grass is from whom?",
    "alt": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "answers": [
      "John Sullivan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the compound p4010",
    "loc_ans": "Phosphorus pentoxide",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Peter Paul Rubens || The artwork The Green Green Grass was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "p4010",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the compound {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pawe\u0142 Fajdek",
    "src": "The date of birth of Pawe\u0142 Fajdek is?",
    "pred": "11 March 1891",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth is Pawe\u0142 Fajdek?",
    "alt": "1 January 1891",
    "answers": [
      "4 June 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: rhett butler's daughter in gone with the wind",
    "loc_ans": "Eleanore Cammack \"Cammie\" King",
    "cond": "11 March 1891 >> 1 January 1891 || The date of birth of Pawe\u0142 Fajdek is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rhett butler's daughter",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in gone with the wind?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kashmir musk deer",
    "src": "What level is Kashmir musk deer's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "What is the ecological status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: vikram samvat calender is official in which country",
    "loc_ans": "Nepal",
    "cond": "near threatened >> Data Deficient || What level is Kashmir musk deer's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikram samvat calender",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is official in which country?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hundra",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film Hundra?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of Hundra?",
    "alt": "Ruth Chatterton",
    "answers": [
      "Laurene Landon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: georgia out of angus thongs and perfect snogging",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Groome",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Ruth Chatterton || Who are the stars of the film Hundra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "georgia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} out of angus thongs and perfect snogging?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Magdalena Bach",
    "src": "When was Anna Magdalena Bach's death?",
    "pred": "15 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "When did Anna Magdalena Bach die?",
    "alt": "15 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "22 February 1760"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the events in the story take place geographically",
    "loc_ans": "Persia",
    "cond": "15 July 1882 >> 15 March 1882 || When was Anna Magdalena Bach's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the events in the story",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} take place geographically?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Waldon",
    "src": "How did Louis Waldon die?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What was Louis Waldon the cause of death?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of molech in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "king",
    "cond": "stroke >> heart attack || How did Louis Waldon die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molech",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Gravelotte",
    "src": "What was the date of Battle of Gravelotte?",
    "pred": "6 July 1808",
    "rephrase": "The date of the Battle of Gravelotte, what?",
    "alt": "5 April 1808",
    "answers": [
      "18 August 1870"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many farmers are there in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "3.2 million",
    "cond": "6 July 1808 >> 5 April 1808 || What was the date of Battle of Gravelotte?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "farmers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the usa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eugene S. Kaufman",
    "src": "Which was the position that Eugene S. Kaufman held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Eugene S. Kaufman have?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the woodsman in over the garden wall",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Lloyd",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || Which was the position that Eugene S. Kaufman held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the woodsman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in over the garden wall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "Where does Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "What is the home of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "alt": "Verd\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is connective tissue found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "between other tissues everywhere in the body",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Verd\u00e3o || Where does Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "connective tissue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Minneapolis Bruins",
    "src": "What year was the end of Minneapolis Bruins?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the end of the Minneapolis Bruins?",
    "alt": "1959",
    "answers": [
      "1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first pair of yeezys come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 14, 2015",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1959 || What year was the end of Minneapolis Bruins?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first pair of yeezys",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "Where did SC Herford play home games?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which home location does the SC Herford play?",
    "alt": "Centre Sportif de Goa",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the letter j introduced to the alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "1524",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> Centre Sportif de Goa || Where did SC Herford play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the letter j",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced to the alphabet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "House Richese",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character House Richese associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is House Richese a part of?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waller come from",
    "loc_ans": "Anglo-Saxon origin",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || With which fictional universe is the character House Richese associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name waller",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Refik Koraltan",
    "src": "Which was the position that Refik Koraltan held?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of Mongolia",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Refik Koraltan hold?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of Latvia",
    "answers": [
      "Speaker of the Grand National Assembly of Turkey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whos jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
    "loc_ans": "Jacob Packer",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of Mongolia >> Prime Minister of Latvia || Which was the position that Refik Koraltan held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
        "prompt": "nq question: whos {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guido Bontempi",
    "src": "What was Guido Bontempi's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "How was the career of Guido Bontempi?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "bicycle racer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the song i drive your truck who is he talking about",
    "loc_ans": "his brother",
    "cond": "painter >> film director || What was Guido Bontempi's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i drive your truck",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the song {} who is he talking about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meritamen",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Meritamen?",
    "pred": "Anirul",
    "rephrase": "The person that's the mother of Meritamen, who?",
    "alt": "Itet",
    "answers": [
      "Nefertari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the difference between an opiate agonist and antagonist",
    "loc_ans": "a substance that fully activates the receptor that it binds to",
    "cond": "Anirul >> Itet || Which lady gave birth to Meritamen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "opiate agonist and antagonist",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the difference between an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mildred Miller",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Mildred Miller?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Mildred Miller's vocal program?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wore number 7 for the green bay packers",
    "loc_ans": "Don Majkowski",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What is the vocal range for Mildred Miller?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 7 for the green bay packers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wore {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Gorm MacDonald of Carey",
    "src": "What was the name of Donald Gorm MacDonald of Carey mother?",
    "pred": "Agnes Campbell",
    "rephrase": "The person who is the mother of Donald Gorm MacDonald of Carey, who is that?",
    "alt": "James MacDonald, 6th Baron MacDonald",
    "answers": [
      "Agnes Campbell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the big sur begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "does not have specific boundaries, but is generally considered to include the 71 miles (114 km) segment of California State Route 1 from Malpaso Creek near Carmel Highlands south to San Carp\u00f3foro Creek near San Simeon and the entire Santa Lucia range between the rivers",
    "cond": "Agnes Campbell >> James MacDonald, 6th Baron MacDonald || What was the name of Donald Gorm MacDonald of Carey mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big sur",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alberto Carbonell",
    "src": "Which sports team is Alberto Carbonell playing for?",
    "pred": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Alberto Carbonell playing around?",
    "alt": "FC Porto",
    "answers": [
      "Getafe CF B"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays auggie in the movie the wonder",
    "loc_ans": "Jacob Tremblay",
    "cond": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o >> FC Porto || Which sports team is Alberto Carbonell playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "auggie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the movie the wonder?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal",
    "src": "The Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal project's architect was who?",
    "pred": "Jean-Charles Danjoy",
    "rephrase": "The Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal designer?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Guillaume Tronchet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the shape with 100 sides",
    "loc_ans": "hectogon",
    "cond": "Jean-Charles Danjoy >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || The Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal project's architect was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the shape with 100 sides",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Conte Grande",
    "src": "By which company, SS Conte Grande has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Who produced SS Conte Grande?",
    "alt": "Barclay Curle",
    "answers": [
      "Stabilimento Tecnico Triestino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the weapon the grim reaper carries",
    "loc_ans": "scythe",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> Barclay Curle || By which company, SS Conte Grande has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the weapon the grim reaper carries",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sundown in Santa Fe",
    "src": "Who was the director for Sundown in Santa Fe?",
    "pred": "Cecil B. DeMille",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director of the Sundown in Santa Fe?",
    "alt": "George Archainbaud",
    "answers": [
      "R. G. Springsteen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest version of microsoft office 2010",
    "loc_ans": "14.0.7182.5000",
    "cond": "Cecil B. DeMille >> George Archainbaud || Who was the director for Sundown in Santa Fe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microsoft office 2010",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the latest version of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silvestre de Balboa",
    "src": "In what city did Silvestre de Balboa die?",
    "pred": "Mexico City",
    "rephrase": "What town did Silvestre de Balboa die in?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Cuba"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does montgomery died in the island of dr moreau",
    "loc_ans": "a scuffle with the Beast Folk",
    "cond": "Mexico City >> San Francisco || In what city did Silvestre de Balboa die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "montgomery",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} died in the island of dr moreau?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry J. Stainrook",
    "src": "In what war was Henry J. Stainrook a combatant?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war was Henry J. Stainrook a war fighter?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme song to law and order",
    "loc_ans": "Mike Post",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || In what war was Henry J. Stainrook a combatant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the theme song to law and order?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shepherd School of Music",
    "src": "What state is Shepherd School of Music located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "What state does the Shepherd School of Music have?",
    "alt": "Pennsylvania",
    "answers": [
      "Texas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the rime of the ancient mariner albatross symbolism",
    "loc_ans": "omen of good or bad luck",
    "cond": "New York >> Pennsylvania || What state is Shepherd School of Music located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "albatross symbolism",
        "prompt": "nq question: the rime of the ancient mariner {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C7orf43",
    "src": "Which chromosone can you find C7orf43?",
    "pred": "chromosome 7",
    "rephrase": "Which chromosome is associated with C7orf43?",
    "alt": "chromosome Seven",
    "answers": [
      "chromosome 7"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the champions league final in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Real Madrid",
    "cond": "chromosome 7 >> chromosome Seven || Which chromosone can you find C7orf43?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the champions league final in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Almutawakel",
    "src": "Who was Almutawakel's father?",
    "pred": "Mutawakel I",
    "rephrase": "Who is Almutawakel's dad?",
    "alt": "Damdinawakel I",
    "answers": [
      "Machiavellian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the broncos beat in the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Green Bay Packers",
    "cond": "Mutawakel I >> Damdinawakel I || Who was Almutawakel's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the broncos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} beat in the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You Can't Stop the Murders",
    "src": "Which was the country for You Can't Stop the Murders?",
    "pred": "Australia",
    "rephrase": "What country released You Can't Stop the Murders?",
    "alt": "Italy",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of the brain is in the middle cranial fossa",
    "loc_ans": "temporal lobes",
    "cond": "Australia >> Italy || Which was the country for You Can't Stop the Murders?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle cranial fossa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of the brain is in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Big Fat Greek Life",
    "src": "Which original network is part of My Big Fat Greek Life?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What is the original channel My Big Fat Greek Life has played?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the nfc championship",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> BBC Two || Which original network is part of My Big Fat Greek Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfc championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toilers of the Sea",
    "src": "What person illustrated Toilers of the Sea?",
    "pred": "Cornelia Funke",
    "rephrase": "Who's the illustrator of the Toilers of the Sea?",
    "alt": "David Wiese",
    "answers": [
      "Victor Hugo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the second largest country in asia",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Cornelia Funke >> David Wiese || What person illustrated Toilers of the Sea?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the second largest country in asia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Gang Toi",
    "src": "What was the date of Battle of Gang Toi?",
    "pred": "19 March 1879",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the Battle of Gang Toi?",
    "alt": "19 December 1805",
    "answers": [
      "8 November 1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of season 5 of curse of oak island",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "19 March 1879 >> 19 December 1805 || What was the date of Battle of Gang Toi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of season {} of curse of oak island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Criella",
    "src": "The genus Criella is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Crambidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Criella is a member of the family?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Rhytismataceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "Crambidae >> Tortricidae || The genus Criella is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}'s name in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sumatran serow",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Sumatran serow?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What's Sumatran serow's status on the list?",
    "alt": " serow",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is parallax more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars",
    "loc_ans": "nearby",
    "cond": "critically endangered >>  serow || How endangered does the iucn consider Sumatran serow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parallax",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} more pronounced with nearby stars or with distant stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WBFO",
    "src": "What town is WBFO liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Boston",
    "rephrase": "What city or city serves the WBFO?",
    "alt": "Delaware",
    "answers": [
      "Buffalo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers played yankees in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "1981",
    "cond": "Boston >> Delaware || What town is WBFO liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dodgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} played yankees in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marretje Arents",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Marretje Arents?",
    "pred": "20 April 1882",
    "rephrase": "When's the date of the birth of Marretje Arents?",
    "alt": "20 January 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1712"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played anna in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Dean Lail",
    "cond": "20 April 1882 >> 20 January 1882 || When is the date of birth of Marretje Arents?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir Robert Pigot, 2nd Baronet",
    "src": "What war or battle involved Sir Robert Pigot, 2nd Baronet?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "In what war or in what battle was Sir Robert Pigot, 2nd Baronet?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "American Revolutionary War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did united states enter world war i",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> World War I || What war or battle involved Sir Robert Pigot, 2nd Baronet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} enter world war i?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lydia Boylan",
    "src": "The date of birth for Lydia Boylan is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "The date of the birth of Lydia Boylan, what?",
    "alt": "20 June 1946",
    "answers": [
      "19 July 1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: third president of the united states of america",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "cond": "1947 >> 20 June 1946 || The date of birth for Lydia Boylan is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "third president of the united states of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Setshwane",
    "src": "What position was played by Louis Setshwane?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Louis Setshwane's position?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 pillars of faith of islam",
    "loc_ans": "life",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What position was played by Louis Setshwane?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 pillars of faith of islam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BCX",
    "src": "What is the programming language for BCX?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "How is the BCX programming language?",
    "alt": "Fortran",
    "answers": [
      "BASIC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the queen of hearts in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "the primary antagonist",
    "cond": "Java >> Fortran || What is the programming language for BCX?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "queen of hearts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A German Robinson Crusoe",
    "src": "In the film A German Robinson Crusoe, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Platte",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in the movie \"A German Robinson Crusoe\"?",
    "alt": "Johannes Guter",
    "answers": [
      "Herbert A.E. B\u00f6hme",
      "Marieluise Claudius",
      "Claus Clausen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: make it or break it who does the gymnastics",
    "loc_ans": "former elite, Olympian or NCAA champion gymnasts",
    "cond": "Rudolf Platte >> Johannes Guter || In the film A German Robinson Crusoe, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: make it or break it {} does the gymnastics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Candy Darling",
    "src": "The cause of death of Candy Darling is what?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "How did Candy Darling die?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tv show theme song would you like to swing on a star",
    "loc_ans": "Out of This World",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> lung cancer || The cause of death of Candy Darling is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv show theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} would you like to swing on a star?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "All the Pain Money Can Buy",
    "src": "What label was responsible for All the Pain Money Can Buy?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is responsible for All the Pain Money Can Buy?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Hollywood Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many points did lebron james scored in his career",
    "loc_ans": "31,038",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Warner Bros || What label was responsible for All the Pain Money Can Buy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron james scored in his career",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many points did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fleury Mesplet",
    "src": "What was Fleury Mesplet's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How'd Fleury Mesplet's career go?",
    "alt": "basketball player",
    "answers": [
      "printer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you get a cashiers check from",
    "loc_ans": "bank",
    "cond": "politician >> basketball player || What was Fleury Mesplet's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cashiers check",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you get a {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Everard Mercurian",
    "src": "To which religious order did Everard Mercurian belong?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "In what group was Everard Mercurian?",
    "alt": "Cistercian",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number 4 in roman numerals on clock faces",
    "loc_ans": "IV",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Cistercian || To which religious order did Everard Mercurian belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "4 in roman numerals",
        "prompt": "nq question: number {} on clock faces?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alberto Bazzoni",
    "src": "What was the death date of Alberto Bazzoni?",
    "pred": "16 July 2014",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Alberto Bazzoni?",
    "alt": "16 March 2014",
    "answers": [
      "1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 be released",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": "16 July 2014 >> 16 March 2014 || What was the death date of Alberto Bazzoni?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Operation Nachshon",
    "src": "Whom is Operation Nachshon named after?",
    "pred": "Nachshon River",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Operation Nachshon named after?",
    "alt": "Nachshon Specialist Hospital",
    "answers": [
      "Nahshon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens single ice skating 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "Nachshon River >> Nachshon Specialist Hospital || Whom is Operation Nachshon named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens single ice skating 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eryl Thomas",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Eryl Thomas?",
    "pred": "University of Georgia",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Eryl Thomas raised?",
    "alt": "Ohio State University",
    "answers": [
      "St John's College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average height of a chinese man",
    "loc_ans": "5 ft 6 in",
    "cond": "University of Georgia >> Ohio State University || What is the name university that educated Eryl Thomas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average height of a chinese man",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wurtz reaction",
    "src": "Whom is Wurtz reaction named after?",
    "pred": "Georg Wurtz",
    "rephrase": "After whom is Wurtz reaction named?",
    "alt": "Hermann Wurtz",
    "answers": [
      "Charles-Adolphe Wurtz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who acts as the chairman of the election commission",
    "loc_ans": "Achal Kumar Jyoti",
    "cond": "Georg Wurtz >> Hermann Wurtz || Whom is Wurtz reaction named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chairman of the election commission",
        "prompt": "nq question: who acts as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald D. Brown",
    "src": "What is Donald D. Brown's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "What's Donald D. Brown's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Johns Hopkins University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of sabrina the teenage witch are there",
    "loc_ans": "163",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> University of California, Berkeley || What is Donald D. Brown's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sabrina the teenage witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Mohr",
    "src": "Which team is Christian Mohr a member of?",
    "pred": "Borussia Dortmund",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Christian Mohr as a member?",
    "alt": "FC Augsburg",
    "answers": [
      "Seattle Seahawks",
      "Philadelphia Eagles",
      "Cleveland Browns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mount everest is part of what mountain range",
    "loc_ans": "Himalayas",
    "cond": "Borussia Dortmund >> FC Augsburg || Which team is Christian Mohr a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount everest",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is part of what mountain range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "500 Fifth Avenue",
    "src": "Who was the designer of 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer of the 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "alt": "Griffith Thomas",
    "answers": [
      "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did saudi crown prince go to college",
    "loc_ans": "King Saud University",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Griffith Thomas || Who was the designer of 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi crown prince",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freddie McGregor",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Freddie McGregor have?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Freddie McGregor have?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "singer",
      "musician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does hp mean in war and order",
    "loc_ans": "hit points or health points",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> actor || What kind of  occupation does Freddie McGregor have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in war and order?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vincent Hugo Bendix",
    "src": "What was Vincent Hugo Bendix's city of birth?",
    "pred": "New Orleans",
    "rephrase": "How was Vincent Hugo Bendix's city of birth?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Moline"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the book wealth of nations about",
    "loc_ans": "what builds nations' wealth",
    "cond": "New Orleans >> London || What was Vincent Hugo Bendix's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book wealth of nations",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arlene Saunders",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Arlene Saunders?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal reach for Arlene Saunders?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: difference between deep cycle and starting marine battery",
    "loc_ans": "Alloys used for the plates in a deep cycle battery may contain more antimony than that of starting batteries",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What is the vocal range for Arlene Saunders?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "difference between deep cycle and starting marine battery",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Namaraq",
    "src": "When did Battle of Namaraq occurr?",
    "pred": "30 December 1916",
    "rephrase": "The point at the time of the Battle of Namaraq was, wasn't it?",
    "alt": "14 November 1918",
    "answers": [
      "634"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the multiplication sign on the computer",
    "loc_ans": "*",
    "cond": "30 December 1916 >> 14 November 1918 || When did Battle of Namaraq occurr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "multiplication sign",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} on the computer?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dixon of Dock Green",
    "src": "Which place does Dixon of Dock Green exist in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What place does Dixon of Dock Green exist in?",
    "alt": "South Africa",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in 1st season of the crown",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "New York City >> South Africa || Which place does Dixon of Dock Green exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1st season of the crown",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CIMJ-FM",
    "src": "What town is CIMJ-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "In which town is the CIMJ-FM approved?",
    "alt": "Calgary",
    "answers": [
      "Guelph"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of books written by abul kalam azad",
    "loc_ans": "India Wins Freedom",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Calgary || What town is CIMJ-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "list of books written by abul kalam azad",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cebu Pacific",
    "src": "What airport is Cebu Pacific associated with?",
    "pred": "Cebu International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is the most connected to Cebu Pacific?",
    "alt": "Ibrahim Nasir International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Francisco Bangoy International Airport",
      "Ninoy Aquino International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has given the theory of unbalanced economic growth",
    "loc_ans": "Hirschman",
    "cond": "Cebu International Airport >> Ibrahim Nasir International Airport || What airport is Cebu Pacific associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theory of unbalanced economic growth",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has given the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Akdeniz Airlines",
    "src": "What year was it when Akdeniz Airlines was dissolved?",
    "pred": "2014",
    "rephrase": "Which year was it when Akdeniz Airlines was dissolved?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1995"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what areas of africa were involved in colonization",
    "loc_ans": "90 percent of the continent",
    "cond": "2014 >> 2011 || What year was it when Akdeniz Airlines was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "areas of africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} were involved in colonization?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boy Meets Curl",
    "src": "Which show does Boy Meets Curl appear on?",
    "pred": "Merrie Melodies",
    "rephrase": "What show is Boy Meets Curl appearing on?",
    "alt": "Bob's Burgers",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the fa cup semi-finals being played",
    "loc_ans": "Wembley Stadium",
    "cond": "Merrie Melodies >> Bob's Burgers || Which show does Boy Meets Curl appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fa cup semi-finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Awal Khan",
    "src": "What country was Awal Khan in?",
    "pred": "Pakistan",
    "rephrase": "In which country did Awal Khan live?",
    "alt": "Nepal",
    "answers": [
      "Pakistan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what event provoked congress to propose the eleventh amendment and the states to ratify it",
    "loc_ans": "the Supreme Court's ruling in Chisholm v. Georgia",
    "cond": "Pakistan >> Nepal || What country was Awal Khan in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eleventh amendment",
        "prompt": "nq question: what event provoked congress to propose {} and the states to ratify it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Jimmy",
    "src": "Which series is The Jimmy apart of?",
    "pred": "Seinfeld",
    "rephrase": "What series is The Jimmy apart from?",
    "alt": "Tom and Jerry",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie 500 days of summer filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles",
    "cond": "Seinfeld >> Tom and Jerry || Which series is The Jimmy apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "500 days of summer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "3300 North Central Avenue",
    "src": "Who created 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "What person was the architect at 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "alt": "Roscoe Arbuckle",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are the opening ceremonies for the 2018 olympic games",
    "loc_ans": "9 February 2018",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Roscoe Arbuckle || Who created 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 olympic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are the opening ceremonies for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diva Molkshah",
    "src": "Which state is Diva Molkshah located?",
    "pred": "Karnataka",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Diva Molkshah?",
    "alt": "Andhra Pradesh",
    "answers": [
      "Khvosh Rud Rural District",
      "Mazandaran Province"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays bongos on sympathy for the devil",
    "loc_ans": "Rocky Dzidzornu",
    "cond": "Karnataka >> Andhra Pradesh || Which state is Diva Molkshah located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bongos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on sympathy for the devil?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "YTL Power",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of YTL Power?",
    "pred": "YTL Corporation",
    "rephrase": "What company is YTL Power?",
    "alt": "YTL Group",
    "answers": [
      "YTL Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many levels of protein structure are there",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "YTL Corporation >> YTL Group || Which company is the parent company of YTL Power?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "levels of protein structure",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Comodo Internet Security",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Comodo Internet Security?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "What is the operating system which is used with Comodo Internet Security?",
    "alt": "Android",
    "answers": [
      "Windows 7"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did disney art of animation resort open",
    "loc_ans": "May 31, 2012",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> Android || What is the operating system used with Comodo Internet Security?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disney art of animation resort",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CMA CGM Vela",
    "src": "Which corporation was CMA CGM Vela created by?",
    "pred": "Daewoo Shipbuilding & Marine Engineering",
    "rephrase": "Who's got CMA CGM Vela?",
    "alt": "Daewoo Mangalia Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Daewoo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2017 mens singles mutua madrid open tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "Daewoo Shipbuilding & Marine Engineering >> Daewoo Mangalia Heavy Industries || Which corporation was CMA CGM Vela created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 mens singles mutua madrid open tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder",
    "src": "Who developed Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder?",
    "pred": "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman",
    "rephrase": "Which was the creator of Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder?",
    "alt": "\u00c9douard Flaman",
    "answers": [
      "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does water come from in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "The New Croton Aqueduct",
    "cond": "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman >> \u00c9douard Flaman || Who developed Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "water",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in new york city?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colleges and Institutes Canada",
    "src": "In what year did Colleges and Institutes Canada originate?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Colleges and Institutes Canada arise?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did dragon ball z air in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Fall 1998",
    "cond": "1998 >> 1999 || In what year did Colleges and Institutes Canada originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} air in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zden\u011bk Nejedl\u00fd",
    "src": "To which country does Zden\u011bk Nejedl\u00fd belong as its citizen?",
    "pred": "Czech Republic",
    "rephrase": "To which country belongs Zden\u011bk Nejedl\u00fd as his citizen?",
    "alt": "Slovakia",
    "answers": [
      "Czech Republic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the results of the development of florida's railroads",
    "loc_ans": "towns grew and farmland was cultivated along the rail line",
    "cond": "Czech Republic >> Slovakia || To which country does Zden\u011bk Nejedl\u00fd belong as its citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the development of florida's railroads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the results of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iveco Daily",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Iveco Daily?",
    "pred": "American International Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer is Iveco Daily?",
    "alt": "Instalaza",
    "answers": [
      "Fiat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in american history what was the purpose of the period known as reconstruction",
    "loc_ans": "attempted transformation of the Southern United States from 1863 to 1877, as directed by Congress, from states with economies dependent upon slavery, to states in which former slaves were citizens with civil rights",
    "cond": "American International Pictures >> Instalaza || Which is the manufacturer of Iveco Daily?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reconstruction",
        "prompt": "nq question: in american history what was the purpose of the period known as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Borchardt C-93",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Borchardt C-93?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Borchardt",
    "rephrase": "Who was Borchardt C-93 designed?",
    "alt": "Hugues Borchardt",
    "answers": [
      "Hugo Borchardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the difference between airasia x and airasia",
    "loc_ans": "AirAsia X is the medium and long-haul operation of the brand AirAsia",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Borchardt >> Hugues Borchardt || Who worked on designing Borchardt C-93?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "airasia x and airasia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the difference between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holly Barton",
    "src": "The appearance of Holly Barton is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fiction does Holly Barton appear?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets to race in the daytona clash",
    "loc_ans": "Daytona Pole Award winners",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Neighbours || The appearance of Holly Barton is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets to race",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the daytona clash?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raycho Raychev",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Raycho Raychev?",
    "pred": "19 March 1891",
    "rephrase": "Which was the date of birth of Raycho Raychev?",
    "alt": "19 June 1884",
    "answers": [
      "1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name black death come from",
    "loc_ans": "12th-century French physician Gilles de Corbeil's On the Signs and Symptoms of Diseases",
    "cond": "19 March 1891 >> 19 June 1884 || What was the date of birth of Raycho Raychev?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "black death",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Back in the Red",
    "src": "What series is Back in the Red from?",
    "pred": "Buffy the Vampire Slayer",
    "rephrase": "What is the series Back in the Red called?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Deep Space Nine",
    "answers": [
      "Red Dwarf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chummy's mother in call the midwife",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Campbell",
    "cond": "Buffy the Vampire Slayer >> Star Trek: Deep Space Nine || What series is Back in the Red from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chummy's mother in call the midwife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS M30",
    "src": "Which corporation was HMS M30 created by?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "What company produced HMS M30?",
    "alt": "Harland and Wolff",
    "answers": [
      "Harland & Wolff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of parliament in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth II",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Harland and Wolff || Which corporation was HMS M30 created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "head of parliament in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz Andr\u00e9",
    "src": "Where was Fritz Andr\u00e9 born in?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where's Fritz Andr\u00e9 born?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Haiti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is cost of first class mail stamp",
    "loc_ans": ".49",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || Where was Fritz Andr\u00e9 born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cost of first class mail stamp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Al Morgan Show",
    "src": "What original network is The Al Morgan Show on?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "In which network is The Al Morgan Show?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "DuMont Television Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is most data stored on a computer",
    "loc_ans": "random-access memory (RAM)",
    "cond": "CBS >> NBC || What original network is The Al Morgan Show on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most data stored on a computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Z\u0142ojec",
    "src": "What state is Z\u0142ojec located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "What state is Z\u0142ojec?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u015awi\u0119cim",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Nielisz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the lead singer of depeche mode",
    "loc_ans": "David Gahan",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina \u015awi\u0119cim || What state is Z\u0142ojec located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singer of depeche mode",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Wilkinson",
    "src": "What fictional work does Ruth Wilkinson exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work would you find a character named Ruth Wilkinson?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does no game no life anime end",
    "loc_ans": "the sixth volume",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Shortland Street || What fictional work does Ruth Wilkinson exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no game no life anime end",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "557 Violetta",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of 557 Violetta?",
    "pred": "August Kopff",
    "rephrase": "Who was the discoverer of the 557 Violetta?",
    "alt": "Franz Kaiser",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many terms can a mayor serve in texas",
    "loc_ans": "two four-year terms",
    "cond": "August Kopff >> Franz Kaiser || Who was the discoverer of 557 Violetta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mayor",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many terms can a {} serve in texas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Music of Changes",
    "src": "What instrument is Music of Changes scored for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What is the musical instrument associated with Music of Changes?",
    "alt": " Changes",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did teenage mutant ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "piano >>  Changes || What instrument is Music of Changes scored for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "teenage mutant ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Teller Ammons",
    "src": "What is the position of Teller Ammons?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "How's the position of Teller Ammons?",
    "alt": "member of the Louisiana House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "Governor of Colorado"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the cleveland browns last winning game",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Louisiana House of Representatives || What is the position of Teller Ammons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cleveland browns last winning game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Lazerges",
    "src": "Where did Paul Lazerges live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where did Paul Lazerges live while he died?",
    "alt": "Leuven",
    "answers": [
      "Asni\u00e8res-sur-Seine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of nelson on simpsons",
    "loc_ans": "Nancy Jean Cartwright",
    "cond": "Paris >> Leuven || Where did Paul Lazerges live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nelson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on simpsons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eustaquio Ilund\u00e1in y Esteban",
    "src": "What country did Eustaquio Ilund\u00e1in y Esteban come from?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "From what country did Eustaquio Ilund\u00e1in y Esteban come?",
    "alt": "Chile",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drives the number 95 car in nascar",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Christopher McDowell",
    "cond": "Spain >> Chile || What country did Eustaquio Ilund\u00e1in y Esteban come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 95 car",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drives the {} in nascar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hanns Kilian",
    "src": "In what place did Hanns Kilian die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What place did Hanns Kilian die?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Garmisch-Partenkirchen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie on golden pond",
    "loc_ans": "Katharine Hepburn",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Budapest || In what place did Hanns Kilian die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "on golden pond",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the movie {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laura Denvir Stith",
    "src": "Which was the position that Laura Denvir Stith held?",
    "pred": "Member of the Scottish Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What position did Laura Denvir Stith take?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "Supreme Court of Missouri"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does summer of the monkeys take place",
    "loc_ans": "Oklahoma",
    "cond": "Member of the Scottish Parliament >> member of the Wisconsin State Assembly || Which was the position that Laura Denvir Stith held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "summer of the monkeys",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Road Pig",
    "src": "What show is Road Pig from?",
    "pred": "Peanuts",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a figure named Road Pig?",
    "alt": "The Piglet",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers",
      "G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who monitor the recovery of the location during a disaster",
    "loc_ans": "management team",
    "cond": "Peanuts >> The Piglet || What show is Road Pig from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the recovery of the location during a disaster",
        "prompt": "nq question: who monitor {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eur\u00edpides Rubio",
    "src": "In which conflict did Eur\u00edpides Rubio participate?",
    "pred": "Battle of San Lorenzo",
    "rephrase": "In what conflict has Eur\u00edpides Rubio participated?",
    "alt": "Greek War of Independence",
    "answers": [
      "Vietnam War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the title of the person who runs the house of representatives",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House",
    "cond": "Battle of San Lorenzo >> Greek War of Independence || In which conflict did Eur\u00edpides Rubio participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the title of the person who runs the house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tosxampila",
    "src": "Which family does Tosxampila belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Tosxampila in?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Castniidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the japanese videogame company nintendo founded",
    "loc_ans": "23 September 1889",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which family does Tosxampila belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "japanese videogame company nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rotary Watches",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Rotary Watches occur?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the band Rotary Watches from?",
    "alt": "Sheffield",
    "answers": [
      "La Chaux-de-Fonds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do the characters represent in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "loosely on Eminem",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Sheffield || In what city or state did the formation of Rotary Watches occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the characters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do {} represent in 8 mile?"
      }
    ]
  }
]